<?xml version="1.0"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <link rel="hub" href="https://pubsubhubbub.appspot.com"/>

  <title>The Bold Report - Articles Only</title>
  <link href="http://theboldreport.net"/>
  <link type="application/atom+xml" rel="self" href="http://theboldreport.net/feed.article.xml"/>
  <updated>2013-10-02T14:57:41-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://theboldreport.net</id>
  <author>
    <name>Tim Smith</name>
    <email>smith@ttimsmith.com</email>
  </author>

  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/contentment-and-feeling-grateful</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/contentment-and-feeling-grateful"/>
    <title>Contentment and Being Grateful</title>
    <published>2013-10-02T14:56:56-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-10-02T14:56:56-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We all have our moments when we feel down. In my case, the past two years have been full of personal mistakes and bad decisions. Failure is difficult to accept. Yet, these things considered, it’s not the end; the book has not yet been finished, even when at times, it certainly feels like it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although, anyone would’ve considered me an optimist a year ago, it’s not so easy in practice. Yet, something I’ve forced myself to do, is always remember I have reasons to be grateful. I think it’s a good idea to do this whether you’re going through a tough time or not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I live in a very privileged part of the world, and I often get wrapped up in my own problems, client frustrations, and whining about stupidities, that I forget how much worse it could really be. My alarm in the morning could be a bomb, instead of my cute cat, and I could be in a perpetual state of worry. There are people going through much worse than I’ve &lt;em&gt;ever&lt;/em&gt; gone through, and that empathy allows me to step back and look at my life objectively.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My life isn’t perfect. I don’t make nearly as much money as I’d like, I’ve been a disappointment to people who care about me, I have debt that is far away from being paid off, I’m overweight, and I’ve hurt a girl I was in love with, twice… twice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, I have parents, family and friends that love me, and add meaning to my life. I’m healthy. I haven’t gone hungry. I work in an amazing industry, where I can say I love my job. And I live in a beautiful place that enjoys the four amazing seasons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happiness and contentment are a choice, and I &lt;em&gt;choose&lt;/em&gt; to be happy, I &lt;em&gt;choose&lt;/em&gt; to be grateful for what I have, I &lt;em&gt;choose&lt;/em&gt; to make lemonade out of lemons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Should I pour you a glass?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This post was originally written for &lt;a href=&quot;http://the-pastry-box-project.net/&quot;&gt;The Pastry Box&lt;/a&gt;. They have so many people wanting to contribute, that they weren’t able to accept my submission.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/using-portly-for-local-development</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/using-portly-for-local-development"/>
    <title>Using Portly for Local Development</title>
    <published>2013-10-02T09:52:41-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-10-02T09:52:41-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;My friend, &lt;a href=&quot;http://adamstacoviak.com/&quot;&gt;Adam Stacoviak&lt;/a&gt;, pointed me to a tool called &lt;a href=&quot;https://getportly.com/&quot;&gt;Portly&lt;/a&gt;. Portly allows you to display your local web server, publicly. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you look at the Portly site, you can tell that the applications of this menubar app, are many. I’ve been using it to do local device testing without the need for a staging server. This a very basic usage of this powerful app, but it’s been a huge timesaver for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I &lt;em&gt;always&lt;/em&gt; develop sites locally.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; One problem I constantly ran into, is that I wasn’t able to easily test sites on my different devices. Sure, you can use a bookmarklet, resize your browser, or sign up for something like BrowserStack, but I like to test from the comfort of my couch.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:2&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:2&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/2013/10/portly-screenshot.png&quot; alt=&quot;Portly Preferences&quot; title=&quot;Portly Preferences&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is where Portly comes in. I simply add a tunnel in the app, point it to my local connection string,&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:3&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:3&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; turn on the tunnel,  and go to the subdomain on my iPad or iPhone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, I know there are other ways to do this, but I just wasn’t nerdy enough to implement them. Portly is easy, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://getportly.com/plans&quot;&gt;starting at $2.99/month&lt;/a&gt;, a very good deal. You should definitely check it out. If you need help or have questions, ping me on &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/ttimsmith&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#116;&amp;#105;&amp;#109;&amp;#064;&amp;#116;&amp;#104;&amp;#101;&amp;#098;&amp;#111;&amp;#108;&amp;#100;&amp;#114;&amp;#101;&amp;#112;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#116;&amp;#046;&amp;#110;&amp;#101;&amp;#116;&quot;&gt;email me&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;If you’re working on a live server, stop that. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:2&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;I’ve found that QA is much more enjoyable—and effective—when I’m relaxed and comfortable. I turn on the TV for background noise, sit back on the couch, and browse every single page of the site. I find things I need to fix and assign myself GitHub issues. This ritual is often accompanied by a cup of coffee as well. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:2&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:3&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;For example, &lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000&quot;&gt;http://localhost:4000&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:3&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/document-everything</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/document-everything"/>
    <title>Document Everything</title>
    <published>2013-09-27T14:35:13-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-09-27T14:35:13-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Something I’ve been thinking about a lot recently is documentation. And yes, I’m thinking a little bit about legacy—documenting our life, and the things we make. However, I also mean documenting our process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s a lot of mystery surrounding what we do. I remember being a newcomer and feeling overwhelmed by everything it seemed that I needed to learn. This is where I think documentation can help us a lot. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As an industry, we’re getting comfortable with doing things in the open. &lt;a href=&quot;http://opensourcedesign.is/&quot;&gt;Open Source Design&lt;/a&gt; is trying to do this, a project which I happen to be a contributor on, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://opensourcedesign.is/resourced/&quot;&gt;there are other people doing it&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what about being open about what we charge for services? What about talking about how much designers should be making in a beginning job? Medium level? Senior level? Should we negotiate for a signing bonus? Do companies still do this? To be very honest, I only learned about some of these things a couple months ago when I had dinner with my friend &lt;a href=&quot;http://bermonpainter.com/&quot;&gt;Bermon&lt;/a&gt;. Why is this such a mystery?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On a more personal level, what about our process? I have no documentation of my personal design and development process. All of it lives in my head, which quite frankly, isn’t useful for anyone. Pricing projects could be so much simpler if I had a process to run them through. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a lot of ways, I don’t know what I’m doing. Yet, at the same time, I really do. But that knowledge is wasted if I don’t share it with others. Not to mention, there will always be people that can benefit from something I’ve learned. We’re all in different places of our career.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the past month, I’ve met so many smart people who are saying nothing. They have great ideas, but they don’t tell anyone about them. Then, there are others who are content with believing in mythical gatekeepers that prevent them from having a voice in this industry.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It’s rubbish.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to have a voice, if you want to contribute, document everything. Tell people about what you’re doing, why you did it that way, and why others should think about doing it the same. We need your voice, but no one is going to beg you to use it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As cliché as it might sound, anyone has the power to make our industry better, and personally that’s why I love our industry and working in the open. When many minds come together and collaborate and share, the end result is one-hundred times better. When more people share, we have a more diverse group of people to admire, to interview, to invite to speak, etc. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Step up. Document everything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;further-reading&quot;&gt;Further Reading&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.garann.com/dev/2013/how-to-blog-about-code-and-give-zero-fucks/&quot;&gt;How To Blog About Code and Give Zero *****&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;This particularly makes me mad. It’s so high-school drama. If you want to do something, do it. Complaining isn’t productive. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/welcome</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/welcome"/>
    <title>Dear Reader,</title>
    <published>2013-09-23T00:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-09-23T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Welcome to &lt;em&gt;The Bold Report&lt;/em&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been pondering the creation of a blog for quite some time now. In the past few months, I’ve felt that the goals I have for my writing have outgrown my personal site, and it was time to move it to its own home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Bold Report&lt;/em&gt; is that new home. If you were a fan of my personal blog, you’ll see most of the same content on here. There will be long form articles which address topics that are on my mind, and links which point you to great content or exciting news around the web. As I have before, the links will have my commentary, which I’ve found that people appreciate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The purpose of this site &lt;em&gt;is not&lt;/em&gt; to report on breaking news—there are many other sites doing that—rather to inform you of exciting new technology, products you should keep your eye on, or what I happen to be learning at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We live in fascinating times. The evolution of technology is not only influencing how we design and develop experiences, it is changing the way we interact with others and our surroundings. Whole industries have been re-imagined, and that will only continue to happen. If nothing else, I want this blog to document that, and show my predictions as false or accurate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is my hope that you’ll join me on this journey. You can find the different ways to subscribe on the &lt;a href=&quot;/subscribe/&quot;&gt;subscribe page&lt;/a&gt;. Although there are no comments on this site, please feel free to reach me &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/ttimsmith&quot;&gt;via Twitter&lt;/a&gt; or email me at &lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#110;&amp;#116;&amp;#097;&amp;#099;&amp;#116;&amp;#064;&amp;#116;&amp;#104;&amp;#101;&amp;#098;&amp;#111;&amp;#108;&amp;#100;&amp;#114;&amp;#101;&amp;#112;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#116;&amp;#046;&amp;#110;&amp;#101;&amp;#116;&quot;&gt;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#110;&amp;#116;&amp;#097;&amp;#099;&amp;#116;&amp;#064;&amp;#116;&amp;#104;&amp;#101;&amp;#098;&amp;#111;&amp;#108;&amp;#100;&amp;#114;&amp;#101;&amp;#112;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#116;&amp;#046;&amp;#110;&amp;#101;&amp;#116;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for reading, it means a lot to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;—Tim&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  

</feed>
