<?xml version="1.0"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <link rel="hub" href="https://pubsubhubbub.appspot.com"/>

  <title>The Bold Report</title>
  <link href="http://theboldreport.net"/>
  <link type="application/atom+xml" rel="self" href="http://theboldreport.net/atom.xml"/>
  <updated>2014-11-18T15:51:51-06:00</updated>
  <id>http://theboldreport.net</id>
  <author>
    <name>Tim Smith</name>
    <email>smith@ttimsmith.com</email>
  </author>

  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/11/eastwing-2</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/11/eastwing-2"/>
      <title>The East Wing: Jordan Cooper</title>
      <published>2014-11-18T00:00:00-06:00</published>
      <updated>2014-11-18T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This week: I talk with Jordan Cooper about his day job, his comedic process (spoiler: he says he doesn’t have one), and what every podcaster loves to talk about: podcasting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sponsored by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.campaignmonitor.com/&quot;&gt;Campaign Monitor&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/11/tirp-57</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/11/tirp-57"/>
      <title>The Intellectual Radio Program: Wish I Still Wanted to Be a Web Designer</title>
      <published>2014-11-13T00:00:00-06:00</published>
      <updated>2014-11-13T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This week: Chris is out, so Adam and Tim talk about finding meaning in your work, not wanting to be web designers anymore, and follow-up on the whole “golden age of podcasting” thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sponsored by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.campaignmonitor.com/&quot;&gt;Campaign Monitor&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/11/why-people-write-on-medium</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/11/why-people-write-on-medium"/>
      <title>♨ Why People Write on Medium</title>
      <published>2014-11-12T13:05:11-06:00</published>
      <updated>2014-11-12T13:05:11-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I just saw &lt;a href=&quot;https://upthemes.com/blog/2014/11/medium-to-wordpress/&quot;&gt;this post on UpThemes&lt;/a&gt; about migrating your content from Medium to WordPress. Now, I know that they’re just trying to sell their themes, but their comprehension of why people write on Medium is completely wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before I get into why they’re fundamentally wrong,&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; I’ll go ahead and say that their reasons why you might not want to be publishing on Medium, are sound. I’m all for owning your content. However, they’re also telling you that you can have everything you have on Medium with WordPress, which is a lie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People don’t write on Medium just because the reading experience is beautiful; the writing experience is too. WordPress continues to descend into more and more clutter, making writing with it cumbersome and a burden. Sites like Medium give the writer the ability to focus on writing and publishing, whereas WordPress does not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personally, it’s the biggest reason I moved over to &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;. Yet the average person doesn’t know how to create a Jekyll site, much less get it on to a server. You could go with something like &lt;a href=&quot;https://ghost.org/&quot;&gt;Ghost&lt;/a&gt;, but then you need to know Node.js.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If your goal is to write, have a great reading and writing experience, own your content, and get your site setup quickly, you solution is definitely not WordPress. In fact, you’re attached to another object by an inclined plane, wrapped helically around an axis,&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:2&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:2&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; because it doesn’t exist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;And I promise that’s not even the point of this post. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:2&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://youtu.be/DpnvS7kM4Fs&quot;&gt;The Big Bang Theory way of saying screwed.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:2&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/11/chris-bowler-on-ulysses</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/11/chris-bowler-on-ulysses"/>
      <title>Chris Bowler on Ulysses</title>
      <published>2014-11-11T13:38:55-06:00</published>
      <updated>2014-11-11T13:38:55-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Look and feel are important to me when writing. Ulysses and iA Writer both do this well. But I must admit I like that Ulysses allows me to organize my writing, as well as write. Where iA Writer has to be used in tandem with Finder, Ulysses works on its own.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Scrivener has long been the tool that people recommend for writing long content on the Mac. We’re talking novel length work. But seeing as Scrivener is a bit odd in terms of UI and seems to be updated infrequently, I can see Ulysses challenging in this arena. Ulysses nails the Markdown experience and gives a very solid document management toolset as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interesting non-review—according to Chris—of Ulysses. Seems there’s a healthy amount of apps in this space for everyone’s taste.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/11/weekly-pricing-for-web-development</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/11/weekly-pricing-for-web-development"/>
      <title>‘Weekly Pricing for Web Development’</title>
      <published>2014-11-10T12:43:57-06:00</published>
      <updated>2014-11-10T12:43:57-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Curtis McHale:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;When I’m paid weekly I’m not hoping that you’ll pay me in a timely manner. I was already paid for the week I’m working. So I’m not sweating cash-flow. I’m not trying to dig deep to get other clients and get them to pay deposits (while working for you) to keep that 40% I’m out flowing. I’m simply focused on providing you with value this week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This model makes so much sense in client services.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/11/emmets-hidden-features</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/11/emmets-hidden-features"/>
      <title>Emmet’s Hidden Features</title>
      <published>2014-11-10T12:31:15-06:00</published>
      <updated>2014-11-10T12:31:15-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Jordan Moore:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;There are heaps of really useful features alongside Emmet’s primary text-expanding function. Here are a few of the hidden gems that I frequently use when coding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/11/insanity</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/11/insanity"/>
      <title>‘Insanity’</title>
      <published>2014-11-10T12:10:23-06:00</published>
      <updated>2014-11-10T12:10:23-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Ben Brooks on &lt;em&gt;The Brooks Review&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;In the end, I just emailed the files to myself and read them, finally, on my iPad.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Insanity&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ben perfectly articulates a regular problem I have. I hope hand-off—as developers build in support—solves it.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/11/pocket-casts-gets-an-update</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/11/pocket-casts-gets-an-update"/>
      <title>Pocket Casts Gets an Update</title>
      <published>2014-11-07T00:56:57-06:00</published>
      <updated>2014-11-07T00:56:57-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Shifty Jelly updated Pocket Casts to version 5 today, and with that, two of our awesome shows on Goodstuff were featured in the post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chrisenns.com/2014/11/my-favourite-ios-podcast-app-gets-an-update/&quot;&gt;Here’s what Chris had to say&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Maybe some­day I’ll become blasé about see­ing my pod­cast show art pop up around the web, but that day is not today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks Shifty Jelly. Awesome update.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/11/making-fussy-coffee</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/11/making-fussy-coffee"/>
      <title>‘Making Fussy Coffee’</title>
      <published>2014-11-05T13:07:35-06:00</published>
      <updated>2014-11-05T13:07:35-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Peter Binkowski:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;There are a lot of people on the internet that enjoy making fussy coffee. I’m definitely one of them. However, getting into coffee doesn’t have to a pursuit in snobby-ness and complexity. I’ve found a fairly simple setup, that’s inexpensive, and produces better coffee than 80% of the coffee shops out there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Peter is one of my favorite people. His approach is snobby-ness free,&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; and gives excellent recommendations if you’re interested in making a better cup of joe. As he explains, making great coffee doesn’t have to be expensive, and can be made from the comfort of your home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Which sometimes can be difficult to find with coffee lovers. We can be a bunch of hipsters sometimes. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/11/gina-trapani-on-short-form-blogging</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/11/gina-trapani-on-short-form-blogging"/>
      <title>Gina Trapani on Short-Form Blogging</title>
      <published>2014-11-05T12:25:21-06:00</published>
      <updated>2014-11-05T12:25:21-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I find tweets too reductionist and Medium pieces too bloviating, so I came to the same conclusion &lt;a href=&quot;http://waxy.org/2014/10/middling/&quot;&gt;Andy did on mid-length writing&lt;/a&gt;. His post reminded me of a working draft I started awhile back called “New rules for blogging.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rules I plan to follow too.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/11/sam-soffes-releases-whiskey-beta</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/11/sam-soffes-releases-whiskey-beta"/>
      <title>Sam Soffes Releases Whiskey Beta</title>
      <published>2014-11-05T12:12:38-06:00</published>
      <updated>2014-11-05T12:12:38-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://usewhiskey.com/&quot;&gt;Whiskey&lt;/a&gt; is a new Markdown editor that Sam has been working on. I got in on the beta quite early because I love his work. Whiskey is looking to be an awesome app, and Sam has been updating almost daily recently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The app is great for many reasons, but the most important is this: you can tell it’s been designed and built by someone who writes a lot of Markdown. It makes a difference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, his post reminds me that I have to get better at sending him feedback. I don’t want to be one of those douchebags that just brags about being invited to betas without actually helping out.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/11/third-party-keyboards</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/11/third-party-keyboards"/>
      <title>‘iOS 8, Accessibility, and Third-Party Keyboards’</title>
      <published>2014-11-05T11:57:27-06:00</published>
      <updated>2014-11-05T11:57:27-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Steven Aquino for &lt;em&gt;MacStories&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The second problem with Apple’s implementation of third-party keyboards is they don’t have all the bells and whistles that the system keyboard does. To wit: no access to dictation or autocorrect; neither do they have access to the tap-and-hold-the-globe-button gesture to switch between keyboards. As well, switching from a light to dark keyboard for day/night, and using the &lt;code&gt;UIKit&lt;/code&gt; blur effect is also disallowed by Apple.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;All in all, the limitations that Apple imposes on developers rolling their own keyboards make them less attractive to customers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fascinating article. I hope Apple loosens its grip on the keyboards. Till then, developers can’t make the experience users truly want.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/11/the-ipad-is-in-trouble</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/11/the-ipad-is-in-trouble"/>
      <title>The iPad Is in Trouble?</title>
      <published>2014-11-04T14:31:19-06:00</published>
      <updated>2014-11-04T14:31:19-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Khoi Vinh on &lt;em&gt;Subtraction.com&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;It’s now more than ten days after they went on sale, and yet there have been no sales figure announcements, no bragging about new record-breaking numbers of iPads pre-ordered, no new milestones in adoption reached. There’s just silence. In and of itself that might not be remarkable, but the lack of news around sales numbers seems especially suspicious given that iPad sales have declined now for three quarters in a row.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This goes to show how behind I am. I had no idea that the iPad was in decline. It wasn’t until after I read the article that I realized that not much has been done for the iPad in its most recent iterations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The iPad has become a vital device for me, and many of my friends—not all in tech—feel the same. Yet for the iPad to thrive, it needs more of a commitment from Apple. Khoi says it best:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;What will it take to get there? The short answer is a new commitment from Apple to this product line, and a willingness to reexamine the company’s entire approach to date.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope Apple does the right thing. &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/11/new-york-magazine-interviews-jon-stewart</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/11/new-york-magazine-interviews-jon-stewart"/>
      <title>New York Magazine Interviews Jon Stewart</title>
      <published>2014-11-04T13:57:59-06:00</published>
      <updated>2014-11-04T13:57:59-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Jon Stewart: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;It’s very difficult to say we want the legacy to be “It was the funniest show in television history,” but you want it to be appreciated for what I think it was: consistently funny, consistently smart over a long period of time. I felt like we never took the opportunity for granted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What a great interview. Jon talks about his new film, the news, and the legacy of &lt;em&gt;The Daily Show&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/11/first-thoughts-on-incipio-ngp</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/11/first-thoughts-on-incipio-ngp"/>
      <title>♨ First Thoughts on Incipio NGP</title>
      <published>2014-11-03T16:07:45-06:00</published>
      <updated>2014-11-03T16:07:45-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/2014/10/the-wirecutter-on-the-best-iphone-6-case&quot;&gt;As I said last week&lt;/a&gt;, I was going to order a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.incipio.com/cases/iphone-cases/iphone-6-cases/ngp-flexible-impact-resistant-case-iphone-6.html&quot;&gt;Incipio NGP Case&lt;/a&gt; for my new iPhone 6. I’ve only had it three days, which isn’t enough time to write a thorough review, but just enough time for me to tell you that I love it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I received the case on Friday. I put it on and almost immediately fell in love with it. It’s light, and is thin enough to look great on the phone, but not to the point where you feel like nothing is being protected. The material is a perfect balance of soft yet firm. The case gives you more grip on the phone without being a nuisance to put in or take out of pockets. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Again, I’ve said before that I hate cases, but this case came to change everything. My first impressions are very good, and I see myself using this case in the long term. If you have hesitated at all to buy this case and had some of the same issues I did, hesitate no more. Keep on the lookout for a more in-depth review in the coming months.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/10/woman-documents-sexual-harassment-receives-rape-threats</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/10/woman-documents-sexual-harassment-receives-rape-threats"/>
      <title>Woman Documents Sexual Harassment; Receives Rape Threats</title>
      <published>2014-10-29T17:12:35-05:00</published>
      <updated>2014-10-29T17:12:35-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Cory Doctorow reporting for &lt;em&gt;Boing Boing&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Shoshana B Roberts spent 10 hours walking the streets of New York with a hidden camera crew, documenting over 100 catcalls (plus countless less-visible forms of harassment), as part of a campaign from Hollaback, who work to fight street harassment of women.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Within a day, she had over a million views – and a totally predictable passel of rape-threats from creeps.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is sad. The ensuing rape threats are not only utterly disgusting, they further prove the necessity for awareness on street harassment. Cat calling is not a compliment. The never ending focus on the female appearance is a problem that transcends our industry, and each of us can do our part in being respectful.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/10/the-wirecutter-on-the-best-iphone-6-case</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/10/the-wirecutter-on-the-best-iphone-6-case"/>
      <title>The Wirecutter on The Best iPhone 6 Case</title>
      <published>2014-10-29T13:35:07-05:00</published>
      <updated>2014-10-29T13:35:07-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, I went out and got myself an iPhone 6.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; I’ve had an iPhone since the iPhone 4, and at first I had a screen protector on it, and a bulky case.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:2&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:2&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; When I upgraded to an 5s last year, I decided that I wasn’t going to use a case anymore. I wanted it naked so as to not devalue the beauty and design of the phone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;extendout&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://theboldreport.net/uploads/2014/10/iPhone5s-front.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;My iPhone 5s on the front side. You&#39;ll notice no huge scratches or dings.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It wasn’t that bad. The phone did pretty well on some minor drops. I made it a point to treat the phone as if it had a case, but still take care of it as much as possible. In my opinion, the phone still looks pretty great, but I’ve included some pictures&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:3&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:3&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; for you to judge yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;alignright&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://theboldreport.net/uploads/2014/10/iPhone5s-back.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;The back side of my iPhone 5s. Again no scratches! I&#39;ve had this phone for a year, and that it&#39;s in such great condition without a case, is pretty surprising.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that said, when I got the new iPhone, I decided to look into cases just for kicks. &lt;em&gt;The Wirecutter&lt;/em&gt; did an amazing review of cases, and in fact they recommend one as “the best (so far)”. I’ve linked the full article and review above. If you’re also looking for a case, I think you’ll find their opinions interesting. I ordered one, and will write something on it once I’ve used it for a month or two.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:4&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:4&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;This is the first impulse buy that I’ve made in a really long time. My girlfriend had to get a new phone, and she went with the iPhone 6. After seeing it, I just had to have it.  &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:2&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;If you remember that phone, you’ll remember that the actual phone was bulky, so you’re basically carrying around a brick with a case on it. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:2&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:3&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Pictures taken with my new iPhone 6. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:3&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;One review on Youtube said, “Some people complain about the wear on this case. I’ve had it for a couple of days, and I haven’t noticed any wear.” Really? Maybe it’s because you’ve only had the case for a couple of days?! &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:4&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/10/third-avengers-split-into-two-films</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/10/third-avengers-split-into-two-films"/>
      <title>Third ‘Avengers’ Split Into Two Films</title>
      <published>2014-10-28T00:00:00-05:00</published>
      <updated>2014-10-28T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Some awesome news on &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt; today:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Everyone expected a third Avengers film a few years from now, but Marvel has a surprise for you: you’ll be getting two of them. The third Avengers film is called Avengers: Infinity War, and it’s being broken into two parts: its first part is being released on May 4th, 2018, and its second part is being released on May 3rd, 2019.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Marvel has done such an amazing job with all these different films. I hope that DC gets their act together because they have great characters to work with too. Who knows? Maybe the Batman vs. Superman film will be a great start.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/10/pinging-feedpress-with-rake</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/10/pinging-feedpress-with-rake"/>
      <title>Pinging FeedPress with Rake</title>
      <published>2014-10-27T16:08:45-05:00</published>
      <updated>2014-10-27T16:08:45-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Using Jekyll instead of a CMS like WordPress, means that some things aren’t automated like before. With WordPress, when you publish a new post, the system automatically pings services around the web letting them know you’ve published new content. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can use Rake to do this. If you use Jekyll together with FeedPress for your RSS Feed, this Gist helps you write a simple Rake task that interacts with the FeedPress API.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Easy peasy.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/10/khoi-vinhs-thoughts-on-yosemite</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/10/khoi-vinhs-thoughts-on-yosemite"/>
      <title>Khoi Vinh’s Thoughts on Yosemite</title>
      <published>2014-10-27T15:46:53-05:00</published>
      <updated>2014-10-27T15:46:53-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Spend just a bit of time with [Yosemite], and you can almost picture the iterations to come, when future releases will have fully worked out the visual language and the gestalt of the interface will have cohered to a more advanced state. OS X Balboa and OS X Palisades are going to look great.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;In the meantime, though, I find Yosemite lacking in polish, full of awkward decisions and unresolved tensions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Khoi’s opinions are spot on.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/10/retailers-are-disabling-nfc-to-block-apple-pay</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/10/retailers-are-disabling-nfc-to-block-apple-pay"/>
      <title>‘Retailers Are Disabling NFC to Block Apple Pay’</title>
      <published>2014-10-27T14:18:49-05:00</published>
      <updated>2014-10-27T14:18:49-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;John Gruber on &lt;em&gt;Daring Fireball&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Think about what they’re doing. They’re turning off NFC payment systems — the whole thing — only because people were actually using them with Apple Pay. Apple Pay works so well that it even works with non-partner systems. These things have been installed for years and so few people used them, apparently, that these retailers would rather block everyone than allow Apple Pay to continue working. I can’t imagine a better validation of Apple Pay’s appeal.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;And the reason they don’t want to allow Apple Pay is because Apple Pay doesn’t give them any personal information about the customer. It’s not about security — Apple Pay is far more secure than any credit/debit card system in the U.S. It’s not about money — Apple’s tiny slice of the transaction comes from the banks, not the merchants. It’s about data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This whole thing is very interesting. I wouldn’t go as far to conclude that Apple is the white knight in this situation—the one looking out for our best interest. The situation just happens to be in Apple’s favor. They seem to be getting everything they need to make payments easier, whereas retailers are not. And what is it that they want? Coming as no surprise: customer data.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/10/macstories-reviews-fantastical-2-2</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/10/macstories-reviews-fantastical-2-2"/>
      <title>MacStories Reviews Fantastical 2.2</title>
      <published>2014-10-22T12:06:17-05:00</published>
      <updated>2014-10-22T12:06:17-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Federico Viticci writing on &lt;em&gt;MacStories&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;With version 2.2, Flexibits has built a powerful share extension that brings the full Fantastical interface to any app that can share text and links. From Safari, Drafts, Digg, and other iOS 8 apps that properly support share extensions, you’ll be able to tap the Fantastical icon to get the app’s complete UI for event and reminder creation.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;…&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;What I like about Fantastical’s share extension is that it’s not a compromise – unlike other iOS 8 app updates, it’s not a bare-bones share sheet where you can type text with no other controls or menus. Flexibits has brought the full-blown Fantastical UI to a share sheet that has all the controls you’re used to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Federico, as usual, writes an excellent review on Fantastical 2.2. When I say excellent, I not only mean that he loves the update, but his attention to what makes a calendar great is on point. This looks like a great update.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/10/the-bold-report-version-3-0-0</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/10/the-bold-report-version-3-0-0"/>
      <title>♨  The Bold Report Version 3.0.0</title>
      <published>2014-10-22T11:39:03-05:00</published>
      <updated>2014-10-22T11:39:03-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hi Reader,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m taking a quick moment to write you about the new design on &lt;em&gt;The Bold Report&lt;/em&gt;. This is the second redesign of this site, and its third major incarnation. If you normally read links and articles via your RSS reader, please take a moment to take a look.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been up to a lot lately. &lt;a href=&quot;http://instagram.com/p/saorGTycIO/&quot;&gt;Exciting things are happening in my personal life&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://theboldreport.net/2014/10/the-east-wing-is-back/&quot;&gt;The East Wing is back&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://goodstuff.fm/dailycolumn&quot;&gt;I started a daily show&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://ttimsmith.com/membership&quot;&gt;a membership I launched&lt;/a&gt; about a month ago already has seven members that are supporting my online work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With all of that, I’ve decided it was time to get back into this site. With all my different commitments and my client work, I can’t commit to the daily posting of times past, but I would like to start writing useful articles and links again. I have a Sonos Play:1 review that I’ve been writing for almost a year, that I just need to buckle down and actually finish. Over the next few weeks, links and articles will begin to ramp up again which I’m really excited about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All in all, if you’ve been a fan of this site, I hope your patience and support will soon pay off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you from the bottom of my heart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Best, &lt;br /&gt;
Timmy Tim Tim&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/10/the-east-wing-is-back</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/10/the-east-wing-is-back"/>
      <title>The East Wing Is Back!</title>
      <published>2014-10-21T17:11:15-05:00</published>
      <updated>2014-10-21T17:11:15-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;My old show is back! I can’t tell you how excited I am. This relaunch means that we’re starting all over. We’ve started back from episode one!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This week, I talk with Guy Routledge about how he got his start, his video series AtoZ CSS, and a little behind-the-scenes work he does for the screencasts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can subscribe &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/the-east-wing/id931108499?mt=2&quot;&gt;via iTunes&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href=&quot;http://goodstuff.fm/theeastwing/feed&quot;&gt;via RSS&lt;/a&gt;. If you’re still subscribed elsewhere, please update your subscription. If you’re feeling especially kind, leave the show a rating or review in iTunes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you so much for listening and for your support!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/09/tirp-50</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/09/tirp-50"/>
      <title>The Intellectual Radio Program: You Dare Call Yourself an Apple Fanboy</title>
      <published>2014-09-11T00:00:00-05:00</published>
      <updated>2014-09-11T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This week: We talk about Adam’s vacation, explaining things to kids but of course spend the majority of the episode talking Apple’s recent announcements. Stay tuned to the end for our own special TIRP announcement as well!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Episode sponsored by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.campaignmonitor.com/&quot;&gt;Campaign Monitor&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/09/the-daily-radio-column</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/09/the-daily-radio-column"/>
      <title>The Daily Radio Column</title>
      <published>2014-09-11T00:00:00-05:00</published>
      <updated>2014-09-11T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I started a new show. It’s called The Daily Radio Column.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I was fifteen, I started a small column that I would write everyday. “Column” is a fancy word for it, really. More accurately, it was me at my computer, with Microsoft Word open (thank goodness those days are gone), writing my thoughts on the world around me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently, I found some of these, and naturally they’re terrible. But it reminded me of the importance of practicing something, and how cathardic it can be to externalize your feelings on what’s happening around you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is what I want this show to be, and I hope you’ll join me for the ride.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/08/ftr-5</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/08/ftr-5"/>
      <title>For the Record: RoboRebellion</title>
      <published>2014-08-19T10:59:45-05:00</published>
      <updated>2014-08-19T10:59:45-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This week: I talk about OnePlus: how they stuck their foot in their mouth, and robot butlers coming to a hotel near you. Myke Hurley is the guest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sponsored by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.campaignmonitor.com/&quot;&gt;Campaign Monitor&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://atozcss.com/&quot;&gt;AtoZ CSS&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.blendconf.com/&quot;&gt;Blend Conf&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://aeropresstimer.com/&quot;&gt;AeroPress Timer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/08/relay-fm</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/08/relay-fm"/>
      <title>Relay FM</title>
      <published>2014-08-11T11:42:46-05:00</published>
      <updated>2014-08-11T11:42:46-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Today is an exciting day. My friends, Stephen Hackett and Myke Hurley, have announced their new project: &lt;a href=&quot;http://relay.fm&quot;&gt;Relay FM&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Relay FM is their new network, that will house some of their classic shows, and a few new ones. I for one, am very excited for them. My sentiments align very much with &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chrisenns.com/2014/08/relay-fm/&quot;&gt;Chris’&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;In as much as some­one might think a new pod­cast net­work would be bad and add com­pe­ti­tion to &lt;a href=&quot;http://goodstuff.fm/&quot;&gt;what I’m work­ing on&lt;/a&gt;, it’s really not the case. Pod­cast­ing needs to become more famil­iar to more peo­ple so that we all rise together. And the only way that’s going to hap­pen is by hav­ing qual­ity pod­casts that draw peo­ple in to the medium.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think this new addition to the podcasting landscape is great for us as a whole. And really, the shows Myke and Stephen work on can’t really be called “new”. It’s more of a continuation of the amazing work they’ve already been doing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, I’m incredibly excited that Relay FM is powered by the CMS that &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/willmanduffy&quot;&gt;Will Duffy&lt;/a&gt; and I created. The fact that we got to work on a project like this is beyond awesome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that said, do your ears a favor, and follow the happenings of Relay FM. It’ll be some &lt;em&gt;goodstuff™&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/07/app-rot</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/07/app-rot"/>
      <title>‘App Rot’</title>
      <published>2014-07-31T08:28:44-05:00</published>
      <updated>2014-07-31T08:28:44-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Marco Arment:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The app market is becoming a mature, developed industry, with vastly increased commoditization compared to its early days. Competition is ubiquitous, relentless, and often shameless, even in categories that were previously under-the-radar niches. Standing out requires more effort than ever, yet profits are harder to come by than ever.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Full-time iOS indie developers — people who make the majority of their income from sales of their apps, rather than consulting or other related work — are increasingly rare.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The struggle of the indie developer is real. It all points to the burst of a bubble we’ve been enjoying the past few of years. I for one, hope those of us who work hard to create quality work can survive the impact.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/07/ftr-3</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/07/ftr-3"/>
      <title>For the Record: Happy &amp; Loved</title>
      <published>2014-07-23T00:00:00-05:00</published>
      <updated>2014-07-23T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This week:&lt;/em&gt; I talk about Microsoft’s layoffs, what’s happening and what it means for the company. Carol Cruz reports on relatively unchanged state borders. Meagan Fisher is the guest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sponsored by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.campaignmonitor.com/&quot;&gt;Campaign Monitor&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.blendconf.com/&quot;&gt;Blend Conf&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/04/not-just-a-boy-scout</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/04/not-just-a-boy-scout"/>
      <title>‘Not Just a Boy Scout’</title>
      <published>2014-04-24T00:00:00-05:00</published>
      <updated>2014-04-24T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The quality of shows that Moisés Chiullan produces is by far one of the best. He’s an expert moderator, and his passion for the topics really shines through.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this episode of Giant Size, they talk about Captain America. The panel, consisting of Moisés, John Gholson, Brad Graeber and Amanda Schuckman, gives such a detailed backstory helping me understand the character a lot better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Give it a listen. In fact, listen to all the ESN shows.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/04/hbo-comes-to-amazon-prime-instant-video</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/04/hbo-comes-to-amazon-prime-instant-video"/>
      <title>HBO Comes to Amazon Prime Instant Video</title>
      <published>2014-04-23T14:30:49-05:00</published>
      <updated>2014-04-23T14:30:49-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Chris Welch reporting for &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Amazon and HBO have signed an extensive, multi-year agreement that will bring many of the premium channel’s greatest shows including The Sopranos, Six Feet Under, and The Wire to Amazon Prime Instant Video. The deal also includes “early” seasons of Boardwalk Empire and True Blood. Newer shows like Girls, The Newsroom and Veep will eventually be made available to Prime subscribers, but not until three years after they’ve first aired on HBO. And other hits like Game of Thrones aren’t even mentioned as part of the deal, so HBO may be holding at least some popular content away from Amazon’s on-demand streaming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Big move by HBO. Their first deal that doesn’t require a cable subscription; a move I never thought possible considering their parent company is Time Warner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the deal doesn’t include new shows. HBO’s back catalogue is great, but most people are hungry for their latest shows. But let’s say we’re ok with getting older episodes, how long are we supposed to wait? &lt;em&gt;“Three years after they’ve first aired on HBO.”&lt;/em&gt; Ridiculous. While this is progress, they need to do better.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/04/goodstuff</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/04/goodstuff"/>
      <title>♨ Presenting Goodstuff Broadcasting</title>
      <published>2014-04-22T17:01:40-05:00</published>
      <updated>2014-04-22T17:01:40-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;On March 17th, I launched &lt;a href=&quot;http://goodstuff.fm/&quot;&gt;Goodstuff Broadcasting&lt;/a&gt; together with my good friends &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/ichris&quot;&gt;Chris Enns&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/avclark&quot;&gt;Adam Clark&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On April 8th we did a more official launch where we did live broadcasting for eight hours, and it was one of the funnest things I’ve done in a long time. We finally got to see this thing that we’ve planned and worked on for months, in the wild. The best part? People seemed to like it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Goodstuff is by no means a huge network. However, we saw from the beginning that we have a core of amazing people who listen to our shows. I can’t tell you how grateful I am about that. If you listen to our shows, a heartfelt thank you to you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what are we doing? What are we trying to accomplish? What makes us different?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those are great questions. We want to produce entertaining and educational content spanning technology (of course), culture, news, and more. As time goes by, we’d like to do shows that cover the different niches of these topics better, but we’re doing a fantastic job for a one month old network.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In terms of what we want to accomplish, all three of us want to do this full time. As you may have heard on &lt;a href=&quot;http://goodstuff.fm/tirp/31&quot;&gt;the latest episode of The Intellectual Radio Program&lt;/a&gt;, I’m so burnt out with the web. I’d love to make a transition into something else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What makes us different? That’s actually quite simple: we’re a group of nice people working hard to make great content. Unfortunately, that’s becoming a big differentiator nowadays.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you like what we’re doing, and would like to help us out, you can do that in couple of ways:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/goodstuff_fm&quot;&gt;Follow us on Twitter.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Twitter is what we use to notify everyone of shows recording live, recently published episodes, and shows we’ve added to our network.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sign up for our newsletter.&lt;/strong&gt; Chris does some really fun things with &lt;a href=&quot;http://goodstuff.fm/newsletter&quot;&gt;the newsletter&lt;/a&gt;. He updates you on the latest episodes, Goodstuff news, and more. In fact, I owe him some behind-the-scenes content about &lt;a href=&quot;http://goodstuff.fm/fullscreen&quot;&gt;Fullscreen&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Share your favorite episodes.&lt;/strong&gt; If you really enjoyed an episode of a show, or like the whole show in general, share it with people. Word of mouth recommendations are the best and are usually trusted a lot more. &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rate and Review in iTunes.&lt;/strong&gt; This we really appreciate. We don’t really understand the black magic that is the iTunes podcast directory, but we hear that ratings and reviews don’t hurt. Plus, hosts love to see reviews of their shows. The review doesn’t have to be positive, but it &lt;em&gt;should be&lt;/em&gt; useful and constructive. You can find the iTunes page for our different shows &lt;a href=&quot;http://goodstuff.fm/broadcasts&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Check out our sponsors.&lt;/strong&gt; We really appreciate our sponsors. They give us money to do something we all love doing. But, they also give us money in the hope to reach you. That’s the reality of advertising. However, because we care about both sides, we only advertise things we like and use. This way, instead of it being &lt;em&gt;advertising&lt;/em&gt;, it’s more of a friend-to-friend recommendation.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bonus: Buy a T-shirt.&lt;/strong&gt; You’ve got about five hours left to &lt;a href=&quot;http://teespring.com/goodstuff_fm&quot;&gt;get a Goodstuff t-shirt&lt;/a&gt;. A huge shoutout to &lt;a href=&quot;http://stevaker.com&quot;&gt;Steve&lt;/a&gt; for making us such a rocking logo.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In closing, thank you so much for supporting my projects. I can’t tell you how excited I am, to finally be doing this with people I love to work with. It’s the first time I’m part of a founding team, and actually enjoy it. In a short time, we’ve built a company and network that I feel fortunate and proud to be part of. &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/03/the-do-not-disturb-settings-for-presentations</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/03/the-do-not-disturb-settings-for-presentations"/>
      <title>‘The Do-Not-Disturb Settings For Presentations’</title>
      <published>2014-03-10T12:28:58-05:00</published>
      <updated>2014-03-10T12:28:58-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I had just seen an app called &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffitivity.com/hush/&quot;&gt;Hush&lt;/a&gt; that turns off notifications on your Mac. It allows you to toggle notifications or specify a period of time in which to disable them. Turns out, it’s baked into Mac OS X. As Sven points out, this is a great way in which Apple brought a feature in iOS, “back to the Mac.”&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/03/fun-facts-about-the-incredibles</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/03/fun-facts-about-the-incredibles"/>
      <title>‘Fun Facts About The Incredibles’</title>
      <published>2014-03-10T08:38:37-05:00</published>
      <updated>2014-03-10T08:38:37-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Incredibles&lt;/em&gt; is my favorite Pixar film. I hope they make a sequel, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.hollywoodreporter.com/heat-vision/brad-bird-incredibles-sequel-i-523427&quot;&gt;Brad Bird has hinted at having interest in making one&lt;/a&gt;. Till then, these are some cool things you probably didn’t know about the film.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Found via &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.loopinsight.com/2014/03/08/if-you-liked-the-incredibles-even-a-tiny-little-bit/&quot;&gt;The Loop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/01/the-east-wing-on-5by5</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/01/the-east-wing-on-5by5"/>
      <title>♨ The East Wing on 5by5</title>
      <published>2014-01-07T13:33:29-06:00</published>
      <updated>2014-01-07T13:33:29-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://5by5.tv/eastwing&quot;&gt;The East Wing has moved to 5by5&lt;/a&gt;! I’m really excited about the move, and I hope that the show will reach a lot more people. I want to thank &lt;a href=&quot;http://5by5.tv/people/dan-benjamin&quot;&gt;Dan Benjamin&lt;/a&gt; for inviting me to his network, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://sensibleworld.com/&quot;&gt;Jory Raphael&lt;/a&gt; for the gorgeous new artwork.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been working behind the scenes on this move for some time now, and I’m happy that the show is launched on it’s new home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;listening-live&quot;&gt;Listening Live&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The East Wing will now record live at &lt;a href=&quot;http://5by5.tv/live&quot;&gt;5by5.tv/live&lt;/a&gt; every Wednesday at 3pm Central.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5by5 has some pretty awesome apps that you can use to listen as well. There’s the &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/5by5-radio/id520847556?mt=8&amp;amp;partnerId=30&amp;amp;siteID=GfpxbBXXpXE-y3gfJGyOQcSr2tOpkzD12A&amp;amp;uo=8&amp;amp;at=11laDR&quot;&gt;5by5 Radio app for iOS&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/5by5-radio/id553498407?mt=12&amp;amp;partnerId=30&amp;amp;siteID=GfpxbBXXpXE-y3gfJGyOQcSr2tOpkzD12A&amp;amp;uo=8&amp;amp;at=11laDR&quot;&gt;5by5 for Mac&lt;/a&gt;. From there, you can decide to be notified when the show starts. As always, you can &lt;a href=&quot;http://theeastwing.net/schedule&quot;&gt;subscribe to the Google calendar&lt;/a&gt; which tells you the time and guest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;subscribing&quot;&gt;Subscribing&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You won’t have to do a thing. I’ve redirected the feed to the new one on 5by5. If you’re not currently subscribed, and you’d like to, the new feed is &lt;a href=&quot;feed://feeds.5by5.tv/eastwing&quot;&gt;feeds.5by5.tv/eastwing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;thank-you&quot;&gt;Thank You&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ll be recording a more in-depth state of the union for The East Wing later, but I just wanted to say thank you. Thank you for listening to the show, supporting the show by sharing it, reviewing it, and checking out the sponsors. It means a lot to me, and I hope you stick around for this new era of the show!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/01/updating-my-rss-setup</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/01/updating-my-rss-setup"/>
      <title>♨ Updating My RSS Setup</title>
      <published>2014-01-06T12:49:32-06:00</published>
      <updated>2014-01-06T12:49:32-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Back in June, I wrote &lt;a href=&quot;http://ttimsmith.com/2013/06/a-new-rss-setup/&quot;&gt;a post on my RSS consumption setup&lt;/a&gt;. The setup has changed a little, so I wanted to write an updated version that I can point people to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I wrote the first post, there were a couple of apps and services that I was using. In case you don’t want to go read the previous post, the gist was that I was using &lt;a href=&quot;https://feedwrangler.net/&quot;&gt;Feed Wrangler&lt;/a&gt; to power the backend, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.curioustimes.de/mrreader/&quot;&gt;Mr. Reader&lt;/a&gt; on the iPad, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://readkitapp.com/&quot;&gt;ReadKit&lt;/a&gt; on the Mac.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since this post, the backend hasn’t changed at all. I’m very happy with Feed Wrangler. David Smith has done a great job with it. He’s constantly working on it to make it better, and I believe only one outage in the six months of use. That’s pretty darn good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plus, the Smart Streams and Filters are great. I have all of my content filtered very well into separate folders, and as you’d assume, they sync across all the devices I use. I’m more than happy to pay $19/year for this.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-has-changed&quot;&gt;What Has Changed&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m no longer using Mr. Reader or ReadKit. Mr. Reader became frustrating with time. I didn’t like a lot of the gestures, the sounds are a bit jarring, and the interface didn’t appeal to me. Thankfully, the icon was updated to something less creepy, but I decided to go another way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m now using &lt;a href=&quot;http://reederapp.com/ios&quot;&gt;Reeder 2&lt;/a&gt;. After moving away from it because updates weren’t ready for when Google Reader shut down, I’ve come back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new iPad app is gorgeous, using the native swipe gestures wonderfully, and elegantly. It’s one of my favorite apps on iOS, as the interface clearly follows the new guidelines, yet clearly exerts its own opinion on certain interface elements. The social and read later integration is great too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve also ditched ReadKit on the mac. I’ve said this previously, although I can’t remember where, that I don’t do much reading on my Mac. If I really want to read something, I usually save it in Pocket and then read on my iPad. Still, I decided to get ReadKit to manage RSS on the occasion that I needed it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For me, it’s been a bit of a disappointment. It runs quite slow, and is buggy. However, I’ve heard a lot of people swear by it, so take my opinion with a grain of salt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s the new setup in a nutshell. If you’re barely starting with RSS, or getting back into it, I hope this helps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;It might also be important to note that Feed Wrangler hasn’t been doing some of the shady things that Feedly has had its hands in. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/01/fired-speak-no-evil</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/01/fired-speak-no-evil"/>
      <title>‘Fired? Speak No Evil’</title>
      <published>2014-01-06T12:36:25-06:00</published>
      <updated>2014-01-06T12:36:25-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Will Blyte writing for &lt;em&gt;The New York Times&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The increased prevalence of nondisparagement agreements is part of a corporate culture of risk management that would have us say nothing if we can’t say anything nice. And yet it occurs to me that if a company isn’t strong enough to be reproached, then it simply isn’t strong enough, period.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interesting perspective.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/01/twenty-thirteen-the-learnering</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/01/twenty-thirteen-the-learnering"/>
      <title>‘Twenty Thirteen, The Learnering’</title>
      <published>2014-01-03T12:13:03-06:00</published>
      <updated>2014-01-03T12:13:03-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Paul Armstrong: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;…there’s no sense in just listing the things that have transpired in a year without taking full account of why they were and are important. If you can’t determine what you’ve learned, whether good and bad, then you’re missing the chance to improve your life — and believe me, there isn’t much life to go around.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love it when Paul writes. Hell, I love it when he writes, thinks, talks, whatever. He’s got a wisdom about him and a sincerity that is difficult to find. He talks about some of the things he’s learned this past year and also gives sound advice.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/01/on-getting-the-work-you-want</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/01/on-getting-the-work-you-want"/>
      <title>On Getting the Work You Want</title>
      <published>2014-01-02T12:50:21-06:00</published>
      <updated>2014-01-02T12:50:21-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Daniel Mall: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;One of the most common questions I’m asked about design is how to get the work you really want to do. Students often bring up the fact that they feel so far away from their dream projects. Even experienced agencies make excuses like “gotta make payroll” and “we’re too busy right now.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First off, I’m honored to be mentioned in this post. I like both of Dan’s suggestions, but especially the second one. Seemingly obvious advice, yet can have such a huge impact on the work you do.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/01/the-silent-subcontractor</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/01/the-silent-subcontractor"/>
      <title>‘The Silent Subcontractor’</title>
      <published>2014-01-02T11:09:02-06:00</published>
      <updated>2014-01-02T11:09:02-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Laura Kalbag in her column on &lt;em&gt;A List Apart&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;For the last four years I’ve had this daft rule: I don’t work with agencies.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;…&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Why was I doing this? I was really just attributing a few dodgy practices to all agencies—and minimizing my potential to work with great people. By a basic definition, an agency is just a collective that produces work for clients. If I worked with one more person, I could be an agency. Now I’m feeling a bit silly for discriminating for so long.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Great advice for independent contractors. Laura’s perspective has definitely changed the way I look at the issue.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/01/the-top-10-worst-albums-of-the-year</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/01/the-top-10-worst-albums-of-the-year"/>
      <title>‘The Top 10 Worst Albums of the Year’</title>
      <published>2014-01-02T10:43:33-06:00</published>
      <updated>2014-01-02T10:43:33-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Henry Monteiro: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;As I’ve said before, 2013 was one of the best years in music I’ve seen personally.But still, even with such great music being released, there had to be some crap. Here are the 10 worst I’ve heard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love Henry’s honest and blunt critique. He’s spot on too.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/01/looking-forward</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/01/looking-forward"/>
      <title>♨ Looking Forward</title>
      <published>2014-01-01T14:27:15-06:00</published>
      <updated>2014-01-01T14:27:15-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;It’s 2014. I can’t believe I’m writing that. It seems like yesterday that I published &lt;a href=&quot;http://ttimsmith.com/2013/01/my-definition-of-success/&quot;&gt;this post&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2013 was an interesting year. It was riddled with both success and failure. Thankfully, the year ended on a high note. This was the first year that I accomplished all of my goals, except one.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My goals for 2013 were:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lose Weight&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pay Attention to the Relationships that Matter&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Speak on Design&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Work Less&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Travel More&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is quite an accomplishment! I spoke at two events last year: &lt;a href=&quot;http://minnestar.org/minnebar/&quot;&gt;MinneBar&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.blendconf.com/&quot;&gt;Blend Conf&lt;/a&gt;. I talked about the benefit of side projects, and people seemed to enjoy the talk. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In May, I quit my job at Rocket Lift, and decided to do Anythin’ Goes full-time. This has been really good for me. I’ve had the opportunity of working with some great clients, and the flexibility of managing my own schedule. I’ve also tried spending less time in front of my desk, and more time with family, friends, or other activities.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:2&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:2&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This year, I travelled a little too. I went to New York City in the summer and the fall. I had the chance to walk Central Park the second time, which was absolutely beautiful, and the weather was perfect. I went to Charlotte, North Carolina to speak, and San Diego, California to visit my folks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what do I want to accomplish in 2014? Here are my goals for this year:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lose Weight&lt;/strong&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;
I know this is a repeat, but I seriously want to tackle this. I know things that are bad for me, but I don’t really know what I &lt;em&gt;should&lt;/em&gt; be eating. I want to dedicate a bit more time into planning my menu every week, which I think will allow me to grocery shop effectively, and help me learn how to cook new dishes.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Learn Rails&lt;/strong&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;
I know I can’t possibly learn Rails in one year, but I want to get very comfortable with it. At the moment, I can build a simple application with Rails, but I’d love to get into more complex things, and start implementing best practices like tests. &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Collaborate with Friends&lt;/strong&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://avclark.com/&quot;&gt;Adam Clark&lt;/a&gt; and I have been talking about working together on something for the longest time. I’d love to finally take a project where we can work on it together. I’d also love to work with other people. 2013 was full of projects that I worked on alone, I’d like to be in a position to assemble teams for projects this year.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mentor a Student&lt;/strong&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;
Similar to &lt;a href=&quot;http://laurakalbag.com/mentoring-a-project-the-idea/&quot;&gt;Laura Kalbag&lt;/a&gt;, I’d like to guide a student through a project. I’m at a point where I can teach someone how to manage a project, and I should do my part in paying that knowledge forward.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Take Work-cations&lt;/strong&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;
Running my own business allows me to work from anywhere. There is no need for me to work from my studio 80 percent of the year. I need to start taking advantage of the flexibility I have.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those are my five goals for 2014. What do you want to accomplish?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Didn’t lose weight. Damn. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:2&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://youtu.be/3BlHY69ZsZ0&quot;&gt;So many activities&lt;/a&gt;! &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:2&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2014/01/version-two</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2014/01/version-two"/>
      <title>♨ Version 2.0</title>
      <published>2014-01-01T13:29:19-06:00</published>
      <updated>2014-01-01T13:29:19-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;With a fresh year, comes a fresh design. I had some serious issues with the previous version’s typography, which I’ve mostly addressed with this redesign. It still needs refinement, but this is a good starting point for the year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you normally read in your RSS reader, take a look at the site today. I’d love to hear what you think.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/12/tirp-17</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/12/tirp-17"/>
      <title>The Intellectual Radio Program: Time Flies When You’re Complaining on the Internet</title>
      <published>2013-12-20T13:57:31-06:00</published>
      <updated>2013-12-20T13:57:31-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;For our final episode of 2013 we talk IRC history, communicating properly with Adam, follow up on Snapchat, Adam’s new MacBook Pro and how to decide when to buy new gear for yourself. Needs vs wants.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/12/my-interview-on-the-shakes</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/12/my-interview-on-the-shakes"/>
      <title>My Interview on The Shakes</title>
      <published>2013-12-20T12:14:24-06:00</published>
      <updated>2013-12-20T12:14:24-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Pat and Jeremy were so kind to invite me on their show. We talk about how I started out, my age, Ron Burgundy, and a lot more.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/12/the-east-wing-77</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/12/the-east-wing-77"/>
      <title>The East Wing: Rachel Shillcock</title>
      <published>2013-12-20T12:07:05-06:00</published>
      <updated>2013-12-20T12:07:05-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This week: I talk with Rachel Shillcock about her speaking engagements, her new podcast, Beyond Ink, and an update on her freelancing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sponsored by &lt;a href=&quot;http://symbolicons.com/&quot;&gt;Symbolicons&lt;/a&gt;. Use the code ‘timlovesicons’ for 15% off.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/12/ala-387</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/12/ala-387"/>
      <title>A List Apart Issue 387</title>
      <published>2013-12-17T11:16:28-06:00</published>
      <updated>2013-12-17T11:16:28-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Nick Cox writes an excellent article in the last &lt;em&gt;A List Apart&lt;/em&gt; issue of the year. In &lt;a href=&quot;http://alistapart.com/article/a-moment-to-breathe&quot;&gt;“A Moment to Breathe”&lt;/a&gt;, he tells the story of how he realized he was working too much, and what he &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;forced himself&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; to do, to correct it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I find so fascinating about stories like this, is that because we’re all so passionate about our work, it can be difficult to listen when our body is telling us we need a break. But story after story (Nick’s included), we see that the world won’t end if we step back, work less, and sleep eight hours.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/12/sponsor-webydo</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/12/sponsor-webydo"/>
      <title>Sponsor: Webydo - Professional Website Design Software</title>
      <published>2013-12-17T00:00:00-06:00</published>
      <updated>2013-12-17T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://webydo.com&quot;&gt;Webydo&lt;/a&gt; enables professional web and graphic designers to create, publish, and manage pixel-perfect websites without having to write a single line of code, and provides them with the freedom of creativity to focus on what’s important—the &lt;em&gt;design&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Webydo is made by designers, for designers and is the only solution for &lt;a href=&quot;http://webydo.com&quot;&gt;website creation&lt;/a&gt; with a built in CMS (content management system) and DMS (design management system). Webydo also gives you the option to directly bill your clients, brand Webydo as your own, and provide full cross-browser capabilities. What’s more, with Webydo, you can efficiently &lt;a href=&quot;http://webydo.com&quot;&gt;create a responsive website&lt;/a&gt; with complete cross-browser capabilities as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Webydo is revolutionizing the way web designers create and work with clients, as the community of 30K designers has the power to &lt;a href=&quot;http://participate.webydo.com/forums/191312-participate-vote-&quot;&gt;vote&lt;/a&gt; on the future of which features should be added to this powerful and intuitive website creator.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Experience the freedom of creativity with Webydo’s professional online design software today for free.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A huge thanks to &lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/s/wh&quot;&gt;Webydo&lt;/a&gt; for sponsoring the RSS feed this week. &lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/&quot;&gt;Sponsorship by The Syndicate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/12/godzilla-official-trailer</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/12/godzilla-official-trailer"/>
      <title>Godzilla Official Trailer</title>
      <published>2013-12-10T12:14:14-06:00</published>
      <updated>2013-12-10T12:14:14-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Please let this one be better than &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0120685/&quot;&gt;the one from 1998&lt;/a&gt;. Brian Cranston is in it, so that’s something to look forward to.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/12/stay-organized-with-bartender</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/12/stay-organized-with-bartender"/>
      <title>Stay Organized with Bartender</title>
      <published>2013-12-10T10:45:04-06:00</published>
      <updated>2013-12-10T10:45:04-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Stephen Hackett writes a concise review of Bartender, and why it’s &lt;em&gt;The Sweet Setup’s&lt;/em&gt; best app for keeping the menu bar organized. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m a huge fan of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.macbartender.com/&quot;&gt;Bartender&lt;/a&gt;. Because I normally prefer menu bar apps, things can get cluttered pretty easily, and as Stephen points out, there are some that you don’t need to monitor 24/7.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/12/sponsor-atlassians-agile-guide</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/12/sponsor-atlassians-agile-guide"/>
      <title>Sponsor: Atlassian’s Agile Guide</title>
      <published>2013-12-10T10:25:43-06:00</published>
      <updated>2013-12-10T10:25:43-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;What’s the point of an agile standup meeting? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gone are the days of 30-minute status meetings where most people are half-asleep or pecking away on their laptops, oblivious to what’s being said. Agile standups are the leaner, more efficient cousin of status meetings where attendees actually stand up. On our feet, we’re more focused, attentive, and concise. It’s science!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether you need &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.atlassian.com/agile/project-management?utm_source=bsa-syndicate&amp;amp;utm_medium=display&amp;amp;utm_content=standup-meetings&amp;amp;utm_campaign=agile-microsite#!standup-meeting&quot;&gt;robust tools&lt;/a&gt; for planning and tracking projects, communicating with coworkers, deploying products, or just some &lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/s/w3&quot;&gt;general tips&lt;/a&gt; on how to run an agile shop (and how to run them Rong?), Atlassian is here to offer you the tools and advice you need to get the most out of your agile practice. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A huge thanks to &lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/s/w3&quot;&gt;Atlassian’s Agile Guide&lt;/a&gt; for sponsoring the RSS feed this week. &lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/&quot;&gt;Sponsorship by The Syndicate.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/12/newsstand-isnt-the-problem</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/12/newsstand-isnt-the-problem"/>
      <title>Newsstand Isn’t the Problem</title>
      <published>2013-12-05T19:20:33-06:00</published>
      <updated>2013-12-05T19:20:33-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Ben Brooks on &lt;em&gt;The Brooks Review&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;[A post on PandoDaily] blames the Newsstand icon and design on faltering sales. Perceived lack of attention from Apple, and lack of icon badging (I assume, because it is never explicitly said) were other ‘excuses’ mentioned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay, fair point. The fact that you can completely hide Newsstand can’t be good for publishers. He goes on to say:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I have a lot of respect for people making a go of digital publishing like this, and for Fleishman specifically. BUT, it seems to me that if subscribers are dwindling and people are “forgetting” about your publication, then your problem is rather straightforward: content.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Agreed. I’ve been very disappointed with the subscriptions I have in Newsstand. Blaming Apple is easy, and people just don’t “forget” about your publication.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/12/tirp-15</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/12/tirp-15"/>
      <title>The Intellectual Radio Program: I Instapaper a Lot of Things I Shouldn’t</title>
      <published>2013-12-05T18:51:37-06:00</published>
      <updated>2013-12-05T18:51:37-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This week: All three amigos are back in the SSKTN studios. We follow up on Adam’s 13″ vs 15″ debate, his smoke alarm battery, and we have a group therapy session on getting projects out the virtual door. In the words of mudmonster from the chat room—“the best TIRP yet.”&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/12/netflix-breaking-from-all-at-once-release-strategy-with-turbo-fast</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/12/netflix-breaking-from-all-at-once-release-strategy-with-turbo-fast"/>
      <title>Netflix Breaking From All-At-Once Release Strategy with ‘Turbo Fast’</title>
      <published>2013-12-04T12:17:50-06:00</published>
      <updated>2013-12-04T12:17:50-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Chris Welch on &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Netflix is deviating from the all-at-once release strategy it’s followed for House of Cards, Orange is the New Black, and the fourth season of Arrested Development. Instead of releasing an entire season on day one, just five episodes of Turbo Fast will be available for streaming on Christmas Eve. Additional new episodes will follow “throughout the year” according to Netflix.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An interesting move by Netflix, but one that makes a lot of sense. The article goes on to say: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;In its Q3 2013 &lt;a href=&quot;http://files.shareholder.com/downloads/NFLX/2822396166x0x698481/ecfe1ab4-66f5-4e23-a64a-1ca025216e5e/Q313%20Earnings%20Letter%2010.21.13%2010.30am.pdf&quot;&gt;letter to shareholders&lt;/a&gt;, Netflix noted that original shows see “more viewing in the early months” after they first premiere.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seems that their numbers drop once people are done binging on a particular show. I know of many who only renew their subscription while they watch a new series,&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; which can’t be good for Netflix financially. We’ll find out whether this is just an experiment, or their new strategy &lt;a href=&quot;/2013/12/house-of-cards-returns-in-february/&quot;&gt;come February&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;These jerks better not ruin it for the rest of us. It’s $8 people. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/12/house-of-cards-returns-in-february</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/12/house-of-cards-returns-in-february"/>
      <title>‘House of Cards’ Returns in February</title>
      <published>2013-12-04T12:14:46-06:00</published>
      <updated>2013-12-04T12:14:46-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Can’t wait.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/12/a-list-apart-386</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/12/a-list-apart-386"/>
      <title>A List Apart Issue 386</title>
      <published>2013-12-04T11:46:32-06:00</published>
      <updated>2013-12-04T11:46:32-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;In &lt;a href=&quot;http://alistapart.com/article/surveying-the-big-screen&quot;&gt;“Surveying the Big Screen”&lt;/a&gt;, Mike Pick does a great job of pointing out the need to explore the possibilities on larger screens.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; Alex Feyerke writes an excellent article titled &lt;a href=&quot;http://alistapart.com/article/offline-first&quot;&gt;“Designing Offline-First Web Apps”&lt;/a&gt;, and talks about a fact of life—being offline. How does that affect the way we design and build applications?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Be sure to check out &lt;a href=&quot;http://d.alistapart.com/386/surveying_the_big_screen/demo/&quot;&gt;the CSS Columns-based demo&lt;/a&gt; that Mike created for this article. (via &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/murtaugh&quot;&gt;Tim Murtaugh&lt;/a&gt;) &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/12/yahoo-year-in-review-report</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/12/yahoo-year-in-review-report"/>
      <title>Yahoo’s ‘Year in Review’ Report</title>
      <published>2013-12-03T12:03:31-06:00</published>
      <updated>2013-12-03T12:03:31-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Ken Yeung on &lt;em&gt;The Next Web&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Are there any shockers in the top searches of 2013? What may come as no surprise to some people is that Miley Cyrus takes the top spot, followed by Kim Kardashian, and American model Kate Upton. Minecraft and Apple’s iPhone 5 are the only two technology-related queries to make it into the top 10.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Shocking&lt;/em&gt;. It should be cause of concern that in the top ten searches on Yahoo, only &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;one&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; of them is a current news item that people should be well informed on. &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/12/sponsor-pencils-com</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/12/sponsor-pencils-com"/>
      <title>Sponsor: Pencils.com</title>
      <published>2013-12-03T11:37:56-06:00</published>
      <updated>2013-12-03T11:37:56-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;At &lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/s/vp&quot;&gt;Pencils.com&lt;/a&gt;, we believe that creativity is the greatest of all virtues. And, with our selection of unique, high-quality pencils, notebooks, and creative tools, we’ve got everything you need to unleash yours. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether you’re a pencil nut who knows all the brands (&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.pencils.com/all-brands/caran-d-ache?utm_source=syndicate&amp;amp;utm_medium=post&amp;amp;utm_content=caran&amp;amp;utm_campaign=dec&quot;&gt;Caran d’Ache&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.pencils.com/all-brands/blackwing?utm_source=syndicate&amp;amp;utm_medium=post&amp;amp;utm_content=blackwing&amp;amp;utm_campaign=dec&quot;&gt;Blackwing&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.pencils.com/all-brands/faber-castell?utm_source=syndicate&amp;amp;utm_medium=post&amp;amp;utm_content=faber&amp;amp;utm_campaign=dec&quot;&gt;Faber-Castell&lt;/a&gt;, we stock them all), or a casual doodler looking for something to inspire you, there’s something for you on Pencils.com. Combine that with our legendary customer service and fast, reliable shipping, and you’ve got some serious creative potential.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, go ahead and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.pencils.com/brands/blackwing?utm_source=syndicate&amp;amp;utm_medium=post&amp;amp;utm_content=blackwing&amp;amp;utm_campaign=dec&quot;&gt;read the story of the $40 pencil&lt;/a&gt;, learn about &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.pencils.com/brands/faber-castell?utm_source=syndicate&amp;amp;utm_medium=post&amp;amp;utm_content=faber&amp;amp;utm_campaign=dec&quot;&gt;the pencil company that has been around since the French Revolution&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.pencils.com/journals-sketchbooks/luxury-journals?utm_source=syndicate&amp;amp;utm_medium=post&amp;amp;utm_content=journals&amp;amp;utm_campaign=dec&quot;&gt;find the perfect notebook to capture your ideas&lt;/a&gt;. If you’re in the giving mood, we also have gifts for &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.pencils.com/gift-ideas/gifts-for-artists?utm_source=syndicate&amp;amp;utm_medium=post&amp;amp;utm_content=gifts-for-artists&amp;amp;utm_campaign=dec&quot;&gt;artists&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.pencils.com/gift-ideas/gifts-for-writers?utm_source=syndicate&amp;amp;utm_medium=post&amp;amp;utm_content=gifts-for-writers&amp;amp;utm_campaign=dec&quot;&gt;writers&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.pencils.com/gift-ideas/gifts-for-musicians?utm_source=syndicate&amp;amp;utm_medium=post&amp;amp;utm_content=gifts-for-musicians&amp;amp;utm_campaign=dec&quot;&gt;musicians&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.pencils.com/gift-guide?utm_source=syndicate&amp;amp;utm_medium=post&amp;amp;utm_content=gift-guide&amp;amp;utm_campaign=dec&quot;&gt;anyone else&lt;/a&gt; on your shopping list. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Above all else, stay creative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A big thank you to &lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/s/vp&quot;&gt;Pencils.com&lt;/a&gt; for sponsoring the RSS feed this week. &lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/&quot;&gt;Sponsorship by The Syndicate.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/12/beyond-ink</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/12/beyond-ink"/>
      <title>Beyond Ink</title>
      <published>2013-12-02T11:13:39-06:00</published>
      <updated>2013-12-02T11:13:39-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;My friend, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.rachil.li/&quot;&gt;Rachel Shillcock&lt;/a&gt;, launched her new podcast called &lt;em&gt;Beyond Ink&lt;/em&gt;. She’s a natural in front of the microphone, and does &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.beyondink.co.uk/shows/01-laura-and-simon&quot;&gt;a great first show with Simon Collison and Laura Kalbag&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She’ll hopefully be on &lt;em&gt;The East Wing&lt;/em&gt; later this month to talk more about her new show.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/12/ron-burgundy-takes-over-local-news-to-promote-anchorman-2</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/12/ron-burgundy-takes-over-local-news-to-promote-anchorman-2"/>
      <title>Ron Burgundy Takes Over Local News to Promote ‘Anchorman 2’</title>
      <published>2013-12-02T10:48:57-06:00</published>
      <updated>2013-12-02T10:48:57-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Kwame Opam on &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The theatrical release of Anchorman 2: The Legend Continues is only weeks away, and the promotion campaign for the film is only getting wilder. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.theverge.com/2013/11/25/5143208/anchorman-2-targets-the-social-web-with-more-than-50-short-videos&quot;&gt;After starring in 50 short clips where Ron Burgundy reads news from around the world&lt;/a&gt;, Will Ferrell co-anchored a live news broadcast in North Dakota last night, staying in character the entire time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hilarious. The way they’ve promoted this film is absolute genius, and I can’t wait to watch it.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/12/amazon-plans-to-use-drones-for-new-prime-air-service</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/12/amazon-plans-to-use-drones-for-new-prime-air-service"/>
      <title>Amazon Plans to Use Drones for New Prime Air Service</title>
      <published>2013-12-02T10:28:44-06:00</published>
      <updated>2013-12-02T10:28:44-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;John Ribeiro on &lt;em&gt;TechHive&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Amazon.com plans to deliver packages to customers using unmanned aerial vehicles in 30 minutes or less.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;“It looks like science fiction, but it’s real,” Amazon said on its website. Its Prime Air service, powered by drones, will be ready from a technology point of view to enter commercial operations as soon as the necessary regulations are in place, it said. The company’s research and development team is already working on the new delivery method.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know whether I should be enthused or panicked by this story. I think the answer is both.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/11/organize-that-sass</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/11/organize-that-sass"/>
      <title>Organize that Sass!</title>
      <published>2013-11-27T10:18:11-06:00</published>
      <updated>2013-11-27T10:18:11-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;One of the many beauties of working with Sass is how easy it is to get organized. In the past, importing different CSS files wasn’t good practice and in fact made for more HTTP requests. With Sass, you can have many different partials which allow you to isolate styles in a logical way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m so excited about my first post for the &lt;em&gt;A List Apart&lt;/em&gt; blog! It’s a quick post on using partials to get organized with Sass.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/11/magneto-blamed-for-jfk-murder</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/11/magneto-blamed-for-jfk-murder"/>
      <title>Magneto Blamed for JFK Murder</title>
      <published>2013-11-27T09:48:03-06:00</published>
      <updated>2013-11-27T09:48:03-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Kwame Opam on &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;To promote the upcoming X-men: Days of Future Past, a new viral site takes the 50th anniversary of JFK’s murder and spins a new conspiracy theory out of the historic tragedy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some will say this is wrong, but it’s quite an interesting twist on actual history, and an intriguing way to promote a movie.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/11/kobe-bryants-signs-2-year-extension-with-lakers</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/11/kobe-bryants-signs-2-year-extension-with-lakers"/>
      <title>Kobe Bryant Signs 2-Year Extension with Los Angeles Lakers</title>
      <published>2013-11-26T13:14:11-06:00</published>
      <updated>2013-11-26T13:14:11-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Kobe Bryant signed a two-year contract extension with the Los Angeles Lakers on Monday.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;The Lakers did not announce financial terms, but a source told ESPNLosAngeles.com’s Ramona Shelburne that the deal is worth $48.5 million.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even as a huge Laker fan, I don’t see the logic behind this decision. Kobe Bryant has been one of the best players of the current era, but I certainly thought this would be his last year. As great as he is, age eventually catches up with you. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;But&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; I could be terribly wrong. They don’t call him the Black Mamba for nothing.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/11/the-sweet-setup</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/11/the-sweet-setup"/>
      <title>The Sweet Setup</title>
      <published>2013-11-26T12:56:52-06:00</published>
      <updated>2013-11-26T12:56:52-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://shawnblanc.net/&quot;&gt;Shawn Blanc&lt;/a&gt; launched a new site last week, called The Sweet Setup. I’ve always payed close attention to Shawn’s app recommendations, but creating a site just for these is a great idea.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/11/sponsor-fracture-your-picture-directly-on-glass</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/11/sponsor-fracture-your-picture-directly-on-glass"/>
      <title>Sponsor: Fracture. Your picture, directly on glass.</title>
      <published>2013-11-26T12:22:09-06:00</published>
      <updated>2013-11-26T12:22:09-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://fractureme.com/?utm_source=syndicate&amp;amp;utm_medium=post&amp;amp;utm_content=fracture&amp;amp;utm_campaign=syn2&quot;&gt;Fracture&lt;/a&gt; prints your photo in vivid color directly on glass. It’s a picture, frame, &amp;amp; mount all in one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a &lt;a href=&quot;http://fractureme.com/?utm_source=syndicate&amp;amp;utm_medium=post&amp;amp;utm_content=modern&amp;amp;utm_campaign=syn2&quot;&gt;modern, elegant, and affordable way&lt;/a&gt; to print and display your favorite memories. Your print comes with everything you need to display your photo, right in the durable packaging.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fractures come in a variety of &lt;a href=&quot;http://fractureme.com/affordable-framing-prices?utm_source=syndicate&amp;amp;utm_medium=post&amp;amp;utm_content=sizes&amp;amp;utm_campaign=syn2&quot;&gt;sizes and prices&lt;/a&gt;, starting at just $12, with free shipping on orders of $100 or more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fracture prints make great gifts and are the perfect way to fill up empty walls in your new home or apartment. &lt;a href=&quot;http://fractureme.com/?utm_source=syndicate&amp;amp;utm_medium=post&amp;amp;utm_content=check&amp;amp;utm_campaign=syn2&quot;&gt;Check it out.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Big thanks to &lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/s/vb&quot;&gt;Fracture&lt;/a&gt; for sponsoring this week’s RSS Feed. &lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/&quot;&gt;Sponsorship by The Syndicate.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/11/geri-coady-on-design-trends</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/11/geri-coady-on-design-trends"/>
      <title>Geri Coady on Design Trends</title>
      <published>2013-11-21T10:56:11-06:00</published>
      <updated>2013-11-21T10:56:11-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Should we really be dropping buttons, even if it negatively affects intuitive interaction patterns or confuses people with cognitive disabilities? Should we really be using thin type to look “modern” at the risk of decreasing legibility? And tell me, should we really be dropping textures and reducing contrast because it’s the “stylish” thing to do this week?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Geri makes some amazing points, and then drops the mic. Such a great read.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/11/sponsor-voila-ultimate-screen-capture-solution-for-your-mac</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/11/sponsor-voila-ultimate-screen-capture-solution-for-your-mac"/>
      <title>Sponsor: Voila: Ultimate Screen Capture Solution for your Mac</title>
      <published>2013-11-21T08:34:24-06:00</published>
      <updated>2013-11-21T08:34:24-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/s/ux&quot;&gt;Voila&lt;/a&gt; is the most powerful screen capturing software available for your Mac. Voila lets you capture and record content and then easily share it with friends and co-workers or upload it to the web.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/s/ux&quot;&gt;Voila&lt;/a&gt; is the perfect screen recorder for your Mac. You can easily make high-quality product demos, DIY app simulations, and tutorials. Create interactive content by recording your Mac screen along with audio and all your click streams. Then complete your screencast by annotating your screenshots with professional tools and features. Record like a pro and publish your final project to FTP/SFTP, Tumblr, Dropbox, Evernote, and YouTube with Voila.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Made for Mavericks, Voila is simple and intuitive. With Voila, keep your captures organized and within your reach while enjoying a boost in productivity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Try Voila today. &lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/s/ux&quot;&gt;Download Free Trial.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Thanks to &lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/s/ux&quot;&gt;Voila&lt;/a&gt; for sponsoring the RSS feed this week. &lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/&quot;&gt;Sponsorship by The Syndicate.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/11/twitter-tests-cleaner-web-design</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/11/twitter-tests-cleaner-web-design"/>
      <title>Twitter Tests Cleaner Web Design</title>
      <published>2013-11-21T00:00:00-06:00</published>
      <updated>2013-11-21T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Darrell Etherington on &lt;em&gt;TechCrunch&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Twitter is testing a new website design, which opts for a lighter, flat design that seems at least partly inspired by its shift to similar design trends on mobile.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This looks terrible. It lacks the polish it should have. The type continues to feel tight, and the fact that they’re going “flat”, is disappointing.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/11/why-you-should-use-sass</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/11/why-you-should-use-sass"/>
      <title>Why You Should Use Sass</title>
      <published>2013-11-15T14:31:59-06:00</published>
      <updated>2013-11-15T14:31:59-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dan Cederholm on &lt;em&gt;A List Apart&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;…the reality is that Sass (and other CSS preprocessors) can be a powerful ally—a tool that any style-crafter can easily insert into their daily work. It took me a while to come around, but I’m sure glad that I did.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We published a great excerpt from Dan’s new book &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.abookapart.com/products/sass-for-web-designers&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sass for Web Designers&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Dan has been long regarded as one of the best when it comes to CSS, and I can’t wait to finish reading this new book. If you’re on the fence about whether to buy the book, this great excerpt might be just the thing to whet your appetite.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/11/sponsor-lootback</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/11/sponsor-lootback"/>
      <title>Sponsor: Lootback</title>
      <published>2013-11-14T12:50:24-06:00</published>
      <updated>2013-11-14T12:50:24-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/2013/11/Lootback.png&quot; alt=&quot;Lootback ad&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.executionists.com/blog/website-design/cost-to-build-websites-2013/&quot;&gt;According to recent research&lt;/a&gt;, the average small business owner can expect to pay somewhere between $100 and $200 for stock images for their website. Of course, for the owner going through a professional designer, this is just part of a larger number. If you’re a designer, you should always be looking for ways to bring down the final cost of a website. Outbidding the competition isn’t the only factor when it comes to success, but cutting costs where possible certainly won’t hurt. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’ve been looking for a way to bring down your stock image costs and increase your bottom line, a new website may be able to help. It’s called Lootback.com, and it functions as a stock image search engine. The site partners with some of the biggest names in the stock photo industry, including iStock, ShutterStock, Graphicriver, Themeforest, and more. The premise is simple: they get a commission on every photo you buy through their site and then split that commission with you. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/s/uj&quot;&gt;Lootback&lt;/a&gt; provides users with a compilation image search engine. You type in whichever keywords fit your needs and it will come back with results from their industry partners. Helpfully, once you’ve created an account, Lootback will tell you right away how much you will save on a particular image once you’ve clicked on it. Rebates are paid into your account within 12 hours. That said, Lootback only pays out 4 times a year, so don’t expect cash back right away. Still, if you’re a designer who buys hundreds of images a year, the savings could prove substantial.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are a lot of websites out there that promise to save the average shopper some money, but very few are dedicated to helping out web designers. Lootback aims to save designers time and money and they do a pretty good job of it. If you’ve been in search of a way to bring down your costs, &lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/s/uj&quot;&gt;Lootback&lt;/a&gt; is a good place to start.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Thanks to &lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/s/uj&quot;&gt;Lootback&lt;/a&gt; for sponsoring the RSS feed this week. &lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/&quot;&gt;Sponsorship by The Syndicate.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/11/marvel-creating-superhero-shows-for-netflix</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/11/marvel-creating-superhero-shows-for-netflix"/>
      <title>Marvel Creating Superhero Shows for Netflix</title>
      <published>2013-11-07T12:55:45-06:00</published>
      <updated>2013-11-07T12:55:45-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Jacob Kastrenakes reporting for &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Marvel is creating four live-action superhero series and an Avengers-style special event that will all air exclusively on Netflix, beginning in 2015. The first of the TV series will focus on Daredevil, while the following series will star Jessica Jones, Iron Fist, and Luke Cage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Netflix does it again. Can’t wait to see this. &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/11/sponsor-meet-techi-all-the-tech-news-in-one-place</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/11/sponsor-meet-techi-all-the-tech-news-in-one-place"/>
      <title>Sponsor: Meet Techi: All the tech news in ONE place</title>
      <published>2013-11-05T11:04:04-06:00</published>
      <updated>2013-11-05T11:04:04-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/2013/11/techi.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Techi.com ad&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/s/u5&quot;&gt;Techi.com&lt;/a&gt; is a site dedicated to all things tech. From updates on Sony’s PS4 to reports on Google’s latest acquisition; whether you’re looking for the latest Apple product or looking for views on mobile web, Techi is the site to visit. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Techi.com’s news is sourced from thousands of sites from across the Internet, then curated by an editorial team with their finger constantly on the pulse of the industry’s most vital developments. You also get a quick summary of the news so you save time and read only what interests you most. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to the best news curated from across the Web, &lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/s/u5&quot;&gt;Techi.com&lt;/a&gt; also offers exclusive original articles and stories featured in the Drudge Report, Reddit, NYTimes, Google news, and many more. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You don’t even have to visit daily. Just sign up for the daily newsletter and get the latest tech news direct to your inbox — with no fuss whatsoever — in time for that commute or mid-day coffee. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t spend your morning sifting through RSS feeds looking for the hot news. Go for the instant solution: get it all from Techi.com in less time than it takes to make your coffee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Thanks to &lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/s/u5&quot;&gt;Techi.com&lt;/a&gt; for sponsoring the RSS feed this week. &lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/&quot;&gt;Sponsorship by The Syndicate.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/11/blackberry-secures-1-billion-in-funding</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/11/blackberry-secures-1-billion-in-funding"/>
      <title>BlackBerry Secures $1 Billion in Funding</title>
      <published>2013-11-04T10:53:00-06:00</published>
      <updated>2013-11-04T10:53:00-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Vlad Savov reporting for &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Today was always going to be a momentous day for BlackBerry, with a looming deadline for its proposed takeover deal with Fairfax Financial Holdings. As it turns out, the full takeover isn’t taking place, but the company is going to receive an investment of $1 billion from Fairfax and a group of other institutional investors as it seeks to steer a new course.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What? I mean, it’s tough to feel bad for a company that just received a billion dollars, but what are they doing? BlackBerry is holding on for dear life, and I have to wonder whether this can turn things around for them. I hope for the best.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/11/twitter-facing-challenges-in-japan-and-korea</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/11/twitter-facing-challenges-in-japan-and-korea"/>
      <title>Twitter Facing Monetary Challenges in Japan and Korea</title>
      <published>2013-11-04T10:39:46-06:00</published>
      <updated>2013-11-04T10:39:46-06:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Reported on &lt;em&gt;The Next Web&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Twitter is strong in Japan (as &lt;a href=&quot;http://thenextweb.com/socialmedia/2011/02/02/why-twitter-outguns-facebook-in-japan/&quot;&gt;we noted back in 2011&lt;/a&gt;) where it’s used by one-third of the Internet population — but the country accounts for under 10 percent of its global revenue and one ad exec told WSJ that many Japanese brands “don’t think Twitter is something to pay money for.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This particular post is interesting to me. Twitter is facing challenges &lt;em&gt;everywhere&lt;/em&gt;. Why is it news that advertisers don’t want to pay in these specific places?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that said, I really do admire these new ways of generating revenue that they’re trying. Partnering with TV, although I originally didn’t understand it, makes a lot of sense, and is one alternative to the advertising route that so many seem to just default to.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/11/rules-of-tech-journalism</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/11/rules-of-tech-journalism"/>
      <title>Rules of Tech Journalism</title>
      <published>2013-11-01T11:08:56-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-11-01T11:08:56-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Harry Marks:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Things have gotten out of hand. Tech writers are given far too much freedom to perpetuate inaccuracies and falsehoods, as well as a generous helping of incompetence these days. That’s why it’s time to put a bit of structure in place for those publications that don’t understand good work from bad work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is an interesting read. Although &lt;em&gt;The Bold Report&lt;/em&gt; isn’t incredibly popular yet, I’ve always tried to hold myself to the rules of proper journalism. I &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;do not&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; want to contribute to the assumption that online writers are an unprofessional bunch.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/adobe-security-breach-worse-than-originally-thought</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/adobe-security-breach-worse-than-originally-thought"/>
      <title>Adobe Security Breach Worse Than Originally Thought</title>
      <published>2013-10-29T15:10:09-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-29T15:10:09-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Jared Newman reporting for &lt;em&gt;Macworld&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;When &lt;a href=&quot;http://blogs.adobe.com/conversations/2013/10/important-customer-security-announcement.html&quot;&gt;Adobe announced the breach on October 3&lt;/a&gt;, it said that attackers stole user names and encrypted passwords for an undisclosed numbers of users, along with encrypted credit or debit card numbers and expiration dates for 2.9 million customers. &lt;a href=&quot;http://krebsonsecurity.com/2013/10/adobe-breach-impacted-at-least-38-million-users/&quot;&gt;Krebs on Security now reports&lt;/a&gt; on the full extent of the attack, confirming the 38 million figure with Adobe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wow. 2.9 million was already a huge number, but now thirty-eight million? I’m keeping a close watch on my card to see if it’s being used, and I’d recommend you do the same. Also, if you were using the same password in multiple places, it might be a good time to look into 1Password. At this point, the probability of your information &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; being involved in this attack is low.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/billy-joel-interviewed-on-heres-the-thing</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/billy-joel-interviewed-on-heres-the-thing"/>
      <title>Billy Joel Interviewed on Here’s the Thing</title>
      <published>2013-10-28T20:30:17-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-28T20:30:17-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I &lt;em&gt;love&lt;/em&gt; Billy Joel, and I &lt;em&gt;love&lt;/em&gt; Alec Baldwin. With every episode that goes by, I’m amazed at how great of an interviewer Mr. Baldwin is. They talk about Joel’s early days, songs that weren’t hits but now considered classics, and a lot more.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/metalab-launches-peak</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/metalab-launches-peak"/>
      <title>MetaLab Launches Peak</title>
      <published>2013-10-28T20:13:39-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-28T20:13:39-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/matro/status/394982616132517889&quot;&gt;Matt Pearson&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Being micromanaged by robots is no better than by humans. This kind of stats-obsessed moronity breeds a toxic workplace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I couldn’t agree more. Although this product might have been created with great intentions, I can easily see it being abused. If people work for you, ask them to update you. Don’t spy on them, even if under the guise of “avoiding shoulder taps.”&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/apple-reports-fourth-quarter-profit</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/apple-reports-fourth-quarter-profit"/>
      <title>Apple Reports Fourth Quarter Profit</title>
      <published>2013-10-28T16:59:17-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-28T16:59:17-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Jim Dalrymple on &lt;em&gt;The Loop&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Apple on Monday reported its fourth quarter results, posting revenue of $37.5 billion and a profit of $7.5 billion. This compares to revenue of $36 billion and net profit of $8.2 billion in the year-ago quarter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love Apple, but the amount of success they have is sickening at times. This is a stupid amount of money.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/honest-slogans</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/honest-slogans"/>
      <title>Honest Slogans</title>
      <published>2013-10-28T12:07:43-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-28T12:07:43-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hilarious, and true. This is Tumblr at its best. &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/marco-arment-on-apples-recent-event</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/marco-arment-on-apples-recent-event"/>
      <title>Marco Arment on Apple’s Recent Event</title>
      <published>2013-10-25T12:19:57-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-25T12:19:57-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Something felt a bit off about this week’s Apple event.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Part of it was the lack of surprises, which isn’t Apple’s fault. All of the product upgrades, while nice, were incremental and predictable. None of the pricing was a surprise. In fact, the only unexpected product announcement is the zombie iPad 2 sticking around for another year, shamelessly at the same price as last year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I agree. It felt weird, and ended abruptly.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/tapbots-launches-new-tweetbot</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/tapbots-launches-new-tweetbot"/>
      <title>Tapbots Launches New Tweetbot</title>
      <published>2013-10-25T12:02:12-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-25T12:02:12-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;While I admire all the hard work that went in creating this new version of Tweetbot, I can’t help be a little disappointed. The app has lost much of its personality; both visually and sonically. The new app has some very well done animations, but unfortunately looks too “default iOS 7” for my taste. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, I did purchase because I respect the work of Tapbots very much and I want to support them. They have the reputation of making incredible things, and I look forward to seeing the betterment of Tweetbot.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/does-the-web-industry-have-a-drinking-problem</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/does-the-web-industry-have-a-drinking-problem"/>
      <title>Does the Web Industry Have a Drinking Problem?</title>
      <published>2013-10-24T11:49:34-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-24T11:49:34-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Rachel Andrew writing on &lt;em&gt;A List Apart&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Almost every conference’s second day opens with attendees being asked how their hangovers are. Second day early-slot speakers joke that no one will turn up anyway, or they’ll all just be staring into their coffee. It has become normal, in fact expected, that drinking and staying out late is what we do while at conferences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think Rachel brings up a very real issue with our conferences and events. Because our industry is very friendly, and social, it seems we might be blurring the lines of professional time and social time, a bit too much. She goes on to say:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;We’re also underlining that our events are for over-18s, maybe even over-21s, by holding them in licensed premises. Most of us know students or even those who are working professionally in our field long before they are “adult.” Should they be excluded?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t get me wrong, I enjoy having drinks—and the article isn’t advocating for the banishment of alcohol—but I remember being the seventeen year-old kid that couldn’t drink. I’ve always been very extroverted, so it never stopped me from talking to people. However, I can see how it could affect others; making them feel excluded and not part of the group, and Rachel’s article does a great job of shining light on that fact.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/amazon-s-biodome-approved-in-seattle</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/amazon-s-biodome-approved-in-seattle"/>
      <title>Amazon’s Biodome Approved in Seattle</title>
      <published>2013-10-24T11:27:21-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-24T11:27:21-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I love this. Architecture is an integral part of the beauty and history of our cities. The fact that companies like Amazon, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.macrumors.com/2013/10/17/apple-cfo-peter-oppenheimer-speaks-about-apple-campus-2-at-cupertino-press-conference/&quot;&gt;Apple&lt;/a&gt; are doing things to contribute to that history, in the cities they call home, is a very good thing.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/samsung-fine-340-000-in-taiwan-for-fake-online-comments</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/samsung-fine-340-000-in-taiwan-for-fake-online-comments"/>
      <title>Samsung Fined $340,000 in Taiwan for Fake Online Comments</title>
      <published>2013-10-24T11:06:11-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-24T11:06:11-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Aaron Souppouris reporting for &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;After being caught paying for false praise and negative comments about competitors, Samsung has been fined just over $340,000. The issue first arose internationally in April, when Taiwan’s Fair Trade Commission (FTC) announced it was opening an investigation into the allegations. That investigation found the allegations were true: the FTC says Samsung used a “large number of hired writers and designated employees” to post in Taiwanese forums.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Embarrassing. But wait! There’s more!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;While Samsung is by no means the first company to engage in astroturfing, it’s been caught in the act twice this year alone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only are they engaging in unethical marketing practices—which hilariously enough has an official term—they’ve been caught doing it &lt;em&gt;twice&lt;/em&gt; in the same year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Get your stuff together, Samsung. You’re better than this.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/microsoft-talks-apple-ipads-and-iwork</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/microsoft-talks-apple-ipads-and-iwork"/>
      <title>Microsoft Talks Apple iPads and iWork</title>
      <published>2013-10-23T16:30:34-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-23T16:30:34-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Frank Shaw on &lt;em&gt;The Official Microsoft Blog&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Surface and Surface 2 both include Office, the world’s most popular, most powerful productivity software for free and are priced below both the iPad 2 and iPad Air respectively. Making Apple’s decision to build the price of their less popular and less powerful iWork into their tablets not a very big (or very good) deal.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;…&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;I think they, like others, are waking up to the fact that we’ve built a better solution for people everywhere, who are getting things done from anywhere, and who don’t have hard lines between their personal and professional lives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Microsoft looks incredibly stupid for publishing this garbage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Who cares that you made a device you think “is the most productive tablet you can buy today,” when it’s not selling? Eighty-one percent of tablet usage is on the iPad, and I highly doubt that the Surface has a significant share of the remaining nineteen percent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Microsoft has so much untapped potential they could use for making great new products. Instead, they waste their time writing a post like this that claims they understand “how people work better than anyone else.” Talk is cheap, but the fact is this: while Microsoft was busy loosing $900 million on Surface tablets in Q3 2013, Apple sold 14.6 million iPads.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/our-first-month</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/our-first-month"/>
      <title>♨ A Look Back on Our First Month</title>
      <published>2013-10-23T12:48:50-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-23T12:48:50-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A month ago today, I launched &lt;em&gt;The Bold Report&lt;/em&gt;. I’m so glad I did it, and we’ve had some pretty great growth in our first month!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First of all, if you’re reading this, I want to say thank you. This site is something I’ve been wanting to do for a long time. I love writing about my interests, and I love the fact that there are people like you, who have similar passions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;now-for-some-stats&quot;&gt;Now for Some Stats&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The site has been viewed 5,013 times, and people stay an average of two minutes. The site had 3,006 visitors, 1,313 of which were returning. 1,902 visitors are from the United States, the United Kingdom came in second place with 399.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not surprisingly, the two most common mobile devices the site is viewed on, are iOS devices. Coming in first place: iPhone with sixty-two percent. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chrome was the popular browser, responsible for fifty-six percent of traffic. Nine people visited from Internet Explorer.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; Most visitors are using a Mac, but twelve percent is on Windows.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:2&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:2&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The number one source of referrals was Twitter with 1,560, my personal site in third place, and Sidebar.io coming in fourth. The main RSS feed currently has twelve subscribers, and the Twitter account has sixty-six followers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;top-five-posts&quot;&gt;Top Five Posts&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the first month, these were the top posts:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/freelancing-and-saying-no/&quot;&gt;Freelancing and Saying “No”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/document-everything/&quot;&gt;Document Everything&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/review-1password-4-for-mac/&quot;&gt;Review: 1Password 4 for Mac&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/welcome/&quot;&gt;Dear Reader,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/using-portly-for-local-development/&quot;&gt;Using Portly for Local Development&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;giveaway&quot;&gt;Giveaway&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a token of my appreciation, I wanted to give away two &lt;a href=&quot;https://tonx.org/&quot;&gt;“The Standard” Tonx Coffee Subscriptions&lt;/a&gt;. I’ll personally pay for your first month, which includes two shipments of great-tasting coffee. My pal Jory Raphael is also kindly giving away two of his amazing &lt;a href=&quot;http://symbolicons.com/&quot;&gt;Symbolicons icon bundles&lt;/a&gt;! The winners will be choosen at random on Friday at 1pm Central. Here’s what you have to do to win:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Follow &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/theboldreport&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Bold Report&lt;/em&gt; on Twitter&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mention @theboldreport, and tell me what you like about the site, and what I could possibly do better.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In closing, a huge thank you to everyone who has followed, subscribed, and read. I sincerely appreciate all of your support, and I hope you continue to find the content here, of interest to you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;—Tim&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Even that, was a bigger number that I would’ve thought. Thanks IE folks! Hope you can see everything well! &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:2&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Again, a bigger number than I thought. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:2&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/os-x-mavericks-review</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/os-x-mavericks-review"/>
      <title>OS X Mavericks Review</title>
      <published>2013-10-22T17:34:20-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-22T17:34:20-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Stephen Hackett on &lt;em&gt;512 Pixels&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The bones haven’t changed all that much over the last 13 years, but every time Apple updates OS X, it continues to improve and refine features and the underlying technologies that make them possible.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;…I firmly believe that OS X is the best consumer desktop operating system on the planet. It has undergone some major changes over the years, but it’s the same OS under the hood. OS X is still as stable, powerful and resilient to viruses and other malware as it has always been.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stephen is one of my favorite writers, and he’s published an amazing, in-depth review of the latest OS X. &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/the-east-wing-74</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/the-east-wing-74"/>
      <title>The East Wing: Liz Elcoate</title>
      <published>2013-10-22T17:14:51-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-22T17:14:51-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This week: I talk with Liz Elcoate about her start in the design industry, her podcast, and how she’d never go back to a full-time job.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bandwidth sponsored by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.campaignmonitor.com/&quot;&gt;Campaign Monitor&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/apple-event-day</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/apple-event-day"/>
      <title>♨ Apple Event Day</title>
      <published>2013-10-22T10:40:36-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-22T10:40:36-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Apple Event Days are always exciting for me, and this one will be no different.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ll be able to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.apple.com/apple-events/october-2013/&quot;&gt;watch the event live&lt;/a&gt; on your iOS device, Mac, or Apple TV. &lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; During the event, I’ll be in the &lt;em&gt;#ssktn&lt;/em&gt; iRC chatroom, as a kind of virtual-viewing party. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the event, Chris Enns, Kyle Roderick, and myself will be talking about the event and new gadgets on the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ssktn.com/live/&quot;&gt;SSKTN live stream&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happy Apple Event Day!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;I’m so glad they’ve started to stream most of these events on the Apple TV. It seems that the only one they’re not streaming live these days is WWDC, which is totally understandable. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/sponsor-tonx-coffee</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/sponsor-tonx-coffee"/>
      <title>Sponsor: Tonx Coffee</title>
      <published>2013-10-22T09:56:29-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-22T09:56:29-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/cms/images/ad_2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Tonx Coffee Ad&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/s/tr&quot;&gt;Tonx&lt;/a&gt; is a small team of coffee experts who believe it’s easy to make a better cup in your kitchen than you’ll get at the best cafes - and for a fraction of the cost. By sourcing the finest coffees in the world and roasting them 24-hours before shipping, you’ll have the freshest coffee delivered straight to your door. &lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/s/tr&quot;&gt;And for a limited time, get a free trial to taste for yourself.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, Tonx is pleased to introduce &lt;a href=&quot;https://tonx.org/newsletter_sign_up/new/?utm_source=syndicate&amp;amp;utm_medium=sponsorship&amp;amp;utm_campaign=syndicate&quot;&gt;The Frequency&lt;/a&gt;, an email newsletter packed with coffee secrets, brew tips, and special limited offers, exclusively for Tonx members.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I have a Tonx Coffee subscription. It’s amazing. Thank you to Tonx Coffee for sponsoring the RSS feed this week. &lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/&quot;&gt;Sponsorship by The Syndicate.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/john-gruber-on-imessage-encryption</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/john-gruber-on-imessage-encryption"/>
      <title>John Gruber on iMessage Encryption</title>
      <published>2013-10-21T13:02:22-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-21T13:02:22-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;What Quarkslab’s research proves […] is that Apple’s iMessage back-end &lt;em&gt;could&lt;/em&gt; be designed to allow for Apple to intercept and read message content, and there is no way we, as iMessage users, would be able to detect it.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;What Apple has said, and reiterated today, is that iMessage’s back-end is not in fact designed in that way — that there is no mechanism in the system for Apple employees to surreptitiously change the encryption key to allow for messages to be decrypted during transit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t have much to add to this one, I just found the article to be interesting. I agree with Gruber that it would be a &lt;em&gt;huge&lt;/em&gt; mistake for Apple to lie about something as sensitive as this. &lt;strong&gt;However&lt;/strong&gt;, at the end of the day, which side does it make more sense for companies to side with? Users? That’s naive.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/netflix-likely-to-have-overtaken-hbo-in-paid-us-subscribers</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/netflix-likely-to-have-overtaken-hbo-in-paid-us-subscribers"/>
      <title>Netflix Likely to Have Overtaken HBO in Paid US Subscribers</title>
      <published>2013-10-21T12:19:57-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-21T12:19:57-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Amar Toor reporting for &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;According to analysis from Needham &amp;amp; Co., it’s likely that Netflix’s paid US subscriber base reached 30 million by the end of September. That may be enough to overtake HBO, which has an estimated 28.7 million subscribers in the US…&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;In its fiscal &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.theverge.com/2013/7/22/4545446/netflix-q2-2013-earnings&quot;&gt;Q2 earnings report&lt;/a&gt; this year, Netflix said it had more than 29 million US subscribers and expected to add between 230,000 and 880,000 in Q3.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Netflix is one of those companies that I love to root for. However, as &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.theverge.com/2013/10/21/4861624/netflix-has-likely-overtaken-hbo-in-paid-us-subscribers-analysts-say#192210067&quot;&gt;someone in the comments for this article pointed out&lt;/a&gt;, the fact that Netflix has more subscribers than HBO, doesn’t mean they’re making more money. Still, these numbers might just give HBO the scare they need, to consider an online subscription that isn’t tied to any cable company. With Time Warner Cable being the parent company of HBO, I see this as a small probability, but there’s no way they don’t see the potential business they’re missing out on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing is for sure, the competition between these two channels will be interesting to watch. &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/freelancing-and-saying-no</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/freelancing-and-saying-no"/>
      <title>♨ Freelancing and Saying “No”</title>
      <published>2013-10-18T12:06:47-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-18T12:06:47-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;No. That word has been given lots of importance in our industry and rightly so. &lt;a href=&quot;http://vimeo.com/53155584&quot;&gt;Jason Santa Maria spoke about it&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/the-year-of-the-looking-glass/23ad80bdfbc&quot;&gt;Julie Zhuo wrote about it&lt;/a&gt;, and I’m sure you’ve read your fair share of articles on the topic. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a powerful word, and I’m glad that we’re a community that looks out for each other and is willing to share with newcomers how to avoid bad projects. There are some relationships that will rob you of your joy, and in the end cost you more money than you’re being paid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, I think it’s been given a misleading reputation. Lots of people confuse saying no,with turning down projects they don’t deem as “fun”. In some articles, I’ve seen it turn into advice that only strokes the growing ego that many designers have. We turn something great, into snobbery and haughtiness. Consequently, people are given the wrong impression of what saying no actually means.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;tim-my-business-is-already-struggling-and-you-expect-me-to-say-no-to-a-project&quot;&gt;“Tim, my business is already struggling and you expect me to say no to a project?”&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course not. I always take projects that help keep the lights on. Everyone does. If they say they don’t, they’re lying. Not every single project will meet all of your requirements &lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;, and even the ones that do will have difficulties and moments of frustration. That’s just a fact of life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saying no means to turn down projects that will kill you or your business. You know exactly what I’m talking about. The client that you’re having a preliminary meeting with, and your gut tells you that you shouldn’t work with the person. The reason could be one of many. They don’t know what they want, they want to pay you considerably less, they’re condescending, whatever. That’s when you say no.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s important to note that someone with a low budget isn’t always a red flag. Learn to trust your gut. You’ll know when it’s a good idea to work for less money, and when it’s just someone that’s trying to take advantage. If you still don’t know, ask a friend. Don’t have someone to ask? Email me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;but-i-need-the-money&quot;&gt;“But I need the money!”&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You think you’re poor now? Just wait till you’re working an insane amount of hours on an insane budget. What happens when you finally get sick of it? Do you fire the client? Will you have to issue a refund? How do you pay for that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trust me, something else will come up. I’ve been hours away from having no money in the bank with no prospects of money, and something has always come up.In all honesty, it’s better to pick up a shift at Starbucks, than work in a toxic relationship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;im-freelancing-so-i-can-have-fun&quot;&gt;“I’m freelancing so I can have fun.”&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Freelancing is work. There are a lot of hardships. Lots of anxiety. Lots of stress. Maybe even playing “credit card shuffle”. &lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:2&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:2&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; Not every day is going to be fun, and that’s something you have to come to terms with. However, it’s also very rewarding. I wake up when I want, I work when I want, I get to choose my clients,&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:3&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:3&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; I can choose to collaborate with other designers, developers, etc., and I can work from wherever there is internet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ll land three projects one month, and have no work the next.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:4&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:4&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; Money management becomes crucial when you freelance. But, don’t worry. If I can do it—and I’m literally the best blower of money—you can definitely do it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;wrapping-up&quot;&gt;Wrapping Up&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All projects aren’t going to be fun, and they won’t all be big brands or names. Learn to appreciate projects that allow you to work with people who care, make an impact on peoples lives, and teach you new things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not all clients are bad. Most are well-meaning people who are trying to do their best by their business or company. Saying no, should never satisfy an emotional need to rebel. Instead, it should be educated by the goals of your business, and that of the client. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In closing, remember that the objective of saying no, will give you the opportunity to say yes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;further-reading&quot;&gt;Further Reading&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.franklincovey.com/blog/effectively.html&quot;&gt;Saying “No” Effectively&lt;/a&gt; — Via &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.markrondina.com/&quot;&gt;Mark Rondina&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A very sincere thank you to &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hamstu&quot;&gt;Hamish Macpherson&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/mattriopelle&quot;&gt;Matt Riopelle&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/mrondina&quot;&gt;Mark Rondina&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/sara_ann_marie&quot;&gt;Sara Wachter-Boettcher&lt;/a&gt;, for their help in editing this article.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;You’re the one that decides what those requirements are. For me, I have an internal checklist. Is the project fun? Do I believe in the message of the project and the company trying to communicate it? Does the client show respect for me, my work, and my time? Who else will I be working with? What will I learn? Will I be able to display the work in my portfolio? Do I have time? Is the budget reasonable? &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:2&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;This is when you pay one card with another card. Or you’re paying bills with a credit card. It’s scary stuff. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:2&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:3&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;This is true whether you have clients are not. You’re &lt;strong&gt;never&lt;/strong&gt; forced to work on something you don’t want to. Even if the work is horrible, it was &lt;em&gt;my choice&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:3&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;July was killer. September was dry. Feast or famine. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:4&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/shawn-blanc-on-successful-creative-business</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/shawn-blanc-on-successful-creative-business"/>
      <title>Shawn Blanc on Successful Creative Business</title>
      <published>2013-10-18T11:21:37-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-18T11:21:37-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;A huge part of making art online and growing an audience is centered around how often you show up, how good you are at what you do, and how narrow your focus is and how “&lt;a href=&quot;http://daringfireball.net/2009/03/obsession_times_voice&quot;&gt;weirdly obsessed&lt;/a&gt;” you are about it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shawn knows what he’s talking about.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/fitbit-tracker-becoming-more-like-a-smartwatch</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/fitbit-tracker-becoming-more-like-a-smartwatch"/>
      <title>Fitbit Tracker Becoming More Like a Smartwatch</title>
      <published>2013-10-18T11:11:02-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-18T11:11:02-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Josh Ong reporting for &lt;em&gt;The Next Web&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Fitbit CEO James Park said the company is “inching closer and closer to being a smartwatch.”&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;…&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Park also emphasized that Fitbit is vertically focused on the health and fitness space, so it’s not worried about smartwatches that are rumored to be coming from Apple and Google.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s very smart of Fitbit, because they have no chance in competing with Google or Apple, if these rumors are true. For some, a “smartwatch”&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; will be overkill for tracking their health and fitness. However, if their products serve the niche market well, they have the opportunity to continue being very successful in the space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Is that really the term we’ve settled on? &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/easter-eggs-in-star-wars-and-indiana-jones</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/easter-eggs-in-star-wars-and-indiana-jones"/>
      <title>Easter Eggs in Star Wars and Indiana Jones</title>
      <published>2013-10-18T10:58:22-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-18T10:58:22-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Stuff like this is just so cool. I need to find ways to hide things on the sites I design. &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/laura-kalbag-on-being-open</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/laura-kalbag-on-being-open"/>
      <title>Laura Kalbag on Being Open</title>
      <published>2013-10-17T11:49:07-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-17T11:49:07-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The most conscious decision I made about openness was to not put up a front and not always try to make myself look better. We all do things that make us look stupid from time to time (I do it a lot!). But what’s really wrong with looking stupid? Why would I want to pretend to be superhuman? That would just set unrealistic expectations for my clients and everybody else around me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Laura is one of my favorite people. She’s real, she’s humble, and crazy talented. That combination of qualities have made her the success she is. In her column today, on &lt;em&gt;A List Apart&lt;/em&gt;, she does a great job explaining why being open and transparent is a very good thing.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/square-cash-makes-sending-money-easy</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/square-cash-makes-sending-money-easy"/>
      <title>Square Cash Makes Sending Money Easy</title>
      <published>2013-10-16T13:24:20-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-16T13:24:20-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;To use Square Cash, all you do is compose an email to a friend, type the amount you way to pay in the subject title, and cc cash@square.com. If it’s your first time using the service, you’re directed to Square’s website where you type in your debit card number — and you’re done. There are no accounts to create, apps to download, friends to add, surcharges to pay, or bank account numbers to look up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is amazing. My only question is: why has this taken so long? It seems that this could’ve existed years ago. Good on Square for continuing to do great things.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/tim-likes-to-teach-using-the-jekyll-assets-plugin</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/tim-likes-to-teach-using-the-jekyll-assets-plugin"/>
      <title>Tim Likes to Teach: Using the Jekyll Assets Plugin</title>
      <published>2013-10-15T13:02:56-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-15T13:02:56-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I made a quick video tutorial on how to use the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/ixti/jekyll-assets&quot;&gt;Jekyll Assets plugin&lt;/a&gt;. It’s super helpful, and allows you to use Sass, Compass, Coffeescript, and other cool stuff.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/sponsor-squarespace</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/sponsor-squarespace"/>
      <title>Sponsor: Squarespace</title>
      <published>2013-10-15T12:37:46-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-15T12:37:46-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/cms/images/600px.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Squarespace ad image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What do you want people to see when they find you online?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether you’re growing a business, starting a blog, or are ready to sell online, you need to make a great impression. Squarespace is the best way to create a modern and professional website, with all the features you need integrated into one platform. Every Squarespace website is mobile-ready, includes e-commerce, and is backed up by award-winning 24/7 customer service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/s/td&quot;&gt;Try Squarespace today at squarespace.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Thank you to &lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/s/td&quot;&gt;Squarespace&lt;/a&gt; for sponsoring the RSS feed this week. &lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/&quot;&gt;Sponsorship by The Syndicate.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/chris-coyier-on-media-temple-acquisition</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/chris-coyier-on-media-temple-acquisition"/>
      <title>Chris Coyier on Media Temple Acquisition</title>
      <published>2013-10-15T12:19:33-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-15T12:19:33-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;If anyone thinks MediaTemple is just going to be exactly the same or better forever, I’ll bet you a nickel you’re wrong. I bet they are losing employees as we speak who aren’t happy about this. Things will change. I am going to give them the benefit of the doubt though. I’m going to keep on liking both services until there is a real reason to not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Agreed.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/sonos-announces-the-play-1</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/sonos-announces-the-play-1"/>
      <title>Sonos Announces the Play:1</title>
      <published>2013-10-14T11:57:23-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-14T11:57:23-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dan Seifert from &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Compared to the similarly priced Jambox, the Play:1 is considerably louder, crisper, and more present. The more expensive Big Jambox offers a wider range and better separation than a single Play:1 thanks to its larger speakers and configuration. But the Play:1 is still louder and sounds bigger, if slightly more muddled because of the lack of speaker separation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Really excited about this news. Since receiving my new iPhone, I now need to replace by bathroom speaker because it uses the old 30-pin connector. I started thinking that it would be better to buy things that are connector-independent, this way, it’ll last me longer. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’d looked at several speakers, and had heard very good things of all the Sonos speakers and &lt;a href=&quot;https://jawbone.com/speakers/bigjambox&quot;&gt;Big Jambox&lt;/a&gt;, but was worried to go Sonos because of the high price point. This new speaker is more wallet friendly, and could be the start of a great relationship with the Sonos ecosystem. I’ll write some thoughts on the speaker once I receive and use it for a while.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/minor-upgrade-to-instagram-no-longer-lets-users-disable-video-autoplay</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/minor-upgrade-to-instagram-no-longer-lets-users-disable-video-autoplay"/>
      <title>‘Minor’ Upgrade to Instagram No Longer Lets Users Disable Video Autoplay</title>
      <published>2013-10-11T13:05:20-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-11T13:05:20-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Jon Russell reporting for &lt;em&gt;The Next Web&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Instagram announced earlier this month that it will begin serving in-feed advertising before the end of the year, and the Facebook-owned photo and video app has made a subtle, but important, change after it removed the option to switch off autoplay for videos on iOS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know what to say. Do I like that Instagram is about to be Facebook-ized? No. But, the fact of the matter is, that they weren’t profitable, and now they have to be. Is there a better way? Maybe. But what is it? I have no idea. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s what I do know: I hate quotes like this, where Instagram says they want “these ads to be enjoyable and creative in much the same way you see engaging, high-quality ads when you flip through your favorite magazine.” Guess what? Everyone, &lt;em&gt;everyone&lt;/em&gt;, flips right past them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, what are they supposed to do? If they offered some type of subscription, it wouldn’t make enough to sustain the business. If they &lt;em&gt;only&lt;/em&gt; allowed paying customers, they’d loose their core user base of adolescents and young adults. They could offer filters as an in-app purchase, &lt;a href=&quot;http://favd.net/&quot;&gt;like Favd does&lt;/a&gt;, but I have no idea whether that would make enough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, as much as it bothers me that they’ve gone the advertising route, I can’t help but empathize. I myself put ads on this site, and on my podcast. It’s easy, it often pays the bills, and sometimes more. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;further-reading&quot;&gt;Further Reading&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://powazek.com/posts/3024&quot;&gt;What If Social Networks Just Aren’t Profitable?&lt;/a&gt; — A really great read, on the cycle that social networks go through.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/facebook-removes-hide-from-search-privacy-setting</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/facebook-removes-hide-from-search-privacy-setting"/>
      <title>Facebook Removes ‘Hide from Search’ Privacy Setting</title>
      <published>2013-10-11T12:27:27-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-11T12:27:27-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The &lt;em&gt;Associated Press&lt;/em&gt; reports:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Facebook Inc. said Thursday that it is removing a setting that controls whether users could be found when people type their name into the website’s search bar.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Facebook says only a single-digit percentage of the nearly 1.2 billion people on its network were using the setting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is Facebook without their continued unethical behavior involving privacy. And then to say “only a single-digit percentage of the nearly 1.2 billion people on its network” are using it? As &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/tubes/status/388505400527450113&quot;&gt;Sean Tubridy pointed out so well&lt;/a&gt;, that’s “between 10 million and 90 million people.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What Facebook seems to forget, is that what’s bad for users, is bad for business. A lesson they might learn the hard way.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/my-article-on-open-source-design</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/my-article-on-open-source-design"/>
      <title>Open Source Design: Using GitHub for Design Collaboration</title>
      <published>2013-10-10T16:04:03-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-10T16:04:03-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I wrote a small article on how GitHub has really helped us on the Open Source Design project. With the use of GitHub issues, we’ve been able to talk and collaborate as a group. &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/hp-and-microsoft-become-competitors</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/hp-and-microsoft-become-competitors"/>
      <title>HP and Microsoft Become ‘Competitors’</title>
      <published>2013-10-10T11:46:04-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-10T11:46:04-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Hewlett Packard and Microsoft are changing “from partners to outright competitors,” says HP CEO Meg Whitman…&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Microsoft has made a number of recent decisions contrary to HP’s own interests, including bailing out competitor Dell in an attempt to push Windows 8 to the business sector. Also central to her reclassification is Microsoft’s commitment to Surface, despite previous claims from HP that Surface wasn’t a threat to its own Windows 8 tablet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We all could see this coming. As Microsoft moves to create their own hardware, the companies that have built business around that not being the case, are now in trouble. HP didn’t help itself either, by making &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.theverge.com/2011/11/2/2533759/slate-2-hp-tries-tablets-again-with-windows-swype-and-a-stylus-for-699&quot;&gt;horrible tablets&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The article goes on to say:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Craig Mundie — senior advisor to Microsoft’s CEO — said although Microsoft had planned to leave device design to its partners, “it became hard to guarantee a uniform quality of experience that the end user had.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now you’re gettin’ it, Microsoft.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/bill-nye-youtube-series-with-nasa</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/bill-nye-youtube-series-with-nasa"/>
      <title>Bill Nye Back with a YouTube Series on NASA’s Mission to Jupiter</title>
      <published>2013-10-10T11:16:49-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-10T11:16:49-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Bill Nye has collaborated with NASA to launch a new eight-part web series on the agency’s latest mission to Jupiter. The science enthusiast and TV host, who for years entertained kids with the PBS show Bill Nye the Science Guy, first teased a return to presenting back in July…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m so excited to see Bill Nye hosting a science show again. When I was in middle school, we often watched his show in science class. I’ve always loved his ability to make science fun and interesting. He clearly has a passion for it, and it shines through.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/google-fiber-isn-t-for-small-businesses-yet</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/google-fiber-isn-t-for-small-businesses-yet"/>
      <title>Google Fiber Won’t Be Available for Small Businesses… Yet</title>
      <published>2013-10-10T10:55:31-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-10T10:55:31-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Google today decided to clarify its stance for small businesses using Google Fiber. In short, small businesses aren’t allowed to take advantage of the ISP, at least not yet.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;…&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Currently, Google is only bringing Fiber to residential locations (units and homes where people live) as well as the public and nonprofit sites selected by each Fiber city. This means that there is currently a loophole: home-based businesses can use Google Fiber.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why they would make such a seemingly arbitrary rule, doesn’t make sense, and I’m sure will disappoint a lot of local businesses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The question is: Will they enforce the policy?&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/apple-ipad-event-on-october-22</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/apple-ipad-event-on-october-22"/>
      <title>Apple iPad Event on October 22</title>
      <published>2013-10-08T19:20:18-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-08T19:20:18-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;John Paczkowski reporting for &lt;em&gt;AllThingsD&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;People familiar with Apple’s plans tell &lt;em&gt;AllThingsD&lt;/em&gt; that the company will hold its next invitation-only event on Tuesday, October 22. The focal point of the gathering will be the latest updates to the company’s iPad line, but the new Mac Pro and OS X Mavericks will likely get some stage time as well, I’m told.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love Apple Event days. I never get anything else done.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/brad-frost-on-development-being-design</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/brad-frost-on-development-being-design"/>
      <title>Brad Frost on Development Being Design</title>
      <published>2013-10-08T19:00:43-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-08T19:00:43-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;As the Web landscape grows increasingly complex, it’s increasingly important to demonstrate the myriad ways a Web experience can be interacted with. It’s impossible for designers working in static environments to realistically articulate every device, user setting, and variable that effects how a design is realized. Because of this, front-end developers need to work closely with other designers to ensure what’s being created is realistic and feasible. This requires rolling front-end development into the design workflow, rethinking our deliverables, and working together in order to create experiences that look and function beautifully on a whole host of screen sizes, form factors, and environments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well said. Brad excellently explains why I think the web is so exciting right now. Sure, there will always be people who don’t get it. But, the line between design and front-end development is being blurred, and I love that.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/the-east-wing-72</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/the-east-wing-72"/>
      <title>The East Wing: Garth Braithwaite</title>
      <published>2013-10-08T16:53:12-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-08T16:53:12-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This week: I talk with Garth Braithwaite about how he got started, projects he’s worked on at Adobe, Open Source Design, and design education.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bandwidth is kindly provided by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.campaignmonitor.com/&quot;&gt;Campaign Monitor&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/sponsor-mailchimp</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/sponsor-mailchimp"/>
      <title>Sponsor: MailChimp</title>
      <published>2013-10-08T10:59:27-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-08T10:59:27-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/cms/images/MC_GoesWithYou_600wide.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;MailChimp Sponsor&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/s/sz&quot;&gt;new generation of MailChimp&lt;/a&gt; adapts to your workflow, regardless of the device you’re using and size of your team. A cohesive experience across desktop and mobile devices means you can create, send, and track email campaigns in any context.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/s/sz&quot;&gt;Check out the MailChimp today.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Thanks to &lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/s/sz&quot;&gt;MailChimp&lt;/a&gt; for supporting The Bold Report this week. &lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/&quot;&gt;Sponsorship by The Syndicate.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/eric-schmidt-tells-jokes</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/eric-schmidt-tells-jokes"/>
      <title>Eric Schmidt Tells Jokes</title>
      <published>2013-10-08T10:56:17-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-08T10:56:17-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Eric Schmidt is apparently quite the jokester. When told that some don’t find Android secure, Schmidt responded, “Not secure? It’s more secure than the iPhone.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good one, dude.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/starting-with-sass</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/starting-with-sass"/>
      <title>Starting with Sass</title>
      <published>2013-10-07T13:50:16-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-07T13:50:16-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Chris Bowler:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I’ve looked at several tutorials over the years, but many were written with a certain assumption for the level of knowledge on the other end. Many can be a struggle for the beginner because you may not even have the tools to be able to use Sass. Because of this, I wanted to write a handful of tips on what helped me get on board.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’ve been on the fence about trying Sass, this is a really good place to start. I promise you, &lt;em&gt;I promise you&lt;/em&gt;, you’ll never go back to normal CSS.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/yale-professor-calls-bing-it-on-claims-bogus</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/yale-professor-calls-bing-it-on-claims-bogus"/>
      <title>Yale Professor Calls ‘Bing It On’ Claims Bogus</title>
      <published>2013-10-04T11:42:35-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-04T11:42:35-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This week, a Yale law professor took aim at Microsoft’s “&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bingiton.com/&quot;&gt;Bing It On&lt;/a&gt;” campaign…&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;And &lt;a href=&quot;http://islandia.law.yale.edu/ayres/BingItOn_Draft%209.pdf&quot;&gt;Ayres’ results differed sharply&lt;/a&gt; from Microsoft’s: “We found that, to the contrary of Microsoft’s claim, 53 percent of subjects preferred Google and 41 percent Bing (6 percent of results were “ties”). This is not even close to the advertised claim that people prefer Bing ‘nearly two-to-one.’”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is fascinating. Microsoft responded to this professor, but in my opinion, gave a statement that were just words and didn’t explain why this test was so different from the one Microsoft conducted. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is what happens when you make commercials that call out other brands. Making fun of other people is the low thing to do, and quite honestly, the easy thing to do. Tell us how Bing is &lt;em&gt;actually&lt;/em&gt; better Microsoft, or shut up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;related-watching&quot;&gt;Related Watching&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Xubz8EuHosQ&quot;&gt;TV Commercial - Microsoft Surface Tablet: Less Talking. More Doing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/review-1password-4-for-mac</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/review-1password-4-for-mac"/>
      <title>♨ Review: 1Password 4 for Mac</title>
      <published>2013-10-03T00:00:00-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-03T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://agilebits.com/onepassword&quot;&gt;1Password&lt;/a&gt; is one of my favorite apps. The amount of time it has saved me is unmeasurable, and it’s made my password strategy secure and delightful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those of you who don’t know about 1Password, it’s a great utility app to store and generate passwords. For years, I was the person who had &lt;em&gt;the same password for everything&lt;/em&gt;. With 1Password, I don’t do that anymore, I’m able to search through weak passwords and generate stronger ones, making it less likely to get hacked. Even if that does happen, none of my passwords are the same, so I only need to reset the one that’s been compromised.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;first-impressions&quot;&gt;First Impressions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The new interface is beautiful, and obviously influenced by the iOS version.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The Chrome extension got a facelift, and generated passwords are not only filled in forms, they’re also copied to your clipboard.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;1Password Mini brings most of the power of the main app to the menubar. This is great for entering passwords into apps that aren’t the browser. I disliked having to open the main app to do this in previous versions.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;new-features-in-1password-4-for-mac&quot;&gt;New Features in 1Password 4 for Mac&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;design&quot;&gt;Design&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first thing you’ll notice when you open the new 1Password is the beautiful interface. If you’ve already purchased &lt;a href=&quot;https://agilebits.com/onepassword/ios&quot;&gt;the latest iOS app&lt;/a&gt;, you’ll notice that the new design is very similar, which delights me greatly. This redesign is years overdue, and the AgileBits team has delivered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;extendout&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://theboldreport.net/uploads/2013/10/1p4-mac-main.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;1Password 4 for Mac Main View&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love that this redesign in a lot of ways is a re-align. The interface remains in the three column layout, yet with an easy-on-the-eyes, light background. The type has greatly improved, and the middle column no longer has the “shelf” look. The new layout, allows you to see more logins in the window without having to scroll and sports better looking icons. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thankfully, the last column has been redone too. It used to be confusing to look at, and honestly, I didn’t know what was going on. It’s now a lot more simplified and only displays necessary information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That being said, my favorite part of the main view, is the new “Security Audit” that appears in the far left column. It gives you easy access to weak passwords, duplicate passwords, and passwords that are old and might need to be changed. To be clear, this type of filtering has always been present in 1Password, but the fact that it’s now front and center, is very valuable to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;multiple-vaults&quot;&gt;Multiple Vaults&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One feature that I can see becoming very popular is the new feature of multiple vaults. I haven’t actually been using this feature, but it’s one of those things that I think could help me organize the different sets of passwords. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is especially true when I worked for a company. Having a separate vault exclusively for company logins, would’ve been a great way to get organized. This makes managing items easier, and makes cleaning out items you no longer need, a breeze.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;alignright&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://theboldreport.net/uploads/2013/10/1p4-mac-create-new-vault.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;With 1Password 4 you can now create new vaults. Organizing your passwords based on their use is simple.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;password-mini&quot;&gt;1Password Mini&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love that they made a menubar app. I’m definitely one of those people that has &lt;em&gt;way too many&lt;/em&gt; of them.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:2&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:2&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; Interestingly, the menubar app is what comes up now when you press &lt;code&gt;⌘CMD + \&lt;/code&gt;. It seems that the 1Password browser extension is now only needed to run the code necessary for the autofill. You’ll never actually need to press the button anymore, which is nice, because it’s one less button in the extensions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;alignleft&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://theboldreport.net/uploads/2013/10/1p4-mac-1p-mini-item-details.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;1Password Mini makes using 1Password easier and faster than ever.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s too early for me to say, but I think 1Password Mini could completely replace the main app for me. So far, I haven’t needed to open the main app for day-to-day responsibilities. To be honest, I only looked at the main app the day I downloaded it, and today when writing this review.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;other-features-you-should-know-about&quot;&gt;Other Features You Should Know About&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shared Items&lt;/strong&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;
Till now, I haven’t needed to ever share login items, but I can definitely see the practicality of this. You can share items with email or iMessage, and if the person makes changes, the item automatically updates when shared back.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;256-bit Authenticated Encryption&lt;/strong&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;
I have no idea what this means, except that 1Password is constantly being updated to be more and more secure. From what I’m told, this prevents attacks that don’t even exist yet.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wifi Sync&lt;/strong&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;
This feature is back from previous versions. Personally, I use Dropbox to sync my Vault between my Mac, iPad and iPhone, but whatever floats your boat. They have iCloud sync too.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;final-thoughts&quot;&gt;Final Thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The AgileBits team have definitely outdone themselves. Not only is this update to 1Password beautiful, the new features and menubar app, make the upgrade very worth it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’ve never used 1Password, this is a perfect time to purchase. In this day and age, it’s crucial to have secure passwords. This is an app you’ll later wonder how you did without.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It seems you can’t currently purchase the new 1Password from &lt;a href=&quot;https://agilebits.com/store&quot;&gt;the AgileBits store&lt;/a&gt;, but that is where it’ll be very soon.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:3&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:3&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; You can also purchase from &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/1password/id443987910?mt=12&quot;&gt;the Mac App Store&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update:&lt;/strong&gt; You can now purchase and/or upgrade on &lt;a href=&quot;https://agilebits.com/store&quot;&gt;the AgileBits store&lt;/a&gt;. Seems my speculation was wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;further-reading&quot;&gt;Further Reading&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.agilebits.com/2013/08/31/how-long-should-my-passwords-be/&quot;&gt;How long should my passwords be?&lt;/a&gt; - If you’re interested in making generated passwords from 1Password very secure, I definitely recommend this article by the AgileBits team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;This might seem like a small thing, but it’s one of my favorite additions to 1Password. I used to copy the password then press the fill button, and now those two actions are done with one press. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:2&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;By the way, you can use &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.macbartender.com/&quot;&gt;Bartender&lt;/a&gt; to clean that menubar up.  &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:2&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:3&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;This is only speculation, but I wonder if they’re required to give the App Store preference for a set amount of time. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:3&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/babblenut-9</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/babblenut-9"/>
      <title>Babblenut: I’m Not Scared of the Feels</title>
      <published>2013-10-02T18:58:00-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-02T18:58:00-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This week: Paul and I talk about Breaking Bad, being grateful, learning to be an advocate, and much more.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/contentment-and-feeling-grateful</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/contentment-and-feeling-grateful"/>
      <title>♨ Contentment and Being Grateful</title>
      <published>2013-10-02T14:56:56-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-02T14:56:56-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We all have our moments when we feel down. In my case, the past two years have been full of personal mistakes and bad decisions. Failure is difficult to accept. Yet, these things considered, it’s not the end; the book has not yet been finished, even when at times, it certainly feels like it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although, anyone would’ve considered me an optimist a year ago, it’s not so easy in practice. Yet, something I’ve forced myself to do, is always remember I have reasons to be grateful. I think it’s a good idea to do this whether you’re going through a tough time or not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I live in a very privileged part of the world, and I often get wrapped up in my own problems, client frustrations, and whining about stupidities, that I forget how much worse it could really be. My alarm in the morning could be a bomb, instead of my cute cat, and I could be in a perpetual state of worry. There are people going through much worse than I’ve &lt;em&gt;ever&lt;/em&gt; gone through, and that empathy allows me to step back and look at my life objectively.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My life isn’t perfect. I don’t make nearly as much money as I’d like, I’ve been a disappointment to people who care about me, I have debt that is far away from being paid off, I’m overweight, and I’ve hurt a girl I was in love with, twice… twice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, I have parents, family and friends that love me, and add meaning to my life. I’m healthy. I haven’t gone hungry. I work in an amazing industry, where I can say I love my job. And I live in a beautiful place that enjoys the four amazing seasons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happiness and contentment are a choice, and I &lt;em&gt;choose&lt;/em&gt; to be happy, I &lt;em&gt;choose&lt;/em&gt; to be grateful for what I have, I &lt;em&gt;choose&lt;/em&gt; to make lemonade out of lemons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Should I pour you a glass?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This post was originally written for &lt;a href=&quot;http://the-pastry-box-project.net/&quot;&gt;The Pastry Box&lt;/a&gt;. They have so many people wanting to contribute, that they weren’t able to accept my submission.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/using-portly-for-local-development</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/using-portly-for-local-development"/>
      <title>♨ Using Portly for Local Development</title>
      <published>2013-10-02T09:52:41-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-02T09:52:41-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;My friend, &lt;a href=&quot;http://adamstacoviak.com/&quot;&gt;Adam Stacoviak&lt;/a&gt;, pointed me to a tool called &lt;a href=&quot;https://getportly.com/&quot;&gt;Portly&lt;/a&gt;. Portly allows you to display your local web server, publicly. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you look at the Portly site, you can tell that the applications of this menubar app, are many. I’ve been using it to do local device testing without the need for a staging server. This a very basic usage of this powerful app, but it’s been a huge timesaver for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I &lt;em&gt;always&lt;/em&gt; develop sites locally.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; One problem I constantly ran into, is that I wasn’t able to easily test sites on my different devices. Sure, you can use a bookmarklet, resize your browser, or sign up for something like BrowserStack, but I like to test from the comfort of my couch.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:2&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:2&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/2013/10/portly-screenshot.png&quot; alt=&quot;Portly Preferences&quot; title=&quot;Portly Preferences&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is where Portly comes in. I simply add a tunnel in the app, point it to my local connection string,&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:3&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:3&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; turn on the tunnel,  and go to the subdomain on my iPad or iPhone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, I know there are other ways to do this, but I just wasn’t nerdy enough to implement them. Portly is easy, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://getportly.com/plans&quot;&gt;starting at $2.99/month&lt;/a&gt;, a very good deal. You should definitely check it out. If you need help or have questions, ping me on &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/ttimsmith&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#116;&amp;#105;&amp;#109;&amp;#064;&amp;#116;&amp;#104;&amp;#101;&amp;#098;&amp;#111;&amp;#108;&amp;#100;&amp;#114;&amp;#101;&amp;#112;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#116;&amp;#046;&amp;#110;&amp;#101;&amp;#116;&quot;&gt;email me&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;If you’re working on a live server, stop that. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:2&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;I’ve found that QA is much more enjoyable—and effective—when I’m relaxed and comfortable. I turn on the TV for background noise, sit back on the couch, and browse every single page of the site. I find things I need to fix and assign myself GitHub issues. This ritual is often accompanied by a cup of coffee as well. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:2&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:3&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;For example, &lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000&quot;&gt;http://localhost:4000&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:3&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/the-east-wing-71</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/the-east-wing-71"/>
      <title>The East Wing: Scott Johnson</title>
      <published>2013-10-01T16:31:08-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-01T16:31:08-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This week: I talk with Scott Johnson about how he got started, takings risks, and being kind to people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bandwidth is provided by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.campaignmonitor.com/&quot;&gt;Campaign Monitor&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/sponsor-the-theme-foundry</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/sponsor-the-theme-foundry"/>
      <title>Sponsor: The Theme Foundry</title>
      <published>2013-10-01T11:32:29-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-10-01T11:32:29-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/cms/images/collections-theme-by-the-theme-foundry.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The Theme Foundry&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://thethemefoundry.com/&quot;&gt;The Theme Foundry&lt;/a&gt; has been building premium WordPress themes since 2008. They recently released Collections – a unique and beautiful WordPress theme for sharing, designed by Veerle Pieters. Visit the &lt;a href=&quot;http://demo.thethemefoundry.com/collections-theme/&quot;&gt;live demo of Collections&lt;/a&gt; to see it in action, or &lt;a href=&quot;http://thethemefoundry.com/wordpress/collections/&quot;&gt;purchase it now for $79&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What makes The Theme Foundry special?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A focus on quality over quantity.&lt;/strong&gt; You won’t find a huge assortment on their site – they keep a small, curated collection of &lt;a href=&quot;http://thethemefoundry.com/wordpress/&quot;&gt;premium WordPress themes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exclusive partner with WordPress.com&lt;/strong&gt; (the official hosted WordPress provider). Each and every theme goes through a stringent audit process from some of the best WordPress coders in the world.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Whole team support.&lt;/strong&gt; You get fast and friendly support from the team that &lt;em&gt;actually built&lt;/em&gt; your theme, not a part time support rep.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Thanks to &lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/s/sl&quot;&gt;The Theme Foundry&lt;/a&gt; for supporting The Bold Report this week. They’re awesome people. You might also want to checkout &lt;a href=&quot;http://memberful.com/&quot;&gt;Memberful&lt;/a&gt;, which is made by the same team.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/&quot;&gt;Sponsorship by The Syndicate.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/an-argument-for-app-net</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/an-argument-for-app-net"/>
      <title>An Argument for App.net</title>
      <published>2013-09-30T16:17:17-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-09-30T16:17:17-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Chris Enns:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The peo­ple who scoff at App​.net and won­der “why do we need another Twit­ter?” are missing the point. Actu­ally, they’re miss­ing the point of the inter­net. There’s plenty of room for another social net­work. You don’t have to use it but that doesn’t make it invalid. For every per­son that makes fun of Google+, there’s another 5 peo­ple get­ting a lot of com­mu­nity and fun out of it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, this article is talking about Favd, yet almost accidentally, he describes what I think is a very convincing argument for App.net’s relevance. Chris goes on to say:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;And while Favd might look like “yet another Insta­gram clone”, it’s tak­ing the parts of Insta­gram that peo­ple enjoy — tak­ing and shar­ing pho­tos with friends online — and leav­ing behind the cor­po­rate shadi­ness that comes with being asso­ci­ated with Facebook.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chris effectively points out, that just when we think a market has been saturated beyond belief, there’s always someone who can approach a problem a bit smarter.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/apple-becomes-most-valuable-brand-of-2013</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/apple-becomes-most-valuable-brand-of-2013"/>
      <title>Apple Becomes ‘Most Valuable Brand’ of 2013</title>
      <published>2013-09-30T12:05:04-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-09-30T12:05:04-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Apple has taken the top spot as 2013′s Most Valuable Brand, ending Coca-Cola’s 13 year streak as number one in the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.interbrand.com/en/best-global-brands/2013/Best-Global-Brands-2013-Brand-View.aspx&quot;&gt;annual Best Global Brands report&lt;/a&gt; compiled by Interbrand. Coca-Cola ended up third, surpassed by both Apple and Google this year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think this is pretty big news. A company’s brand is based a lot on public perception, and for Apple and Google to surpass Coca-Cola, which in my opinion is the one of the best brands ever created,&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; is quite the compliment on how they’re doing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;You know you agree with that. Whether you’re a Coke lover, or Pepsi lover (Oh god, can I footnote the footnote?), Coca-Cola has been advertising it’s drink with bears… bears. If you can advertise your product without taking cheap shots at your competitor, you’re doing well. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/google-web-designer</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/google-web-designer"/>
      <title>Google Web Designer</title>
      <published>2013-09-30T11:41:11-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-09-30T11:41:11-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, I see a tool like this from Google, and my whole opinion changes. I had some pretty harsh things to say about Macaw.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Google—in many ways—is the reason I do my job the way I do it. They’re advocates for building the web well, and fast. It’s hard for me to believe they’ll make a tool that does the opposite.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;I don’t know what happened to the tweet. But, I basically said that Macaw holds designers back from doing what they should do: learn to code. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/the-14-hour-work-day-myth</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/the-14-hour-work-day-myth"/>
      <title>The 14-Hour Work Day Myth</title>
      <published>2013-09-27T16:02:02-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-09-27T16:02:02-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Once I discovered the best times I like to work as a freelancer, I realized, why would I want to be working past that anyways? I love my job but I also love doing things outside my job. These things bring me great happiness and satisfaction, in turn, giving me the motivation and passion needed to perform effectively at my job.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love when people write about how working long hours is not a good idea. I love it when someone like Janna Hagan—whom I admire very much—does it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of which, have a great weekend!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/making-star-wars-great-again</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/making-star-wars-great-again"/>
      <title>Making Star Wars Great Again</title>
      <published>2013-09-27T16:01:57-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-09-27T16:01:57-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This is just magical. I think Abrams should bring this guy on board as a technical advisor in charge of proper use of the force.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Agreed.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/document-everything</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/document-everything"/>
      <title>♨ Document Everything</title>
      <published>2013-09-27T14:35:13-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-09-27T14:35:13-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Something I’ve been thinking about a lot recently is documentation. And yes, I’m thinking a little bit about legacy—documenting our life, and the things we make. However, I also mean documenting our process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s a lot of mystery surrounding what we do. I remember being a newcomer and feeling overwhelmed by everything it seemed that I needed to learn. This is where I think documentation can help us a lot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As an industry, we’re getting comfortable with doing things in the open. &lt;a href=&quot;http://opensourcedesign.is/&quot;&gt;Open Source Design&lt;/a&gt; is trying to do this, a project which I happen to be a contributor on, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://opensourcedesign.is/resourced/&quot;&gt;there are other people doing it&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what about being open about what we charge for services? What about talking about how much designers should be making in a beginning job? Medium level? Senior level? Should we negotiate for a signing bonus? Do companies still do this? To be very honest, I only learned about some of these things a couple months ago when I had dinner with my friend &lt;a href=&quot;http://bermonpainter.com/&quot;&gt;Bermon&lt;/a&gt;. Why is this such a mystery?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On a more personal level, what about our process? I have no documentation of my personal design and development process. All of it lives in my head, which quite frankly, isn’t useful for anyone. Pricing projects could be so much simpler if I had a process to run them through.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a lot of ways, I don’t know what I’m doing. Yet, at the same time, I really do. But that knowledge is wasted if I don’t share it with others. Not to mention, there will always be people that can benefit from something I’ve learned. We’re all in different places of our career.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the past month, I’ve met so many smart people who are saying nothing. They have great ideas, but they don’t tell anyone about them. Then, there are others who are content with believing in mythical gatekeepers that prevent them from having a voice in this industry.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It’s rubbish.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to have a voice, if you want to contribute, document everything. Tell people about what you’re doing, why you did it that way, and why others should think about doing it the same. We need your voice, but no one is going to beg you to use it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As cliché as it might sound, anyone has the power to make our industry better, and personally that’s why I love our industry and working in the open. When many minds come together and collaborate and share, the end result is one-hundred times better. When more people share, we have a more diverse group of people to admire, to interview, to invite to speak, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Step up. Document everything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;further-reading&quot;&gt;Further Reading&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.garann.com/dev/2013/how-to-blog-about-code-and-give-zero-fucks/&quot;&gt;How To Blog About Code and Give Zero *****&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;This particularly makes me mad. It’s so high-school drama. If you want to do something, do it. Complaining isn’t productive. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/the-app-store-problem</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/the-app-store-problem"/>
      <title>The App Store Problem</title>
      <published>2013-09-25T11:50:17-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-09-25T11:50:17-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Stephen Hackett on 512 Pixels:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The bottom line is this: developers should be able to work on their product in a sustainable way. Realmac are some of the good guys, and to have to backtrack on a business decision is a damn shame, especially in a world where people pour money into IAP-based games day and night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a real problem. We can obviously see a huge hole in the App Store ecosystem. Honestly, I have no idea if Apple will ever implement upgrade pricing. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.imore.com/apple-puts-its-price-tag-where-its-policy-charges-full-price-logic-pro-x-mac-app-store&quot;&gt;Signs point to no&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple desperately needs to examine this problem, and understand that the beautiful ecosystem it’s created, could crumble because of issues like this. And as the person purchasing software, I need to understand that developers &lt;strong&gt;are in their right&lt;/strong&gt; to charge money for new software. I love what &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/marcoarment/status/382899550341853184&quot;&gt;Marco Arment said&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Upset about &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/realmacsoftware&quot;&gt;@realmacsoftware&lt;/a&gt; asking for another 3 dollars for a big update to Clear and going universal?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;You should be ashamed of yourself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/deployments-with-github-and-ssh</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/deployments-with-github-and-ssh"/>
      <title>Deployments with GitHub and SSH</title>
      <published>2013-09-25T11:12:03-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-09-25T11:12:03-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I had no idea that deployments could be this easy. Which surprises me, because I thought I had explored my deployment options. Kennedy was kind enough to make a video too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Obviously this route is a bit nerdy, so if you want something that’s managed for you, I recommend &lt;a href=&quot;http://beanstalkapp.com/&quot;&gt;Beanstalk&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;http://deployhq.com/&quot;&gt;Deploy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/theeastwing-70</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/theeastwing-70"/>
      <title>The East Wing: Jeremy Fuksa</title>
      <published>2013-09-24T16:15:55-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-09-24T16:15:55-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This week: I talk with Jeremy Fuksa about being a design director, hiring designers, and the side-projects he works on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bandwidth is kindly provided by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.campaignmonitor.com/&quot;&gt;Campaign Monitor&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/marco-arments-lastest-project-overcast</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/marco-arments-lastest-project-overcast"/>
      <title>Marco Arment’s Latest Project: Overcast</title>
      <published>2013-09-24T11:29:01-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-09-24T11:29:01-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;If you need tons of features or anything I’m choosing not to do, you’ll probably be happier with one of the others. (Before I started using Overcast full-time, Downcast was my podcast app of choice.)&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;I’m adding some new stuff that I haven’t seen before in podcast players, and implementing what I think is the best set of core features from the existing apps. It’s my ideal podcast app.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is why I love Marco Arment. It happens to be the reason he’s also very successful. He trusts his gut, which I think is one of the most difficult things to learn how to do. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Marco isn’t given enough credit as a designer. He may not create the visuals for all of his products, but he is very deliberate with his design decisions. Can’t wait for this app.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/sustainable-web</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/sustainable-web"/>
      <title>James Christie on Sustainable Web Design</title>
      <published>2013-09-24T10:10:39-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-09-24T10:10:39-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;At 1.4MB, today’s average page is 15 times larger than it was 10 years ago, primarily due to images (881kB) and script (224kB). Plain old HTML totals just 54kB—but when’s the last time you saw an HTML-only site? This average page also makes more than 100 HTTP requests. Whether they fetch a big object or a small one, these add up to more delay and more power wastage. The average site is also slow: Alexa’s top 2,000 retailer sites now take an average of more than seven seconds to load—much longer than users consider acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We published &lt;a href=&quot;http://alistapart.com/issue/383&quot;&gt;a great issue&lt;/a&gt; today, but this particular article written by &lt;a href=&quot;http://jcux.co.uk/&quot;&gt;James Christie&lt;/a&gt; caught my eye. I’ve been doing a lot of research into performance, but I’d stupidly never thought how slow sites can have an impact on our environment. Site performance matters; not only to visitors, but to our planet.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/apple-iphone-touchscreen-faster-than-android-devices</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/apple-iphone-touchscreen-faster-than-android-devices"/>
      <title>Apple iPhone Touchscreen Faster than Android Devices</title>
      <published>2013-09-23T14:17:25-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-09-23T14:17:25-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Apple’s iPhone 5 is 2.5 times faster at responding to touches than Google Android devices, according to a benchmark test by game and app streaming firm Agawi.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This doesn’t surprise me at all. The level of care and detail Apple spends on this type of stuff is the reason people line up in the rain to get their devices. The article goes on to explain:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;the iPhone 5 responded to touches at an average time of 55 milliseconds…. The closest Android device was the Samsung Galaxy S4 at 114 milliseconds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s almost ridiculous to be examining this at the millisecond level, but tell me you’ve never noticed this delay when borrowing an Android device from a someone.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; Those small details matter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Because you don’t own one do you? &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/netflix-first-to-win-emmy-award-for-online-only-shows</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/netflix-first-to-win-emmy-award-for-online-only-shows"/>
      <title>Netflix First to Win Emmy Award for Online-Only Shows</title>
      <published>2013-09-23T14:03:04-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-09-23T14:03:04-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Netflix made history tonight, winning three Emmy awards for House of Cards, becoming the first company to win the awards for online-only shows. Original shows produced by Netflix had received 14 nominations — 9 of those for House of Cards alone. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is huge. I’ve said it before, and I’ll say it again: Netflix gets it. They’re making entertaining shows, and minimizing piracy. Traditional television hasn’t been able to nail both.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/blackberry-receives-buyout-offer</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/blackberry-receives-buyout-offer"/>
      <title>BlackBerry Receives Buyout Offer</title>
      <published>2013-09-23T12:50:07-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-09-23T12:50:07-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;BlackBerry has officially filed a letter with Canadian holding company Fairfax Financial, an offer that could lead to it returning to private ownership.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This could be a good thing for them. I remember when BlackBerry was on top, and then fell to the pits of irrelevance. Personally, I hope this helps them get their act together. I believe that the smartphone market will only continue to get better with better competition.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/apple-sells-nine-million-iphones</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/apple-sells-nine-million-iphones"/>
      <title>Apple Sells Nine Million iPhones in a Weekend</title>
      <published>2013-09-23T11:43:37-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-09-23T11:43:37-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Apple® today announced it has sold a record-breaking nine million new iPhone® 5s and iPhone 5c models, just three days after the launch of the new iPhones on September 20. In addition, more than 200 million iOS devices are now running the completely redesigned iOS 7, making it the fastest software upgrade in history.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every time the worlds says Apple is done, they come and do something like this. It’s also interesting to note that &lt;a href=&quot;http://news.cnet.com/8301-1035_3-57603876-94/samsung-sends-spies-to-uncover-apples-iphone-line-phenom/&quot;&gt;Samsung sent out a film crew to the iPhone lines&lt;/a&gt;. None of the competitors get why people are so passionate about Apple’s products.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/welcome</id>
      <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/welcome"/>
      <title>♨ Dear Reader,</title>
      <published>2013-09-23T00:00:00-05:00</published>
      <updated>2013-09-23T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
      <author>
        <name>Tim Smith</name>
        <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
      </author>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Welcome to &lt;em&gt;The Bold Report&lt;/em&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been pondering the creation of a blog for quite some time now. In the past few months, I’ve felt that the goals I have for my writing have outgrown my personal site, and it was time to move it to its own home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Bold Report&lt;/em&gt; is that new home. If you were a fan of my personal blog, you’ll see most of the same content on here. There will be long form articles which address topics that are on my mind, and links which point you to great content or exciting news around the web. As I have before, the links will have my commentary, which I’ve found that people appreciate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The purpose of this site &lt;em&gt;is not&lt;/em&gt; to report on breaking news—there are many other sites doing that—rather to inform you of exciting new technology, products you should keep your eye on, or what I happen to be learning at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We live in fascinating times. The evolution of technology is not only influencing how we design and develop experiences, it is changing the way we interact with others and our surroundings. Whole industries have been re-imagined, and that will only continue to happen. If nothing else, I want this blog to document that, and show my predictions as false or accurate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is my hope that you’ll join me on this journey. You can find the different ways to subscribe on the &lt;a href=&quot;/subscribe/&quot;&gt;subscribe page&lt;/a&gt;. Although there are no comments on this site, please feel free to reach me &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/ttimsmith&quot;&gt;via Twitter&lt;/a&gt; or email me at &lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#110;&amp;#116;&amp;#097;&amp;#099;&amp;#116;&amp;#064;&amp;#116;&amp;#104;&amp;#101;&amp;#098;&amp;#111;&amp;#108;&amp;#100;&amp;#114;&amp;#101;&amp;#112;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#116;&amp;#046;&amp;#110;&amp;#101;&amp;#116;&quot;&gt;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#110;&amp;#116;&amp;#097;&amp;#099;&amp;#116;&amp;#064;&amp;#116;&amp;#104;&amp;#101;&amp;#098;&amp;#111;&amp;#108;&amp;#100;&amp;#114;&amp;#101;&amp;#112;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#116;&amp;#046;&amp;#110;&amp;#101;&amp;#116;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for reading, it means a lot to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;—Tim&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
  

</feed>
