<?xml version="1.0"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <link rel="hub" href="https://pubsubhubbub.appspot.com"/>

  <title>The Bold Report</title>
  <link href="http://theboldreport.net"/>
  <link type="application/atom+xml" rel="self" href="http://theboldreport.net/atom.xml"/>
  <updated>2013-09-22T18:39:14-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://theboldreport.net</id>
  <author>
    <name>Tim Smith</name>
    <email>smith@ttimsmith.com</email>
  </author>

  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/testing</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/testing"/>
    <title>Testing This Out</title>
    <published>2013-09-22T00:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-09-22T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A snappy introduction that sets out the main argument for the piece. I’ll cover the main ideas right here and hint at my conclusion without giving the game away completely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you can keep your head when all about you are losing theirs and blaming it on you; If you can trust yourself when all men doubt you, but make allowance for their doubting too; if you can wait and not be tired by waiting,or being lied about, don’t deal in lies, or being hated, don’t give way to hating, and yet don’t look too good, nor talk too wise; if you can dream — and not make dreams your master; if you can think — and not make thoughts your aim; if you can meet with Triumph and Disaster and treat those two impostors just the same.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you can bear to hear the truth you’ve spoken twisted by knaves to make a trap for fools, or watch the things you gave your life to broken, and stoop and build ‘em up with worn-out tools; if you can make one heap of all your winnings and risk it on one turn of pitch-and-toss, and lose, and start again at your beginnings and never breathe a word about your loss.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-second-level-heading&quot;&gt;A Second Level Heading&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you can force your heart and nerve and sinew to serve your turn long after they are gone, and so hold on when there is nothing in you except the will which says to them; ‘Hold on!’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“If you can talk with crowds and keep your virtue, or walk with kings — nor lose the common touch.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If neither foes nor loving friends can hurt you, if all men count with you, but none too much; if you can fill the unforgiving minute with sixty seconds’ worth of distance run - yours is the Earth and everything that’s in it, and - which is more - you’ll be a man my son!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“If—” is a poem written in 1895 by British Nobel laureate Rudyard Kipling. It was first published in the “Brother Square Toes” chapter of Rewards and Fairies, Kipling’s 1910 collection of short stories and poems. Like William Ernest Henley’s “Invictus”, it is a memorable evocation of Victorian stoicism and the “stiff upper lip” that popular culture has made into a traditional British virtue. Its status is confirmed both by the number of parodies it has inspired, and by the widespread popularity it still enjoys amongst Britons. It is often voted Britain’s favourite poem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“If you can meet with Triumph and Disaster and treat those two impostors just the same”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-third-level-heading&quot;&gt;A Third Level Heading&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This line is written on the wall of the Centre Court players’ entrance at the British tennis tournament, Wimbledon, and a part of the poem was read in a promotional video for the Wimbledon 2008 gentleman’s final by Roger Federer and Rafael Nadal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;a-fourth-level-heading&quot;&gt;A Fourth Level Heading&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to Kipling in his autobiography Something of Myself, posthumously published in 1937, the poem was inspired by Dr. Leander Starr Jameson, who in 1895 led a raid by British forces against the Boers in South Africa, subsequently called the Jameson Raid. This defeat increased the tensions that ultimately led to the Second Boer War. The British press, however, portrayed Jameson as a hero in the middle of the disaster, and the actual defeat as a British victory. Jameson’s life — and the connection to the poem — is covered in the book The If Man.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The text used in this fake article is from Rudyard Kipling’s If—&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/tirp-8</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/tirp-8"/>
    <title>The Intellectual Radio Program: X-Files Theme, Then A Mariachi Band</title>
    <published>2013-09-20T00:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-09-20T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This week: We talk iPhone 5S/5C, side projects and ended with a therapy session with Chris on whether he should make Minecraft videos or keep podcasting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hx6Ao4CB9t4&amp;amp;feature=share&quot;&gt;video version&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/i-need-to-save-money</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/i-need-to-save-money"/>
    <title>Save Your Money, or Go Out of Business</title>
    <published>2013-09-20T00:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-09-20T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Save your money. A small business/freelancer needs cash. Keep at least three months of overhead sitting in a savings account. Then personally you need at least two months of living costs in a savings account.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What an honest post. I’m historically horrible at saving money, and yet as a freelancer, I know I should have at least 5 months of savings. I don’t think I’ve ever had that saved in my life, even when I was making good money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Save your money peeps!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/ios7-review</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/ios7-review"/>
    <title>iOS 7 Review</title>
    <published>2013-09-18T00:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-09-18T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;It’s pretty awesome. Control Center is the bomb-diggity.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/rss-ping-for-static-blogs</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/rss-ping-for-static-blogs"/>
    <title>RSS Ping for Static Blogs</title>
    <published>2013-09-17T00:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-09-17T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;When I moved over to Jekyll, one of things you miss out on is RSS Feed pinging. What the hell is “RSS pinging”? Basically, it’s your site letting the internet know that their’s fresh content on your feed. WordPress automatically does this when you publish new content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For this site, I use a service that automatically tweets new headlines to the Twitter and App.net accounts, and without a ping, these things have no idea there’s a new post in the feed. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, &lt;a href=&quot;http://hami.sh/&quot;&gt;Hamish Macpherson&lt;/a&gt;, came up with a very simple way of making this work. Using a PHP script together with a post-deploy hook, it’s automatic once again! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personally, I use a Rake task, but I may end up switching for the automation aspect. If you’d like to take a look at my Rake task, you’ll find in &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/ttimsmith/ttimsmith.com&quot;&gt;the repo for this site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/ipo-could-kill-twitter</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/ipo-could-kill-twitter"/>
    <title>IPO Could Kill Twitter</title>
    <published>2013-09-16T10:35:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-09-16T10:35:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Marcus Wohlsen from Wired:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;But once it goes public, Twitter will have no choice but to strive to maximize shareholder returns, which would appear to create a Catch-22. More ads on Twitter means more money for Twitter, which makes shareholders happy. But more ads on Twitter will make users less happy, which means fewer users. Fewer users mean lower ad rates, which makes shareholders unhappy — a vicious cycle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is what scares me about Twitter going public. As a private company, they’ve already proven to not give a damn about users, and the pressure of shareholders could make it worse. They’ll serve us just enough ads so we hate them, but not enough so we leave.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I see a very grim future for Twitter clients. Unless these developers budge and allow for sponsored tweets in the timeline, I don’t see how Twitter will allow them to exist. I use Tweetbot exclusively, which can’t be good for Twitter in terms of selling ads and users actually seeing them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The real shame in all of this, is that a platform like App.net will never be as popular for the masses. Which is unfortunate because they &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;actually have a freaking business model&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/dear-readers</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/dear-readers"/>
    <title>Dear Readers,</title>
    <published>2013-09-16T08:44:33-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-09-16T08:44:33-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;As you may have noticed in the past couple of weeks, I’ve taken the responsibility of writing on this site a bit more seriously. If you haven’t noticed, that’s ok, I’m telling you now. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since &lt;a href=&quot;/2013/08/moving-over-to-jekyll/&quot;&gt;moving over to Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;, the ability to write and publish quickly has given me fewer excuses not to write. I know that whether people read or not, it’s important to maintain some type of documentation of life and work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For years, I’ve stressed about writing things that would be “interesting”; judging at every turn whether people would like what I had to say. More recently, I’ve been persuading myself not to care. I write and share my opinion on things that interest me, and call it a day. To my surprise, there are those who appreciate that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m also interested in becoming a better writer, and after doing research, I found that as with most things, the best way is to practice. I look up to writers like &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.marco.org/&quot;&gt;Marco Arment&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://shawnblanc.net/&quot;&gt;Shawn Blanc&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://sarawb.com/&quot;&gt;Sara Wachter-Boettcher&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.avclark.com/&quot;&gt;Adam Clark&lt;/a&gt;, and draw inspiration from how they write. What I love especially about Sara and Adam is the level of honesty they’re able to communicate with their writing. I admire that vulnerability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So here’s to a new beginning with this site. I hope you’ll be part of it. You can now subscribe to the &lt;a href=&quot;http://ttimsmith.com/feed.xml&quot;&gt;master feed&lt;/a&gt; or an &lt;a href=&quot;http://ttimsmith.com/feed.article.xml&quot;&gt;articles-only feed&lt;/a&gt;. All of the posts are shared on &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/ttimsmith_com&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://alpha.app.net/ttimsmith_com&quot;&gt;App.net&lt;/a&gt;, and if you prefer email, &lt;a href=&quot;/newsletter&quot;&gt;there’s an option for that&lt;/a&gt; too. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please &lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#115;&amp;#109;&amp;#105;&amp;#116;&amp;#104;&amp;#064;&amp;#116;&amp;#116;&amp;#105;&amp;#109;&amp;#115;&amp;#109;&amp;#105;&amp;#116;&amp;#104;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#109;&quot;&gt;say hello&lt;/a&gt;. I love hearing from you guys.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;—Tim&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/garann-means-on-writing-about-code</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/garann-means-on-writing-about-code"/>
    <title>Garann Means on Writing about Code</title>
    <published>2013-09-12T12:50:32-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-09-12T12:50:32-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;All joking aside, our communities need to hear from people who aren’t the maintainers and conference speakers and web celebrities.[…] The big names create an echo chamber where ideas are safe and popular and failure and being wrong are covered up so no one else can learn from them. We don’t really badly need any more of that crap. We need you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just love how Garann writes. I haven’t had the chance to talk with her much, but I imagines she writes a lot like she talks, which is awesome. Her and Divya Manian do an &lt;a href=&quot;http://fripfrap.io/&quot;&gt;awesome podcast about front-end stuff&lt;/a&gt;. You should check it out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, this is something I talked about with many people at Blend Conf. Not enough people are writing about their experiences and process. If you finish the article and don’t feel the need to write something, we really need to talk. &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/reeder-is-back-with-a-new-app</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/reeder-is-back-with-a-new-app"/>
    <title>Reeder is Back with a New App</title>
    <published>2013-09-12T11:34:39-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-09-12T11:34:39-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Reeder 2 features a new design, support for services like Fever’s “Hot List”, and a convenient pull-out tab for sharing reminiscent of Windows 8’s “Charms” menu, but the app’s most important new feature is that it’s “universal” — it works on both iPhone and iPad.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reeder is back! So happy to see Reeder come out with a new app, that works with new services.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; Shawn Blanc &lt;a href=&quot;http://shawnblanc.net/2013/09/the-new-reeder-for-ios/&quot;&gt;says the new app is great&lt;/a&gt;, and I trust him. I’ll most likely buy and give it a try in the next couple of days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s truly amazing to see how the RSS landscape has changed in the past few months. The whole Google Reader shutdown gave everyone a kick in the pants to do a better job with their app, and gave others the opportunity to create new businesses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;From what I can see, it works with Feed Wrangler, Feedbin, Feedly, Fever, Readability, and allows you to bypass syncing and just do local RSS subscriptions. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/blend-conf-2013</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/blend-conf-2013"/>
    <title>Blend Conf 2013</title>
    <published>2013-09-10T00:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-09-10T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I had an absolute blast in Charlotte for Blend Conf, and I really hope I can make it next year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First off, I just want to extend a thank you to Bermon Painter for putting on this amazing event. The fact he did it mostly by himself is admirable, and was a complete hit in its first year. Bermon was so kind to take a chance on me, and I’m so grateful, and honored to have spoken at the first Blend Conf. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The interesting thing about conferences is that when you hear about them, often times you hear about the speakers, the venue, the city, friends that are going, etc. Those are all great. However, the beauty lies in the things you have no idea about. The people you meet, the friends you make, and the conversations you have. For me, Blend Conference was definitely all of this. I’ve made great new friends, and I’m following new people who are just so insanely smart. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two talks that really stood out for me were &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.garthdb.com/&quot;&gt;Garth’s&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://wrenlanier.com/&quot;&gt;Wren’s&lt;/a&gt;. Garth talked about how designers can open source, and he’s in fact &lt;a href=&quot;http://opensourcedesign.is/&quot;&gt;created a site to begin this movement&lt;/a&gt;. I realized during that talk that developers are more and more comfortable with sharing how things are accomplished, and putting tons of their source code on GitHub. At this point, it seemed so normal, I’d forgotten that designers don’t really do this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re very protective of our designs and don’t like to reveal how the “sausage is made” per se. This happens for various reasons, but the biggest one is often thinking a particular solution is specific to a project. The artistic side of us loves to believe that our thoughts aren’t somehow reusable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wren also gave a great talk about designing on the z-axis. It blew my mind. That’s really all I can say. The way she explained the future of design got me really excited.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ll see both of these people on The East Wing soon, so stay tuned for that. If you weren’t able to make it to Blend Conf this year, I definitely recommend it. The atmosphere is just so nice, and Charlotte is a beautiful city.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you next year!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/the-best-piece-ive-read-this-year</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/the-best-piece-ive-read-this-year"/>
    <title>The Best Piece I’ve Read This Year</title>
    <published>2013-09-04T16:50:32-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-09-04T16:50:32-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Every time I open up Photoshop or IA Writer or sit down at the drum kit, a cloud of angst settles around me as I set out to create or write something people will find impressive. And not just impressive, but so damn good, it will be linked to thousands of times and retweeted for all eternity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adam wrote so many things that I just didn’t know how to communicate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I never ship because I can’t face the potential of failure. But this is failure in itself. The only thing worse than being the fat guy in the pool, is being the fat guy in the pool with a shirt on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can’t tell you how many times I’ve been &lt;strong&gt;that&lt;/strong&gt; guy. Read this, it might explain your feelings perfectly.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/microsoft-acquiring-nokia-is-an-important-move</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/microsoft-acquiring-nokia-is-an-important-move"/>
    <title>Microsoft Acquiring Nokia is an Important Move</title>
    <published>2013-09-03T11:31:51-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-09-03T11:31:51-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Microsoft’s Nokia acquisition is more important than you think. It’s being brushed off by many in the media, and definitely by a lot of Apple fans; we love to ridicule this type of news. &lt;a href=&quot;http://gigaom.com/2013/09/03/why-i-think-the-7-2-billion-microsoft-nokia-deal-is-a-terrible-idea/&quot;&gt;Some just downright think it’s a terrible idea&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing is definitely true, the move is late. This acquisition would’ve interested a lot more people a couple of years ago. The mobile market is very competitive, Apple and Google have years of experience, and it seems Amazon wants a piece of the pie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Microsoft and Nokia may be a joke in terms of market share&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;, but them joining forces is important news. The fact that hardware and software are now being done semi-in-house is a big deal, and indicative of some type of vision which could be successful&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:2&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:2&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. Microsoft has noticed something very important, and I talked about this when I wrote about &lt;a href=&quot;/2013/08/why-scott-forstall-should-be-microsofts-next-ceo/&quot;&gt;Scott Forstall becoming CEO&lt;/a&gt;—being responsible for the complete experience is the key to making products people want to use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since its inception, the company has allowed others to create the hardware for their software&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:3&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:3&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. They’ve given up control of the experience, and I feel it’s one of the biggest reasons they aren’t the company they want to be. Nokia becoming part of Microsoft begins to fix that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Microsoft doesn’t want to be &lt;em&gt;just&lt;/em&gt; a software company.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Steve Ballmer’s letter to employees, he said, “We are committed to working with partners, helping them build great products and great businesses on our platform, and we believe this deal will increase our partner value proposition over time.” I predict that in 4 years, Microsoft will be exclusively making Windows Phone. It’ll be theirs; software and hardware.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the things that makes Apple so successful is the way they control the ecosystem. Lots of power users are turned away by how little control they have, but to the normal consumer, the careful curation of an ecosystem, makes the experience more enjoyable. It’s also important to note, that companies that don’t exercise this type of control &lt;a href=&quot;http://bits.blogs.nytimes.com/2013/08/28/u-s-government-issues-warning-about-security-on-android-phones/&quot;&gt;have lots of security problems&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next year and a half will tell whether Microsoft will take this opportunity, and execute well on it. They need a new phone, running a better operating system. If Microsoft is at all successful in the next 5 years, it will be in part because of this move.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a href=&quot;http://http://www.theverge.com/2013/9/3/4688962/with-nokia-microsoft-wants-to-triple-windows-phone-marketshare-by-2018&quot;&gt;this article&lt;/a&gt;, Microsoft’s marketshare is just over 4% in the smartphone market. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:2&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;I think the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nokia.com/us-en/phones/phone/lumia1020/&quot;&gt;Nokia Lumia&lt;/a&gt; is a great example of some great hardware decisions. It’s a pretty good-looking phone, and has a 41 megapixel camera which is perfect for what people want to do with their phone: take pictures of themselves and food. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:2&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:3&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;This is the reason you spend hours uninstalling software from a PC you just bought. Android has this same problem by allowing carriers to make different versions of it. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:3&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/keyboard-maestro-macros-sharing-links</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/keyboard-maestro-macros-sharing-links"/>
    <title>Keyboard Maestro Macros: Sharing Links</title>
    <published>2013-09-02T16:40:14-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-09-02T16:40:14-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I’ve been using Keyboard Maestro for about two weeks, and I’ve enjoyed how much time it’s starting to save me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two new Keyboard Maestro Macros I’ve made are for sharing links. I often come across things on the web that I want to share and I have to copy the title, switch to Tweetbot, paste the tile, switch back to Chrome, copy the URL, switch back to Tweetbot, and paste the URL. This get’s irritating, so I created a Macro two copy these two values and put them on my clipboard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/2013/09/macro-1.png&quot; alt=&quot;Tweet Sharing Macro&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe Safari has built in sharing, but that still sucks because you have to click. This uses a keyboard shortcut.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another thing I do often is copy links for show notes. For most podcasters, show notes are the worst part of doing the show. It’s difficult to get the link quick and save it somewhere. I personally envy the hosts on 5by5 that have a bookmarklet. However, I’ve solved this problem quite easily for me with another macro.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/2013/09/macro-2.png&quot; alt=&quot;Markdown Sharing Link&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So easy! I press &lt;code&gt;Ctrl+Opt+M&lt;/code&gt; and the link is in my clipboard formatted as Markdown. The time this saves me! I used to use a Chrome Extension, but again, I try to use the mouse as little as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hope these can save you some time. If you’ve never used &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.keyboardmaestro.com/main/&quot;&gt;Keyboard Maestro&lt;/a&gt;, I recommend you look into it. Keyboard shortcuts FTW!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/getting-interested-in-front-end-performance</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/getting-interested-in-front-end-performance"/>
    <title>Getting Interested in Front-end Performance</title>
    <published>2013-09-01T16:17:44-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-09-01T16:17:44-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Harry Roberts:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;It’s hard, if not impossible, to deny that performance is by far one of the most critical aspects of any decent web project, be it a small portfolio site, a mobile-first web app, right through to a full-scale ecommerce project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is an area I’ve been dabbling into more recently. As a wanna-be front-end developer, I’ve tried to do more research into how I can do my job better, and make the sites I create faster. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This article is quite the extensive guide on various things you could do to make your sites faster. The obvious ones are things like minimizing http requests, and minifying files. Yet, one technique I hadn’t heard of before was using &lt;code&gt;rel=&quot;dns-prefetch&quot;&lt;/code&gt;. On this site, I put this in the head:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;html&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;link&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;rel=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;dns-prefetch&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;href=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;//engine.carbonads.com&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;link&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;rel=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;dns-prefetch&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;href=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;//static.carbonads.com&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;link&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;rel=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;dns-prefetch&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;href=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;//use.typekit.net&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Essentially this does exactly what you think it would do. You can prefetch a hostname’s DNS with the code above. This is helpful when you need assets from an external source.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re building sites of any kind, check out the article, very helpful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;further-reading&quot;&gt;Further Reading&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://daverupert.com/2010/06/web-performant-wordpress/&quot;&gt;Web Performant WordPress by Dave Rupert&lt;/a&gt; - A really great article if you’re running on WordPress. It is from 2010, so take the advice with a grain of salt.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/08/netflix-expands-original-content-with-stand-up-comedy</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/08/netflix-expands-original-content-with-stand-up-comedy"/>
    <title>Netflix Expands Original Content with Stand-up Comedy</title>
    <published>2013-08-29T12:59:37-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-08-29T12:59:37-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Netflix is opening up another front in its ongoing battle with HBO: comedy. The New York Times reports that Parks and Recreation star Aziz Ansari’s upcoming special Buried Alive will debut on Netflix on November 1st, making it the highest profile stand-up special on the service to date.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Netflix get’s it. If I had the money, I’d buy Netflix stock, because they’ve done nothing but make great decisions in the past year. To think, there was a time when Netflix looked like it would go down in flames, and now is a producer of quality content at an &lt;strong&gt;affordable&lt;/strong&gt; price. That’s a difficult thing to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can’t wait to see what’s in store for the company in the next year. I see very good things.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/08/speaking-at-blend-conf</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/08/speaking-at-blend-conf"/>
    <title>Speaking at Blend Conf</title>
    <published>2013-08-28T15:10:51-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-08-28T15:10:51-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Next week, I’ll be flying to Charlotte, North Carolina, to give my second-ever conference talk. That I’m nervous would be an understatement. But, I’m very passionate about the topic,&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; and can’t wait to talk about it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to take a moment to thank &lt;a href=&quot;http://bermonpainter.com/&quot;&gt;Bermon Painter&lt;/a&gt; and Blend Conf. He invited me to speak even before I had &lt;a href=&quot;/2013/05/become-a-better-designer-with-side-projects/&quot;&gt;proof that I could speak&lt;/a&gt; at a venue. I really appreciate that. Not to mention, Blend Conf has been our primary sponsor since July, and I’m very grateful for that as well. Without Blend Conf, we could not have kept doing the show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those of you going, please &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/ttimsmith&quot;&gt;get in touch&lt;/a&gt;! We should grab lunch, dinner, or something. It’ll be lots of fun. If by any chance you’ve been waiting to get a ticket, do it now! I believe there are only 20 tickets left, and remember you can use &lt;code&gt;timsentme&lt;/code&gt; for 20% off. If you can’t make it, Bermon has an &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.indiegogo.com/projects/help-us-record-40-amazing-sessions-at-blend-conference&quot;&gt;Indiegogo Campaign&lt;/a&gt; to get all the sessions recorded. Then you can watch them from your couch. How cool is that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you next week! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;I’ll be talking about side-projects and how they make you a better designer. Here’s the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.blendconf.com/schedule/&quot;&gt;full schedule&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  

</feed>
