<?xml version="1.0"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <link rel="hub" href="https://pubsubhubbub.appspot.com"/>

  <title>The Bold Report - Articles Only</title>
  <link href="http://theboldreport.net"/>
  <link type="application/atom+xml" rel="self" href="http://theboldreport.net/feed.article.xml"/>
  <updated>2013-09-30T11:41:30-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://theboldreport.net</id>
  <author>
    <name>Tim Smith</name>
    <email>smith@ttimsmith.com</email>
  </author>

  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/document-everything</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/document-everything"/>
    <title>Document Everything</title>
    <published>2013-09-27T14:35:13-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-09-27T14:35:13-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Something I’ve been thinking about a lot recently is documentation. And yes, I’m thinking a little bit about legacy—documenting our life, and the things we make. However, I also mean documenting our process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s a lot of mystery surrounding what we do. I remember being a newcomer and feeling overwhelmed by everything it seemed that I needed to learn. This is where I think documentation can help us a lot. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As an industry, we’re getting comfortable with doing things in the open. &lt;a href=&quot;http://opensourcedesign.is/&quot;&gt;Open Source Design&lt;/a&gt; is trying to do this, a project which I happen to be a contributor on, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://opensourcedesign.is/resourced/&quot;&gt;there are other people doing it&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what about being open about what we charge for services? What about talking about how much designers should be making in a beginning job? Medium level? Senior level? Should we negotiate for a signing bonus? Do companies still do this? To be very honest, I only learned about some of these things a couple months ago when I had dinner with my friend &lt;a href=&quot;http://bermonpainter.com/&quot;&gt;Bermon&lt;/a&gt;. Why is this such a mystery?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On a more personal level, what about our process? I have no documentation of my personal design and development process. All of it lives in my head, which quite frankly, isn’t useful for anyone. Pricing projects could be so much simpler if I had a process to run them through. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a lot of ways, I don’t know what I’m doing. Yet, at the same time, I really do. But that knowledge is wasted if I don’t share it with others. Not to mention, there will always be people that can benefit from something I’ve learned. We’re all in different places of our career.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the past month, I’ve met so many smart people who are saying nothing. They have great ideas, but they don’t tell anyone about them. Then, there are others who are content with believing in mythical gatekeepers that prevent them from having a voice in this industry.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It’s rubbish.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to have a voice, if you want to contribute, document everything. Tell people about what you’re doing, why you did it that way, and why others should think about doing it the same. We need your voice, but no one is going to beg you to use it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As cliché as it might sound, anyone has the power to make our industry better, and personally that’s why I love our industry and working in the open. When many minds come together and collaborate and share, the end result is one-hundred times better. When more people share, we have a more diverse group of people to admire, to interview, to invite to speak, etc. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Step up. Document everything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;further-reading&quot;&gt;Further Reading&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.garann.com/dev/2013/how-to-blog-about-code-and-give-zero-fucks/&quot;&gt;How To Blog About Code and Give Zero *****&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;This particularly makes me mad. It’s so high-school drama. If you want to do something, do it. Complaining isn’t productive. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/welcome</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/welcome"/>
    <title>Dear Reader,</title>
    <published>2013-09-23T00:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-09-23T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Welcome to &lt;em&gt;The Bold Report&lt;/em&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been pondering the creation of a blog for quite some time now. In the past few months, I’ve felt that the goals I have for my writing have outgrown my personal site, and it was time to move it to its own home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Bold Report&lt;/em&gt; is that new home. If you were a fan of my personal blog, you’ll see most of the same content on here. There will be long form articles which address topics that are on my mind, and links which point you to great content or exciting news around the web. As I have before, the links will have my commentary, which I’ve found that people appreciate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The purpose of this site &lt;em&gt;is not&lt;/em&gt; to report on breaking news—there are many other sites doing that—rather to inform you of exciting new technology, products you should keep your eye on, or what I happen to be learning at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We live in fascinating times. The evolution of technology is not only influencing how we design and develop experiences, it is changing the way we interact with others and our surroundings. Whole industries have been re-imagined, and that will only continue to happen. If nothing else, I want this blog to document that, and show my predictions as false or accurate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is my hope that you’ll join me on this journey. You can find the different ways to subscribe on the &lt;a href=&quot;/subscribe/&quot;&gt;subscribe page&lt;/a&gt;. Although there are no comments on this site, please feel free to reach me &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/ttimsmith&quot;&gt;via Twitter&lt;/a&gt; or email me at &lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#110;&amp;#116;&amp;#097;&amp;#099;&amp;#116;&amp;#064;&amp;#116;&amp;#104;&amp;#101;&amp;#098;&amp;#111;&amp;#108;&amp;#100;&amp;#114;&amp;#101;&amp;#112;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#116;&amp;#046;&amp;#110;&amp;#101;&amp;#116;&quot;&gt;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#110;&amp;#116;&amp;#097;&amp;#099;&amp;#116;&amp;#064;&amp;#116;&amp;#104;&amp;#101;&amp;#098;&amp;#111;&amp;#108;&amp;#100;&amp;#114;&amp;#101;&amp;#112;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#116;&amp;#046;&amp;#110;&amp;#101;&amp;#116;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for reading, it means a lot to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;—Tim&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  

</feed>
