<?xml version="1.0"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <link rel="hub" href="https://pubsubhubbub.appspot.com"/>

  <title>The Bold Report</title>
  <link href="http://theboldreport.net"/>
  <link type="application/atom+xml" rel="self" href="http://theboldreport.net/atom.xml"/>
  <updated>2013-10-08T10:59:37-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://theboldreport.net</id>
  <author>
    <name>Tim Smith</name>
    <email>smith@ttimsmith.com</email>
  </author>

  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/sponsor-mailchimp</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/sponsor-mailchimp"/>
    <title>Sponsor: MailChimp</title>
    <published>2013-10-08T10:59:27-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-10-08T10:59:27-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/cms/images/MC_GoesWithYou_600wide.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;MailChimp Sponsor&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/s/sz&quot;&gt;new generation of MailChimp&lt;/a&gt; adapts to your workflow, regardless of the device you’re using and size of your team. A cohesive experience across desktop and mobile devices means you can create, send, and track email campaigns in any context.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/s/sz&quot;&gt;Check out the MailChimp today.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Thanks to &lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/s/sz&quot;&gt;MailChimp&lt;/a&gt; for supporting The Bold Report this week. &lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/&quot;&gt;Sponsorship by The Syndicate.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/eric-schmidt-tells-jokes</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/eric-schmidt-tells-jokes"/>
    <title>Eric Schmidt Tells Jokes</title>
    <published>2013-10-08T10:56:17-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-10-08T10:56:17-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Eric Schmidt is apparently quite the jokester. When told that some don’t find Android secure, Schmidt responded, “Not secure? It’s more secure than the iPhone.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good one, dude.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/starting-with-sass</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/starting-with-sass"/>
    <title>Starting with Sass</title>
    <published>2013-10-07T13:50:16-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-10-07T13:50:16-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Chris Bowler:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I’ve looked at several tutorials over the years, but many were written with a certain assumption for the level of knowledge on the other end. Many can be a struggle for the beginner because you may not even have the tools to be able to use Sass. Because of this, I wanted to write a handful of tips on what helped me get on board.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’ve been on the fence about trying Sass, this is a really good place to start. I promise you, &lt;em&gt;I promise you&lt;/em&gt;, you’ll never go back to normal CSS.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/yale-professor-calls-bing-it-on-claims-bogus</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/yale-professor-calls-bing-it-on-claims-bogus"/>
    <title>Yale Professor Calls ‘Bing It On’ Claims Bogus</title>
    <published>2013-10-04T11:42:35-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-10-04T11:42:35-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This week, a Yale law professor took aim at Microsoft’s “&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bingiton.com/&quot;&gt;Bing It On&lt;/a&gt;” campaign…&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;And &lt;a href=&quot;http://islandia.law.yale.edu/ayres/BingItOn_Draft%209.pdf&quot;&gt;Ayres’ results differed sharply&lt;/a&gt; from Microsoft’s: “We found that, to the contrary of Microsoft’s claim, 53 percent of subjects preferred Google and 41 percent Bing (6 percent of results were “ties”). This is not even close to the advertised claim that people prefer Bing ‘nearly two-to-one.’”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is fascinating. Microsoft responded to this professor, but in my opinion, gave a statement that were just words and didn’t explain why this test was so different from the one Microsoft conducted. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is what happens when you make commercials that call out other brands. Making fun of other people is the low thing to do, and quite honestly, the easy thing to do. Tell us how Bing is &lt;em&gt;actually&lt;/em&gt; better Microsoft, or shut up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;related-watching&quot;&gt;Related Watching&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Xubz8EuHosQ&quot;&gt;TV Commercial - Microsoft Surface Tablet: Less Talking. More Doing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/review-1password-4-for-mac</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/review-1password-4-for-mac"/>
    <title>Review: 1Password 4 for Mac</title>
    <published>2013-10-03T00:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-10-03T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://agilebits.com/onepassword&quot;&gt;1Password&lt;/a&gt; is one of my favorite apps. The amount of time it has saved me is unmeasurable, and it’s made my password strategy secure and delightful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those of you who don’t know about 1Password, it’s a great utility app to store and generate passwords. For years, I was the person who had &lt;em&gt;the same password for everything&lt;/em&gt;. With 1Password, I don’t do that anymore, I’m able to search through weak passwords and generate stronger ones, making it less likely to get hacked. Even if that does happen, none of my passwords are the same, so I only need to reset the one that’s been compromised.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;first-impressions&quot;&gt;First Impressions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The new interface is beautiful, and obviously influenced by the iOS version.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The Chrome extension got a facelift, and generated passwords are not only filled in forms, they’re also copied to your clipboard.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;1Password Mini brings most of the power of the main app to the menubar. This is great for entering passwords into apps that aren’t the browser. I disliked having to open the main app to do this in previous versions.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;new-features-in-1password-4-for-mac&quot;&gt;New Features in 1Password 4 for Mac&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;design&quot;&gt;Design&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first thing you’ll notice when you open the new 1Password is the beautiful interface. If you’ve already purchased &lt;a href=&quot;https://agilebits.com/onepassword/ios&quot;&gt;the latest iOS app&lt;/a&gt;, you’ll notice that the new design is very similar, which delights me greatly. This redesign is years overdue, and the AgileBits team has delivered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://theboldreport.net/uploads/2013/10/1p4-mac-main.png&quot; alt=&quot;1Password 4 for Mac main view&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love that this redesign in a lot of ways is a re-align. The interface remains in the three column layout, yet with an easy-on-the-eyes, light background. The type has greatly improved, and the middle column no longer has the “shelf” look. The new layout, allows you to see more logins in the window without having to scroll and sports better looking icons. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thankfully, the last column has been redone too. It used to be confusing to look at, and honestly, I didn’t know what was going on. It’s now a lot more simplified and only displays necessary information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That being said, my favorite part of the main view, is the new “Security Audit” that appears in the far left column. It gives you easy access to weak passwords, duplicate passwords, and passwords that are old and might need to be changed. To be clear, this type of filtering has always been present in 1Password, but the fact that it’s now front and center, is very valuable to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;multiple-vaults&quot;&gt;Multiple Vaults&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One feature that I can see becoming very popular is the new feature of multiple vaults. I haven’t actually been using this feature, but it’s one of those things that I think could help me organize the different sets of passwords. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is especially true when I worked for a company. Having a separate vault exclusively for company logins, would’ve been a great way to get organized. This makes managing items easier, and makes cleaning out items you no longer need, a breeze.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://theboldreport.net/uploads/2013/10/1p4-mac-create-new-vault.png&quot; alt=&quot;Create a new vault&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;password-mini&quot;&gt;1Password Mini&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love that they made a menubar app. I’m definitely one of those people that has &lt;em&gt;way too many&lt;/em&gt; of them.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:2&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:2&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; Interestingly, the menubar app is what comes up now when you press &lt;code&gt;⌘CMD + \&lt;/code&gt;. It seems that the 1Password browser extension is now only needed to run the code necessary for the autofill. You’ll never actually need to press the button anymore, which is nice, because it’s one less button in the extensions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://theboldreport.net/uploads/2013/10/1p4-mac-1p-mini-item-details.png&quot; alt=&quot;1Password Mini details&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s too early for me to say, but I think 1Password Mini could completely replace the main app for me. So far, I haven’t needed to open the main app for day-to-day responsibilities. To be honest, I only looked at the main app the day I downloaded it, and today when writing this review.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;other-features-you-should-know-about&quot;&gt;Other Features You Should Know About&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shared Items&lt;/strong&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;
Till now, I haven’t needed to ever share login items, but I can definitely see the practicality of this. You can share items with email or iMessage, and if the person makes changes, the item automatically updates when shared back.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;256-bit Authenticated Encryption&lt;/strong&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;
I have no idea what this means, except that 1Password is constantly being updated to be more and more secure. From what I’m told, this prevents attacks that don’t even exist yet.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wifi Sync&lt;/strong&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;
This feature is back from previous versions. Personally, I use Dropbox to sync my Vault between my Mac, iPad and iPhone, but whatever floats your boat. They have iCloud sync too.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;final-thoughts&quot;&gt;Final Thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The AgileBits team have definitely outdone themselves. Not only is this update to 1Password beautiful, the new features and menubar app, make the upgrade very worth it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’ve never used 1Password, this is a perfect time to purchase. In this day and age, it’s crucial to have secure passwords. This is an app you’ll later wonder how you did without.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It seems you can’t currently purchase the new 1Password from &lt;a href=&quot;https://agilebits.com/store&quot;&gt;the AgileBits store&lt;/a&gt;, but that is where it’ll be very soon.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:3&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:3&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; You can also purchase from &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/1password/id443987910?mt=12&quot;&gt;the Mac App Store&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update:&lt;/strong&gt; You can now purchase and/or upgrade on &lt;a href=&quot;https://agilebits.com/store&quot;&gt;the AgileBits store&lt;/a&gt;. Seems my speculation was wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;further-reading&quot;&gt;Further Reading&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.agilebits.com/2013/08/31/how-long-should-my-passwords-be/&quot;&gt;How long should my passwords be?&lt;/a&gt; - If you’re interested in making generated passwords from 1Password very secure, I definitely recommend this article by the AgileBits team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;This might seem like a small thing, but it’s one of my favorite additions to 1Password. I used to copy the password then press the fill button, and now those two actions are done with one press. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:2&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;By the way, you can use &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.macbartender.com/&quot;&gt;Bartender&lt;/a&gt; to clean that menubar up.  &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:2&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:3&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;This is only speculation, but I wonder if they’re required to give the App Store preference for a set amount of time. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:3&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/babblenut-9</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/babblenut-9"/>
    <title>Babblenut: I’m Not Scared of the Feels</title>
    <published>2013-10-02T18:58:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-10-02T18:58:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This week: Paul and I talk about Breaking Bad, being grateful, learning to be an advocate, and much more.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/contentment-and-feeling-grateful</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/contentment-and-feeling-grateful"/>
    <title>Contentment and Being Grateful</title>
    <published>2013-10-02T14:56:56-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-10-02T14:56:56-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We all have our moments when we feel down. In my case, the past two years have been full of personal mistakes and bad decisions. Failure is difficult to accept. Yet, these things considered, it’s not the end; the book has not yet been finished, even when at times, it certainly feels like it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although, anyone would’ve considered me an optimist a year ago, it’s not so easy in practice. Yet, something I’ve forced myself to do, is always remember I have reasons to be grateful. I think it’s a good idea to do this whether you’re going through a tough time or not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I live in a very privileged part of the world, and I often get wrapped up in my own problems, client frustrations, and whining about stupidities, that I forget how much worse it could really be. My alarm in the morning could be a bomb, instead of my cute cat, and I could be in a perpetual state of worry. There are people going through much worse than I’ve &lt;em&gt;ever&lt;/em&gt; gone through, and that empathy allows me to step back and look at my life objectively.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My life isn’t perfect. I don’t make nearly as much money as I’d like, I’ve been a disappointment to people who care about me, I have debt that is far away from being paid off, I’m overweight, and I’ve hurt a girl I was in love with, twice… twice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, I have parents, family and friends that love me, and add meaning to my life. I’m healthy. I haven’t gone hungry. I work in an amazing industry, where I can say I love my job. And I live in a beautiful place that enjoys the four amazing seasons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happiness and contentment are a choice, and I &lt;em&gt;choose&lt;/em&gt; to be happy, I &lt;em&gt;choose&lt;/em&gt; to be grateful for what I have, I &lt;em&gt;choose&lt;/em&gt; to make lemonade out of lemons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Should I pour you a glass?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This post was originally written for &lt;a href=&quot;http://the-pastry-box-project.net/&quot;&gt;The Pastry Box&lt;/a&gt;. They have so many people wanting to contribute, that they weren’t able to accept my submission.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/using-portly-for-local-development</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/using-portly-for-local-development"/>
    <title>Using Portly for Local Development</title>
    <published>2013-10-02T09:52:41-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-10-02T09:52:41-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;My friend, &lt;a href=&quot;http://adamstacoviak.com/&quot;&gt;Adam Stacoviak&lt;/a&gt;, pointed me to a tool called &lt;a href=&quot;https://getportly.com/&quot;&gt;Portly&lt;/a&gt;. Portly allows you to display your local web server, publicly. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you look at the Portly site, you can tell that the applications of this menubar app, are many. I’ve been using it to do local device testing without the need for a staging server. This a very basic usage of this powerful app, but it’s been a huge timesaver for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I &lt;em&gt;always&lt;/em&gt; develop sites locally.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; One problem I constantly ran into, is that I wasn’t able to easily test sites on my different devices. Sure, you can use a bookmarklet, resize your browser, or sign up for something like BrowserStack, but I like to test from the comfort of my couch.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:2&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:2&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/2013/10/portly-screenshot.png&quot; alt=&quot;Portly Preferences&quot; title=&quot;Portly Preferences&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is where Portly comes in. I simply add a tunnel in the app, point it to my local connection string,&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:3&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:3&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; turn on the tunnel,  and go to the subdomain on my iPad or iPhone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, I know there are other ways to do this, but I just wasn’t nerdy enough to implement them. Portly is easy, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://getportly.com/plans&quot;&gt;starting at $2.99/month&lt;/a&gt;, a very good deal. You should definitely check it out. If you need help or have questions, ping me on &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/ttimsmith&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#116;&amp;#105;&amp;#109;&amp;#064;&amp;#116;&amp;#104;&amp;#101;&amp;#098;&amp;#111;&amp;#108;&amp;#100;&amp;#114;&amp;#101;&amp;#112;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#116;&amp;#046;&amp;#110;&amp;#101;&amp;#116;&quot;&gt;email me&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;If you’re working on a live server, stop that. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:2&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;I’ve found that QA is much more enjoyable—and effective—when I’m relaxed and comfortable. I turn on the TV for background noise, sit back on the couch, and browse every single page of the site. I find things I need to fix and assign myself GitHub issues. This ritual is often accompanied by a cup of coffee as well. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:2&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:3&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;For example, &lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000&quot;&gt;http://localhost:4000&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:3&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/the-east-wing-71</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/the-east-wing-71"/>
    <title>The East Wing: Scott Johnson</title>
    <published>2013-10-01T16:31:08-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-10-01T16:31:08-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This week: I talk with Scott Johnson about how he got started, takings risks, and being kind to people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bandwidth is provided by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.campaignmonitor.com/&quot;&gt;Campaign Monitor&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/sponsor-the-theme-foundry</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/sponsor-the-theme-foundry"/>
    <title>Sponsor: The Theme Foundry</title>
    <published>2013-10-01T11:32:29-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-10-01T11:32:29-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/cms/images/collections-theme-by-the-theme-foundry.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The Theme Foundry&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://thethemefoundry.com/&quot;&gt;The Theme Foundry&lt;/a&gt; has been building premium WordPress themes since 2008. They recently released Collections – a unique and beautiful WordPress theme for sharing, designed by Veerle Pieters. Visit the &lt;a href=&quot;http://demo.thethemefoundry.com/collections-theme/&quot;&gt;live demo of Collections&lt;/a&gt; to see it in action, or &lt;a href=&quot;http://thethemefoundry.com/wordpress/collections/&quot;&gt;purchase it now for $79&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What makes The Theme Foundry special?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A focus on quality over quantity.&lt;/strong&gt; You won’t find a huge assortment on their site – they keep a small, curated collection of &lt;a href=&quot;http://thethemefoundry.com/wordpress/&quot;&gt;premium WordPress themes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exclusive partner with WordPress.com&lt;/strong&gt; (the official hosted WordPress provider). Each and every theme goes through a stringent audit process from some of the best WordPress coders in the world.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Whole team support.&lt;/strong&gt; You get fast and friendly support from the team that &lt;em&gt;actually built&lt;/em&gt; your theme, not a part time support rep.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Thanks to &lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/s/sl&quot;&gt;The Theme Foundry&lt;/a&gt; for supporting The Bold Report this week. They’re awesome people. You might also want to checkout &lt;a href=&quot;http://memberful.com/&quot;&gt;Memberful&lt;/a&gt;, which is made by the same team.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://syndicateads.net/&quot;&gt;Sponsorship by The Syndicate.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/an-argument-for-app-net</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/an-argument-for-app-net"/>
    <title>An Argument for App.net</title>
    <published>2013-09-30T16:17:17-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-09-30T16:17:17-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Chris Enns:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The peo­ple who scoff at App​.net and won­der “why do we need another Twit­ter?” are missing the point. Actu­ally, they’re miss­ing the point of the inter­net. There’s plenty of room for another social net­work. You don’t have to use it but that doesn’t make it invalid. For every per­son that makes fun of Google+, there’s another 5 peo­ple get­ting a lot of com­mu­nity and fun out of it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, this article is talking about Favd, yet almost accidentally, he describes what I think is a very convincing argument for App.net’s relevance. Chris goes on to say:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;And while Favd might look like “yet another Insta­gram clone”, it’s tak­ing the parts of Insta­gram that peo­ple enjoy — tak­ing and shar­ing pho­tos with friends online — and leav­ing behind the cor­po­rate shadi­ness that comes with being asso­ci­ated with Facebook.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chris effectively points out, that just when we think a market has been saturated beyond belief, there’s always someone who can approach a problem a bit smarter.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/apple-becomes-most-valuable-brand-of-2013</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/apple-becomes-most-valuable-brand-of-2013"/>
    <title>Apple Becomes ‘Most Valuable Brand’ of 2013</title>
    <published>2013-09-30T12:05:04-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-09-30T12:05:04-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Apple has taken the top spot as 2013′s Most Valuable Brand, ending Coca-Cola’s 13 year streak as number one in the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.interbrand.com/en/best-global-brands/2013/Best-Global-Brands-2013-Brand-View.aspx&quot;&gt;annual Best Global Brands report&lt;/a&gt; compiled by Interbrand. Coca-Cola ended up third, surpassed by both Apple and Google this year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think this is pretty big news. A company’s brand is based a lot on public perception, and for Apple and Google to surpass Coca-Cola, which in my opinion is the one of the best brands ever created,&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; is quite the compliment on how they’re doing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;You know you agree with that. Whether you’re a Coke lover, or Pepsi lover (Oh god, can I footnote the footnote?), Coca-Cola has been advertising it’s drink with bears… bears. If you can advertise your product without taking cheap shots at your competitor, you’re doing well. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/google-web-designer</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/google-web-designer"/>
    <title>Google Web Designer</title>
    <published>2013-09-30T11:41:11-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-09-30T11:41:11-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, I see a tool like this from Google, and my whole opinion changes. I had some pretty harsh things to say about Macaw.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Google—in many ways—is the reason I do my job the way I do it. They’re advocates for building the web well, and fast. It’s hard for me to believe they’ll make a tool that does the opposite.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;I don’t know what happened to the tweet. But, I basically said that Macaw holds designers back from doing what they should do: learn to code. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/the-14-hour-work-day-myth</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/the-14-hour-work-day-myth"/>
    <title>The 14-Hour Work Day Myth</title>
    <published>2013-09-27T16:02:02-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-09-27T16:02:02-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Once I discovered the best times I like to work as a freelancer, I realized, why would I want to be working past that anyways? I love my job but I also love doing things outside my job. These things bring me great happiness and satisfaction, in turn, giving me the motivation and passion needed to perform effectively at my job.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love when people write about how working long hours is not a good idea. I love it when someone like Janna Hagan—whom I admire very much—does it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of which, have a great weekend!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/making-star-wars-great-again</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/making-star-wars-great-again"/>
    <title>Making Star Wars Great Again</title>
    <published>2013-09-27T16:01:57-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-09-27T16:01:57-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This is just magical. I think Abrams should bring this guy on board as a technical advisor in charge of proper use of the force.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Agreed.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/document-everything</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/document-everything"/>
    <title>Document Everything</title>
    <published>2013-09-27T14:35:13-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-09-27T14:35:13-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Something I’ve been thinking about a lot recently is documentation. And yes, I’m thinking a little bit about legacy—documenting our life, and the things we make. However, I also mean documenting our process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s a lot of mystery surrounding what we do. I remember being a newcomer and feeling overwhelmed by everything it seemed that I needed to learn. This is where I think documentation can help us a lot. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As an industry, we’re getting comfortable with doing things in the open. &lt;a href=&quot;http://opensourcedesign.is/&quot;&gt;Open Source Design&lt;/a&gt; is trying to do this, a project which I happen to be a contributor on, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://opensourcedesign.is/resourced/&quot;&gt;there are other people doing it&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what about being open about what we charge for services? What about talking about how much designers should be making in a beginning job? Medium level? Senior level? Should we negotiate for a signing bonus? Do companies still do this? To be very honest, I only learned about some of these things a couple months ago when I had dinner with my friend &lt;a href=&quot;http://bermonpainter.com/&quot;&gt;Bermon&lt;/a&gt;. Why is this such a mystery?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On a more personal level, what about our process? I have no documentation of my personal design and development process. All of it lives in my head, which quite frankly, isn’t useful for anyone. Pricing projects could be so much simpler if I had a process to run them through. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a lot of ways, I don’t know what I’m doing. Yet, at the same time, I really do. But that knowledge is wasted if I don’t share it with others. Not to mention, there will always be people that can benefit from something I’ve learned. We’re all in different places of our career.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the past month, I’ve met so many smart people who are saying nothing. They have great ideas, but they don’t tell anyone about them. Then, there are others who are content with believing in mythical gatekeepers that prevent them from having a voice in this industry.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It’s rubbish.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to have a voice, if you want to contribute, document everything. Tell people about what you’re doing, why you did it that way, and why others should think about doing it the same. We need your voice, but no one is going to beg you to use it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As cliché as it might sound, anyone has the power to make our industry better, and personally that’s why I love our industry and working in the open. When many minds come together and collaborate and share, the end result is one-hundred times better. When more people share, we have a more diverse group of people to admire, to interview, to invite to speak, etc. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Step up. Document everything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;further-reading&quot;&gt;Further Reading&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.garann.com/dev/2013/how-to-blog-about-code-and-give-zero-fucks/&quot;&gt;How To Blog About Code and Give Zero *****&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;This particularly makes me mad. It’s so high-school drama. If you want to do something, do it. Complaining isn’t productive. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/the-app-store-problem</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/the-app-store-problem"/>
    <title>The App Store Problem</title>
    <published>2013-09-25T11:50:17-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-09-25T11:50:17-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Stephen Hackett on 512 Pixels:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The bottom line is this: developers should be able to work on their product in a sustainable way. Realmac are some of the good guys, and to have to backtrack on a business decision is a damn shame, especially in a world where people pour money into IAP-based games day and night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a real problem. We can obviously see a huge hole in the App Store ecosystem. Honestly, I have no idea if Apple will ever implement upgrade pricing. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.imore.com/apple-puts-its-price-tag-where-its-policy-charges-full-price-logic-pro-x-mac-app-store&quot;&gt;Signs point to no&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple desperately needs to examine this problem, and understand that the beautiful ecosystem it’s created, could crumble because of issues like this. And as the person purchasing software, I need to understand that developers &lt;strong&gt;are in their right&lt;/strong&gt; to charge money for new software. I love what &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/marcoarment/status/382899550341853184&quot;&gt;Marco Arment said&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Upset about &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/realmacsoftware&quot;&gt;@realmacsoftware&lt;/a&gt; asking for another 3 dollars for a big update to Clear and going universal?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;You should be ashamed of yourself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/deployments-with-github-and-ssh</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/deployments-with-github-and-ssh"/>
    <title>Deployments with GitHub and SSH</title>
    <published>2013-09-25T11:12:03-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-09-25T11:12:03-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I had no idea that deployments could be this easy. Which surprises me, because I thought I had explored my deployment options. Kennedy was kind enough to make a video too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Obviously this route is a bit nerdy, so if you want something that’s managed for you, I recommend &lt;a href=&quot;http://beanstalkapp.com/&quot;&gt;Beanstalk&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;http://deployhq.com/&quot;&gt;Deploy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/theeastwing-70</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/theeastwing-70"/>
    <title>The East Wing: Jeremy Fuksa</title>
    <published>2013-09-24T16:15:55-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-09-24T16:15:55-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This week: I talk with Jeremy Fuksa about being a design director, hiring designers, and the side-projects he works on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bandwidth is kindly provided by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.campaignmonitor.com/&quot;&gt;Campaign Monitor&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/marco-arments-lastest-project-overcast</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/marco-arments-lastest-project-overcast"/>
    <title>Marco Arment’s Latest Project: Overcast</title>
    <published>2013-09-24T11:29:01-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-09-24T11:29:01-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;If you need tons of features or anything I’m choosing not to do, you’ll probably be happier with one of the others. (Before I started using Overcast full-time, Downcast was my podcast app of choice.)&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;I’m adding some new stuff that I haven’t seen before in podcast players, and implementing what I think is the best set of core features from the existing apps. It’s my ideal podcast app.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is why I love Marco Arment. It happens to be the reason he’s also very successful. He trusts his gut, which I think is one of the most difficult things to learn how to do. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Marco isn’t given enough credit as a designer. He may not create the visuals for all of his products, but he is very deliberate with his design decisions. Can’t wait for this app.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/sustainable-web</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/sustainable-web"/>
    <title>James Christie on Sustainable Web Design</title>
    <published>2013-09-24T10:10:39-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-09-24T10:10:39-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;At 1.4MB, today’s average page is 15 times larger than it was 10 years ago, primarily due to images (881kB) and script (224kB). Plain old HTML totals just 54kB—but when’s the last time you saw an HTML-only site? This average page also makes more than 100 HTTP requests. Whether they fetch a big object or a small one, these add up to more delay and more power wastage. The average site is also slow: Alexa’s top 2,000 retailer sites now take an average of more than seven seconds to load—much longer than users consider acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We published &lt;a href=&quot;http://alistapart.com/issue/383&quot;&gt;a great issue&lt;/a&gt; today, but this particular article written by &lt;a href=&quot;http://jcux.co.uk/&quot;&gt;James Christie&lt;/a&gt; caught my eye. I’ve been doing a lot of research into performance, but I’d stupidly never thought how slow sites can have an impact on our environment. Site performance matters; not only to visitors, but to our planet.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/apple-iphone-touchscreen-faster-than-android-devices</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/apple-iphone-touchscreen-faster-than-android-devices"/>
    <title>Apple iPhone Touchscreen Faster than Android Devices</title>
    <published>2013-09-23T14:17:25-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-09-23T14:17:25-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Apple’s iPhone 5 is 2.5 times faster at responding to touches than Google Android devices, according to a benchmark test by game and app streaming firm Agawi.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This doesn’t surprise me at all. The level of care and detail Apple spends on this type of stuff is the reason people line up in the rain to get their devices. The article goes on to explain:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;the iPhone 5 responded to touches at an average time of 55 milliseconds…. The closest Android device was the Samsung Galaxy S4 at 114 milliseconds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s almost ridiculous to be examining this at the millisecond level, but tell me you’ve never noticed this delay when borrowing an Android device from a someone.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; Those small details matter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Because you don’t own one do you? &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/netflix-first-to-win-emmy-award-for-online-only-shows</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/netflix-first-to-win-emmy-award-for-online-only-shows"/>
    <title>Netflix First to Win Emmy Award for Online-Only Shows</title>
    <published>2013-09-23T14:03:04-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-09-23T14:03:04-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Netflix made history tonight, winning three Emmy awards for House of Cards, becoming the first company to win the awards for online-only shows. Original shows produced by Netflix had received 14 nominations — 9 of those for House of Cards alone. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is huge. I’ve said it before, and I’ll say it again: Netflix gets it. They’re making entertaining shows, and minimizing piracy. Traditional television hasn’t been able to nail both.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/blackberry-receives-buyout-offer</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/blackberry-receives-buyout-offer"/>
    <title>BlackBerry Receives Buyout Offer</title>
    <published>2013-09-23T12:50:07-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-09-23T12:50:07-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;BlackBerry has officially filed a letter with Canadian holding company Fairfax Financial, an offer that could lead to it returning to private ownership.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This could be a good thing for them. I remember when BlackBerry was on top, and then fell to the pits of irrelevance. Personally, I hope this helps them get their act together. I believe that the smartphone market will only continue to get better with better competition.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/apple-sells-nine-million-iphones</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/apple-sells-nine-million-iphones"/>
    <title>Apple Sells Nine Million iPhones in a Weekend</title>
    <published>2013-09-23T11:43:37-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-09-23T11:43:37-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Apple® today announced it has sold a record-breaking nine million new iPhone® 5s and iPhone 5c models, just three days after the launch of the new iPhones on September 20. In addition, more than 200 million iOS devices are now running the completely redesigned iOS 7, making it the fastest software upgrade in history.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every time the worlds says Apple is done, they come and do something like this. It’s also interesting to note that &lt;a href=&quot;http://news.cnet.com/8301-1035_3-57603876-94/samsung-sends-spies-to-uncover-apples-iphone-line-phenom/&quot;&gt;Samsung sent out a film crew to the iPhone lines&lt;/a&gt;. None of the competitors get why people are so passionate about Apple’s products.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/welcome</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/welcome"/>
    <title>Dear Reader,</title>
    <published>2013-09-23T00:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-09-23T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Welcome to &lt;em&gt;The Bold Report&lt;/em&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been pondering the creation of a blog for quite some time now. In the past few months, I’ve felt that the goals I have for my writing have outgrown my personal site, and it was time to move it to its own home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Bold Report&lt;/em&gt; is that new home. If you were a fan of my personal blog, you’ll see most of the same content on here. There will be long form articles which address topics that are on my mind, and links which point you to great content or exciting news around the web. As I have before, the links will have my commentary, which I’ve found that people appreciate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The purpose of this site &lt;em&gt;is not&lt;/em&gt; to report on breaking news—there are many other sites doing that—rather to inform you of exciting new technology, products you should keep your eye on, or what I happen to be learning at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We live in fascinating times. The evolution of technology is not only influencing how we design and develop experiences, it is changing the way we interact with others and our surroundings. Whole industries have been re-imagined, and that will only continue to happen. If nothing else, I want this blog to document that, and show my predictions as false or accurate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is my hope that you’ll join me on this journey. You can find the different ways to subscribe on the &lt;a href=&quot;/subscribe/&quot;&gt;subscribe page&lt;/a&gt;. Although there are no comments on this site, please feel free to reach me &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/ttimsmith&quot;&gt;via Twitter&lt;/a&gt; or email me at &lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#110;&amp;#116;&amp;#097;&amp;#099;&amp;#116;&amp;#064;&amp;#116;&amp;#104;&amp;#101;&amp;#098;&amp;#111;&amp;#108;&amp;#100;&amp;#114;&amp;#101;&amp;#112;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#116;&amp;#046;&amp;#110;&amp;#101;&amp;#116;&quot;&gt;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#110;&amp;#116;&amp;#097;&amp;#099;&amp;#116;&amp;#064;&amp;#116;&amp;#104;&amp;#101;&amp;#098;&amp;#111;&amp;#108;&amp;#100;&amp;#114;&amp;#101;&amp;#112;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#116;&amp;#046;&amp;#110;&amp;#101;&amp;#116;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for reading, it means a lot to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;—Tim&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  

</feed>
