<?xml version="1.0"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <link rel="hub" href="https://pubsubhubbub.appspot.com"/>

  <title>The Bold Report - Articles Only</title>
  <link href="http://theboldreport.net"/>
  <link type="application/atom+xml" rel="self" href="http://theboldreport.net/feed.article.xml"/>
  <updated>2013-10-25T12:05:11-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://theboldreport.net</id>
  <author>
    <name>Tim Smith</name>
    <email>smith@ttimsmith.com</email>
  </author>

  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/our-first-month</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/our-first-month"/>
    <title>A Look Back on Our First Month</title>
    <published>2013-10-23T12:48:50-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-10-23T12:48:50-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A month ago today, I launched &lt;em&gt;The Bold Report&lt;/em&gt;. I’m so glad I did it, and we’ve had some pretty great growth in our first month!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First of all, if you’re reading this, I want to say thank you. This site is something I’ve been wanting to do for a long time. I love writing about my interests, and I love the fact that there are people like you, who have similar passions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;now-for-some-stats&quot;&gt;Now for Some Stats&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The site has been viewed 5,013 times, and people stay an average of two minutes. The site had 3,006 visitors, 1,313 of which were returning. 1,902 visitors are from the United States, the United Kingdom came in second place with 399.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not surprisingly, the two most common mobile devices the site is viewed on, are iOS devices. Coming in first place: iPhone with sixty-two percent. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chrome was the popular browser, responsible for fifty-six percent of traffic. Nine people visited from Internet Explorer.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; Most visitors are using a Mac, but twelve percent is on Windows.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:2&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:2&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The number one source of referrals was Twitter with 1,560, my personal site in third place, and Sidebar.io coming in fourth. The main RSS feed currently has twelve subscribers, and the Twitter account has sixty-six followers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;top-five-posts&quot;&gt;Top Five Posts&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the first month, these were the top posts:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/freelancing-and-saying-no/&quot;&gt;Freelancing and Saying “No”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/document-everything/&quot;&gt;Document Everything&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/review-1password-4-for-mac/&quot;&gt;Review: 1Password 4 for Mac&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/welcome/&quot;&gt;Dear Reader,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/using-portly-for-local-development/&quot;&gt;Using Portly for Local Development&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;giveaway&quot;&gt;Giveaway&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a token of my appreciation, I wanted to give away two &lt;a href=&quot;https://tonx.org/&quot;&gt;“The Standard” Tonx Coffee Subscriptions&lt;/a&gt;. I’ll personally pay for your first month, which includes two shipments of great-tasting coffee. The winners will be choosen at random on Friday at 1pm Central. Here’s what you have to do to win:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Follow &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/theboldreport&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Bold Report&lt;/em&gt; on Twitter&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mention @theboldreport, and tell me what you like about the site, and what I could possibly do better.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In closing, a huge thank you to everyone who has followed, subscribed, and read. I sincerely appreciate all of your support, and I hope you continue to find the content here, of interest to you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;—Tim&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Even that, was a bigger number that I would’ve thought. Thanks IE folks! Hope you can see everything well! &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:2&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Again, a bigger number than I thought. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:2&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/apple-event-day</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/apple-event-day"/>
    <title>Apple Event Day</title>
    <published>2013-10-22T10:40:36-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-10-22T10:40:36-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Apple Event Days are always exciting for me, and this one will be no different.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ll be able to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.apple.com/apple-events/october-2013/&quot;&gt;watch the event live&lt;/a&gt; on your iOS device, Mac, or Apple TV. &lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; During the event, I’ll be in the &lt;em&gt;#ssktn&lt;/em&gt; iRC chatroom, as a kind of virtual-viewing party. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the event, Chris Enns, Kyle Roderick, and myself will be talking about the event and new gadgets on the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ssktn.com/live/&quot;&gt;SSKTN live stream&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happy Apple Event Day!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;I’m so glad they’ve started to stream most of these events on the Apple TV. It seems that the only one they’re not streaming live these days is WWDC, which is totally understandable. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/freelancing-and-saying-no</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/freelancing-and-saying-no"/>
    <title>Freelancing and Saying “No”</title>
    <published>2013-10-18T12:06:47-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-10-18T12:06:47-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;No. That word has been given lots of importance in our industry and rightly so. &lt;a href=&quot;http://vimeo.com/53155584&quot;&gt;Jason Santa Maria spoke about it&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/the-year-of-the-looking-glass/23ad80bdfbc&quot;&gt;Julie Zhuo wrote about it&lt;/a&gt;, and I’m sure you’ve read your fair share of articles on the topic. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a powerful word, and I’m glad that we’re a community that looks out for each other and is willing to share with newcomers how to avoid bad projects. There are some relationships that will rob you of your joy, and in the end cost you more money than you’re being paid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, I think it’s been given a misleading reputation. Lots of people confuse saying no,with turning down projects they don’t deem as “fun”. In some articles, I’ve seen it turn into advice that only strokes the growing ego that many designers have. We turn something great, into snobbery and haughtiness. Consequently, people are given the wrong impression of what saying no actually means.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;tim-my-business-is-already-struggling-and-you-expect-me-to-say-no-to-a-project&quot;&gt;“Tim, my business is already struggling and you expect me to say no to a project?”&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course not. I always take projects that help keep the lights on. Everyone does. If they say they don’t, they’re lying. Not every single project will meet all of your requirements &lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;, and even the ones that do will have difficulties and moments of frustration. That’s just a fact of life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saying no means to turn down projects that will kill you or your business. You know exactly what I’m talking about. The client that you’re having a preliminary meeting with, and your gut tells you that you shouldn’t work with the person. The reason could be one of many. They don’t know what they want, they want to pay you considerably less, they’re condescending, whatever. That’s when you say no.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s important to note that someone with a low budget isn’t always a red flag. Learn to trust your gut. You’ll know when it’s a good idea to work for less money, and when it’s just someone that’s trying to take advantage. If you still don’t know, ask a friend. Don’t have someone to ask? Email me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;but-i-need-the-money&quot;&gt;“But I need the money!”&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You think you’re poor now? Just wait till you’re working an insane amount of hours on an insane budget. What happens when you finally get sick of it? Do you fire the client? Will you have to issue a refund? How do you pay for that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trust me, something else will come up. I’ve been hours away from having no money in the bank with no prospects of money, and something has always come up.In all honesty, it’s better to pick up a shift at Starbucks, than work in a toxic relationship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;im-freelancing-so-i-can-have-fun&quot;&gt;“I’m freelancing so I can have fun.”&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Freelancing is work. There are a lot of hardships. Lots of anxiety. Lots of stress. Maybe even playing “credit card shuffle”. &lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:2&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:2&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; Not every day is going to be fun, and that’s something you have to come to terms with. However, it’s also very rewarding. I wake up when I want, I work when I want, I get to choose my clients,&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:3&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:3&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; I can choose to collaborate with other designers, developers, etc., and I can work from wherever there is internet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ll land three projects one month, and have no work the next.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:4&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:4&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; Money management becomes crucial when you freelance. But, don’t worry. If I can do it—and I’m literally the best blower of money—you can definitely do it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;wrapping-up&quot;&gt;Wrapping Up&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All projects aren’t going to be fun, and they won’t all be big brands or names. Learn to appreciate projects that allow you to work with people who care, make an impact on peoples lives, and teach you new things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not all clients are bad. Most are well-meaning people who are trying to do their best by their business or company. Saying no, should never satisfy an emotional need to rebel. Instead, it should be educated by the goals of your business, and that of the client. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In closing, remember that the objective of saying no, will give you the opportunity to say yes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;further-reading&quot;&gt;Further Reading&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.franklincovey.com/blog/effectively.html&quot;&gt;Saying “No” Effectively&lt;/a&gt; — Via &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.markrondina.com/&quot;&gt;Mark Rondina&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A very sincere thank you to &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hamstu&quot;&gt;Hamish Macpherson&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/mattriopelle&quot;&gt;Matt Riopelle&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/mrondina&quot;&gt;Mark Rondina&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/sara_ann_marie&quot;&gt;Sara Wachter-Boettcher&lt;/a&gt;, for their help in editing this article.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;You’re the one that decides what those requirements are. For me, I have an internal checklist. Is the project fun? Do I believe in the message of the project and the company trying to communicate it? Does the client show respect for me, my work, and my time? Who else will I be working with? What will I learn? Will I be able to display the work in my portfolio? Do I have time? Is the budget reasonable? &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:2&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;This is when you pay one card with another card. Or you’re paying bills with a credit card. It’s scary stuff. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:2&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:3&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;This is true whether you have clients are not. You’re &lt;strong&gt;never&lt;/strong&gt; forced to work on something you don’t want to. Even if the work is horrible, it was &lt;em&gt;my choice&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:3&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;July was killer. September was dry. Feast or famine. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:4&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/review-1password-4-for-mac</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/review-1password-4-for-mac"/>
    <title>Review: 1Password 4 for Mac</title>
    <published>2013-10-03T00:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-10-03T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://agilebits.com/onepassword&quot;&gt;1Password&lt;/a&gt; is one of my favorite apps. The amount of time it has saved me is unmeasurable, and it’s made my password strategy secure and delightful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those of you who don’t know about 1Password, it’s a great utility app to store and generate passwords. For years, I was the person who had &lt;em&gt;the same password for everything&lt;/em&gt;. With 1Password, I don’t do that anymore, I’m able to search through weak passwords and generate stronger ones, making it less likely to get hacked. Even if that does happen, none of my passwords are the same, so I only need to reset the one that’s been compromised.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;first-impressions&quot;&gt;First Impressions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The new interface is beautiful, and obviously influenced by the iOS version.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The Chrome extension got a facelift, and generated passwords are not only filled in forms, they’re also copied to your clipboard.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;1Password Mini brings most of the power of the main app to the menubar. This is great for entering passwords into apps that aren’t the browser. I disliked having to open the main app to do this in previous versions.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;new-features-in-1password-4-for-mac&quot;&gt;New Features in 1Password 4 for Mac&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;design&quot;&gt;Design&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first thing you’ll notice when you open the new 1Password is the beautiful interface. If you’ve already purchased &lt;a href=&quot;https://agilebits.com/onepassword/ios&quot;&gt;the latest iOS app&lt;/a&gt;, you’ll notice that the new design is very similar, which delights me greatly. This redesign is years overdue, and the AgileBits team has delivered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://theboldreport.net/uploads/2013/10/1p4-mac-main.png&quot; alt=&quot;1Password 4 for Mac main view&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love that this redesign in a lot of ways is a re-align. The interface remains in the three column layout, yet with an easy-on-the-eyes, light background. The type has greatly improved, and the middle column no longer has the “shelf” look. The new layout, allows you to see more logins in the window without having to scroll and sports better looking icons. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thankfully, the last column has been redone too. It used to be confusing to look at, and honestly, I didn’t know what was going on. It’s now a lot more simplified and only displays necessary information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That being said, my favorite part of the main view, is the new “Security Audit” that appears in the far left column. It gives you easy access to weak passwords, duplicate passwords, and passwords that are old and might need to be changed. To be clear, this type of filtering has always been present in 1Password, but the fact that it’s now front and center, is very valuable to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;multiple-vaults&quot;&gt;Multiple Vaults&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One feature that I can see becoming very popular is the new feature of multiple vaults. I haven’t actually been using this feature, but it’s one of those things that I think could help me organize the different sets of passwords. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is especially true when I worked for a company. Having a separate vault exclusively for company logins, would’ve been a great way to get organized. This makes managing items easier, and makes cleaning out items you no longer need, a breeze.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://theboldreport.net/uploads/2013/10/1p4-mac-create-new-vault.png&quot; alt=&quot;Create a new vault&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;password-mini&quot;&gt;1Password Mini&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love that they made a menubar app. I’m definitely one of those people that has &lt;em&gt;way too many&lt;/em&gt; of them.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:2&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:2&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; Interestingly, the menubar app is what comes up now when you press &lt;code&gt;⌘CMD + \&lt;/code&gt;. It seems that the 1Password browser extension is now only needed to run the code necessary for the autofill. You’ll never actually need to press the button anymore, which is nice, because it’s one less button in the extensions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://theboldreport.net/uploads/2013/10/1p4-mac-1p-mini-item-details.png&quot; alt=&quot;1Password Mini details&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s too early for me to say, but I think 1Password Mini could completely replace the main app for me. So far, I haven’t needed to open the main app for day-to-day responsibilities. To be honest, I only looked at the main app the day I downloaded it, and today when writing this review.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;other-features-you-should-know-about&quot;&gt;Other Features You Should Know About&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shared Items&lt;/strong&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;
Till now, I haven’t needed to ever share login items, but I can definitely see the practicality of this. You can share items with email or iMessage, and if the person makes changes, the item automatically updates when shared back.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;256-bit Authenticated Encryption&lt;/strong&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;
I have no idea what this means, except that 1Password is constantly being updated to be more and more secure. From what I’m told, this prevents attacks that don’t even exist yet.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wifi Sync&lt;/strong&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;
This feature is back from previous versions. Personally, I use Dropbox to sync my Vault between my Mac, iPad and iPhone, but whatever floats your boat. They have iCloud sync too.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;final-thoughts&quot;&gt;Final Thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The AgileBits team have definitely outdone themselves. Not only is this update to 1Password beautiful, the new features and menubar app, make the upgrade very worth it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’ve never used 1Password, this is a perfect time to purchase. In this day and age, it’s crucial to have secure passwords. This is an app you’ll later wonder how you did without.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It seems you can’t currently purchase the new 1Password from &lt;a href=&quot;https://agilebits.com/store&quot;&gt;the AgileBits store&lt;/a&gt;, but that is where it’ll be very soon.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:3&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:3&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; You can also purchase from &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/1password/id443987910?mt=12&quot;&gt;the Mac App Store&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update:&lt;/strong&gt; You can now purchase and/or upgrade on &lt;a href=&quot;https://agilebits.com/store&quot;&gt;the AgileBits store&lt;/a&gt;. Seems my speculation was wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;further-reading&quot;&gt;Further Reading&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.agilebits.com/2013/08/31/how-long-should-my-passwords-be/&quot;&gt;How long should my passwords be?&lt;/a&gt; - If you’re interested in making generated passwords from 1Password very secure, I definitely recommend this article by the AgileBits team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;This might seem like a small thing, but it’s one of my favorite additions to 1Password. I used to copy the password then press the fill button, and now those two actions are done with one press. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:2&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;By the way, you can use &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.macbartender.com/&quot;&gt;Bartender&lt;/a&gt; to clean that menubar up.  &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:2&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:3&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;This is only speculation, but I wonder if they’re required to give the App Store preference for a set amount of time. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:3&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/contentment-and-feeling-grateful</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/contentment-and-feeling-grateful"/>
    <title>Contentment and Being Grateful</title>
    <published>2013-10-02T14:56:56-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-10-02T14:56:56-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We all have our moments when we feel down. In my case, the past two years have been full of personal mistakes and bad decisions. Failure is difficult to accept. Yet, these things considered, it’s not the end; the book has not yet been finished, even when at times, it certainly feels like it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although, anyone would’ve considered me an optimist a year ago, it’s not so easy in practice. Yet, something I’ve forced myself to do, is always remember I have reasons to be grateful. I think it’s a good idea to do this whether you’re going through a tough time or not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I live in a very privileged part of the world, and I often get wrapped up in my own problems, client frustrations, and whining about stupidities, that I forget how much worse it could really be. My alarm in the morning could be a bomb, instead of my cute cat, and I could be in a perpetual state of worry. There are people going through much worse than I’ve &lt;em&gt;ever&lt;/em&gt; gone through, and that empathy allows me to step back and look at my life objectively.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My life isn’t perfect. I don’t make nearly as much money as I’d like, I’ve been a disappointment to people who care about me, I have debt that is far away from being paid off, I’m overweight, and I’ve hurt a girl I was in love with, twice… twice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, I have parents, family and friends that love me, and add meaning to my life. I’m healthy. I haven’t gone hungry. I work in an amazing industry, where I can say I love my job. And I live in a beautiful place that enjoys the four amazing seasons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happiness and contentment are a choice, and I &lt;em&gt;choose&lt;/em&gt; to be happy, I &lt;em&gt;choose&lt;/em&gt; to be grateful for what I have, I &lt;em&gt;choose&lt;/em&gt; to make lemonade out of lemons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Should I pour you a glass?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This post was originally written for &lt;a href=&quot;http://the-pastry-box-project.net/&quot;&gt;The Pastry Box&lt;/a&gt;. They have so many people wanting to contribute, that they weren’t able to accept my submission.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/using-portly-for-local-development</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/10/using-portly-for-local-development"/>
    <title>Using Portly for Local Development</title>
    <published>2013-10-02T09:52:41-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-10-02T09:52:41-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;My friend, &lt;a href=&quot;http://adamstacoviak.com/&quot;&gt;Adam Stacoviak&lt;/a&gt;, pointed me to a tool called &lt;a href=&quot;https://getportly.com/&quot;&gt;Portly&lt;/a&gt;. Portly allows you to display your local web server, publicly. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you look at the Portly site, you can tell that the applications of this menubar app, are many. I’ve been using it to do local device testing without the need for a staging server. This a very basic usage of this powerful app, but it’s been a huge timesaver for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I &lt;em&gt;always&lt;/em&gt; develop sites locally.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; One problem I constantly ran into, is that I wasn’t able to easily test sites on my different devices. Sure, you can use a bookmarklet, resize your browser, or sign up for something like BrowserStack, but I like to test from the comfort of my couch.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:2&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:2&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/2013/10/portly-screenshot.png&quot; alt=&quot;Portly Preferences&quot; title=&quot;Portly Preferences&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is where Portly comes in. I simply add a tunnel in the app, point it to my local connection string,&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:3&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:3&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; turn on the tunnel,  and go to the subdomain on my iPad or iPhone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, I know there are other ways to do this, but I just wasn’t nerdy enough to implement them. Portly is easy, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://getportly.com/plans&quot;&gt;starting at $2.99/month&lt;/a&gt;, a very good deal. You should definitely check it out. If you need help or have questions, ping me on &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/ttimsmith&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#116;&amp;#105;&amp;#109;&amp;#064;&amp;#116;&amp;#104;&amp;#101;&amp;#098;&amp;#111;&amp;#108;&amp;#100;&amp;#114;&amp;#101;&amp;#112;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#116;&amp;#046;&amp;#110;&amp;#101;&amp;#116;&quot;&gt;email me&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;If you’re working on a live server, stop that. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:2&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;I’ve found that QA is much more enjoyable—and effective—when I’m relaxed and comfortable. I turn on the TV for background noise, sit back on the couch, and browse every single page of the site. I find things I need to fix and assign myself GitHub issues. This ritual is often accompanied by a cup of coffee as well. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:2&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:3&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;For example, &lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000&quot;&gt;http://localhost:4000&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:3&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/document-everything</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/document-everything"/>
    <title>Document Everything</title>
    <published>2013-09-27T14:35:13-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-09-27T14:35:13-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Something I’ve been thinking about a lot recently is documentation. And yes, I’m thinking a little bit about legacy—documenting our life, and the things we make. However, I also mean documenting our process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s a lot of mystery surrounding what we do. I remember being a newcomer and feeling overwhelmed by everything it seemed that I needed to learn. This is where I think documentation can help us a lot. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As an industry, we’re getting comfortable with doing things in the open. &lt;a href=&quot;http://opensourcedesign.is/&quot;&gt;Open Source Design&lt;/a&gt; is trying to do this, a project which I happen to be a contributor on, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://opensourcedesign.is/resourced/&quot;&gt;there are other people doing it&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what about being open about what we charge for services? What about talking about how much designers should be making in a beginning job? Medium level? Senior level? Should we negotiate for a signing bonus? Do companies still do this? To be very honest, I only learned about some of these things a couple months ago when I had dinner with my friend &lt;a href=&quot;http://bermonpainter.com/&quot;&gt;Bermon&lt;/a&gt;. Why is this such a mystery?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On a more personal level, what about our process? I have no documentation of my personal design and development process. All of it lives in my head, which quite frankly, isn’t useful for anyone. Pricing projects could be so much simpler if I had a process to run them through. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a lot of ways, I don’t know what I’m doing. Yet, at the same time, I really do. But that knowledge is wasted if I don’t share it with others. Not to mention, there will always be people that can benefit from something I’ve learned. We’re all in different places of our career.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the past month, I’ve met so many smart people who are saying nothing. They have great ideas, but they don’t tell anyone about them. Then, there are others who are content with believing in mythical gatekeepers that prevent them from having a voice in this industry.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It’s rubbish.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to have a voice, if you want to contribute, document everything. Tell people about what you’re doing, why you did it that way, and why others should think about doing it the same. We need your voice, but no one is going to beg you to use it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As cliché as it might sound, anyone has the power to make our industry better, and personally that’s why I love our industry and working in the open. When many minds come together and collaborate and share, the end result is one-hundred times better. When more people share, we have a more diverse group of people to admire, to interview, to invite to speak, etc. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Step up. Document everything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;further-reading&quot;&gt;Further Reading&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.garann.com/dev/2013/how-to-blog-about-code-and-give-zero-fucks/&quot;&gt;How To Blog About Code and Give Zero *****&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;This particularly makes me mad. It’s so high-school drama. If you want to do something, do it. Complaining isn’t productive. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/welcome</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://theboldreport.net/2013/09/welcome"/>
    <title>Dear Reader,</title>
    <published>2013-09-23T00:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-09-23T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Smith</name>
      <uri>http://ttimsmith.com/</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Welcome to &lt;em&gt;The Bold Report&lt;/em&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been pondering the creation of a blog for quite some time now. In the past few months, I’ve felt that the goals I have for my writing have outgrown my personal site, and it was time to move it to its own home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Bold Report&lt;/em&gt; is that new home. If you were a fan of my personal blog, you’ll see most of the same content on here. There will be long form articles which address topics that are on my mind, and links which point you to great content or exciting news around the web. As I have before, the links will have my commentary, which I’ve found that people appreciate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The purpose of this site &lt;em&gt;is not&lt;/em&gt; to report on breaking news—there are many other sites doing that—rather to inform you of exciting new technology, products you should keep your eye on, or what I happen to be learning at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We live in fascinating times. The evolution of technology is not only influencing how we design and develop experiences, it is changing the way we interact with others and our surroundings. Whole industries have been re-imagined, and that will only continue to happen. If nothing else, I want this blog to document that, and show my predictions as false or accurate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is my hope that you’ll join me on this journey. You can find the different ways to subscribe on the &lt;a href=&quot;/subscribe/&quot;&gt;subscribe page&lt;/a&gt;. Although there are no comments on this site, please feel free to reach me &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/ttimsmith&quot;&gt;via Twitter&lt;/a&gt; or email me at &lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#110;&amp;#116;&amp;#097;&amp;#099;&amp;#116;&amp;#064;&amp;#116;&amp;#104;&amp;#101;&amp;#098;&amp;#111;&amp;#108;&amp;#100;&amp;#114;&amp;#101;&amp;#112;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#116;&amp;#046;&amp;#110;&amp;#101;&amp;#116;&quot;&gt;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#110;&amp;#116;&amp;#097;&amp;#099;&amp;#116;&amp;#064;&amp;#116;&amp;#104;&amp;#101;&amp;#098;&amp;#111;&amp;#108;&amp;#100;&amp;#114;&amp;#101;&amp;#112;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#116;&amp;#046;&amp;#110;&amp;#101;&amp;#116;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for reading, it means a lot to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;—Tim&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  

</feed>
